  <para_1>THIS DEED OF RATIFICATION AND ACCESSION (the "Deed") is made and issued on [date] by[&#8226;] (Company Registration no. [&#8226;], a company incorporated in Singapore with its registered office at [&#8226;] (the "Company"), in favour of and for the benefit of each and all of the following (other than the Company):- </para_1>
  <bullets>the parties to the shareholders' agreement dated [&#8226;] (the "Shareholders' Agreement") made between, inter alia, XXX, Pte. Ltd. and the Parties listed in Schedule 2 thereto (collectively the "Initial Shareholders"); and </bullets>
  <bullets>all persons and corporations who are or subsequently become shareholders of the Company. </bullets>
  <para_1>WHEREAS:- </para_1>
  <para_1>The Shareholders' Agreement was entered into between the Initial Shareholders to regulate their rights and obligations in relation to, and the affairs of, the Company, a copy of which the Company hereby confirms that it has been supplied with and acknowledges the terms therein. </para_1>
  <para_1>NOW THIS DEED WITNESSES AS FOLLOWS:- </para_1>
  <numbered_1_para>In this Deed, unless the context otherwise requires, words and expressions respectively defined or construed in the Shareholders' Agreement shall have the same meanings when used or referred to herein. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>The Company hereby accedes to and ratifies the Shareholders' Agreement and covenants and agrees with the Initial Shareholders to be bound by the terms of the Shareholders' Agreement as if it had been an original party thereto from the outset and to duly and punctually perform and discharge all liabilities and obligations whatsoever from time to time to be performed or discharged by it under or by virtue of the Shareholders' Agreement in all respects as if named as a party therein. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>Each of the Initial Shareholders covenants and agrees that the Company shall be entitled to all the benefits of the terms and conditions of the Shareholders' Agreement to the intent and effect that the Company shall be deemed, with effect from the date on which the Company executes this Deed, to be a Party to the Shareholders' Agreement. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>This Deed shall hereafter be read and construed in conjunction and as one document with the Shareholders' Agreement and references in the Shareholders' Agreement to "this Agreement", and references in all other instruments and documents executed thereunder or pursuant thereto to the Shareholders' Agreement, shall for all purposes refer to the Shareholders' Agreement incorporating and as supplemented by this Deed. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>A person who is not a party to this Deed shall have no right under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Cap. 53B) of Singapore to enforce any of the provisions in this Deed but this does not affect any right or remedy of a third party which exists or is available apart from that Act. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>All notices to the Company shall be addressed as follows: </numbered_1_para>
  <para_1>data.company.address </para_1>
  <numbered_1_para>This Deed is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore. </numbered_1_para>
  <numbered_1_para>In relation to any legal action or proceedings arising out of or in connection with this Deed and such other documents relating to this Deed, each of the Parties hereby irrevocably submits to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Republic of Singapore, and irrevocably waives any objection on the grounds of forum non conveniens. </numbered_1_para>
  <para_1>IN WITNESS WHEREOF the Parties have hereunto set their hands this Deed has been signed by the [Parties/authorised representatives of the Parties] the day and year first before written. </para_1>
  <para_1>enumerate signatures</para_1>
