<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<? var activeRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound(); ?>
<?!=include("inc_cover_standard_parties",data, {cover_title: data.security_type+" Agreement", rcpts_to:rcpts_to}) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>This document governs the investment.</sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header><?= data.security_type ?> Agreement</chapter_header>
    <para_1><b>THIS AGREEMENT</b> is made on <?=data.investment_agreement_date || '<textvar name="Output Date" ?></para_1>
    <para_1><b>BETWEEN:-</b></para_1>
    <?!=include("inc_enumerate_parties",data) ?>
    <para_1><b>WHEREAS:-</b></para_1>
	<recitals xname="business_description">The Company <?= data.company.description ?>. The issued and paid-up capital of the Company is <?=data.capTable.getActiveRound().post_money ?> comprising <?=digitCommas_(data.capTable.getActiveRound().by_security_type["Class F Shares"].TOTAL) ?> Class F Shares and <?=digitCommas_(data.capTable.getActiveRound().by_security_type["Ordinary Shares"].TOTAL) ?> Ordinary Shares, which are held by the following persons:</recitals>
    <!-- include table -->
    <recitals>The Company has requested the Investors to invest in the Company by subscribing for new preference shares (the Seed Preference Shares) and the Investors have agreed to so invest in the Company, on the terms and subject to the conditions set out in this Agreement.</recitals>
    <para_1><b>NOW IT IS HEREBY AGREED</b> as follows:</para_1>
    <a_left_sidehead>DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION</a_left_sidehead>
    <para_2>In this Agreement, unless the subject or context otherwise requires:-</para_2>
    <numbered_2_para>the following words and expressions shall have the following meanings:-</numbered_2_para>
    <definition_nonum>Act	means the Companies Act (Cap. 50);</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Articles	means the articles of the Constitution of the Company;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Auditors	means the auditors from time to time of the Company;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Balance Sheet Date	means 30 November of each financial year of the Company, until otherwise decided by the Directors;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Board	means the Board of Directors of the Company;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Business Day	means a day when banks in Singapore are open for banking business (but shall not include Saturday, Sunday and gazetted public holidays in Singapore) and Business Days" shall be construed accordingly;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Claim	includes any notice, demand, assessment, letter or other document issued or action taken by the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore or other statutory or governmental authority, body or official whatsoever (whether of Singapore or elsewhere in the world) whereby the Company is or may be placed or sought to be placed under a liability to make payment or deprived of any relief, allowance, credit or repayment otherwise available;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Completion Date	shall either be on <?=data.long_stop_date ?>, or on the Business Day falling five (5) Business Days after the fulfilment (or, as the case may be, waiver) of the last of the conditions precedent set out in Clause <xref to="conditions"/>, or such other date as may be mutually agreed between the Parties;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Designated Bank Account	has the meaning ascribed thereto in Clause <xref to="designated_bank_account"/>;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Directors	means the directors for the time being of the Company;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Dollars	and the sign S$ mean the lawful currency of Singapore;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Equity Shares	has the meaning ascribed thereto in Recital <xref to="business_description"/>;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Founding Shareholders	means <?=commaAnd(data.parties.founder) ?>;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Investor Director	means the members of the Board for the time being and from time to time nominated by the Investor;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Long-Stop Date	means <?=data.long_stop_date ?> or such other date as the Parties may agree;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Key Management	refers to employees of the Company who have the authority to directly or indirectly plan and control business operations of the Company;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Ordinary Shares	means the ordinary shares issued and allotted by the Company from time to time pursuant to the Articles;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Preference Shares	means the preference shares (which shall include the Seed Preference Shares) issued and allotted by the Company from time to time pursuant to the Articles;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Restructuring	has the meaning ascribed thereto in Clause <xref to="restructuring"/>;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Seed Preference Shares	has the meaning ascribed thereto in Recital ;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Shareholders' Agreement	means the shareholders' agreement to be entered into between the Company, the Founding Shareholders and the Investors;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Shares	means the Ordinary Shares andor Preference Shares in the capital of the Company and Share" shall have the corresponding meaning;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Subsidiary	has the meaning ascribed to it in the Act;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Taxation	means all forms of taxation whether of Singapore or elsewhere in the world, past, present and future (including, without limitation, capital gains tax, income tax, estate duty, profits tax, stamp duty, value added tax, purchase tax, goods and services tax, customs and other import or export duties) and all other statutory, governmental or state impositions, duties and levies and all penalties, charges, costs and interest relating to any Claim;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transaction	includes any transaction, act, event or omission of whatever nature;</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Unaudited Accounts	means the management accounts of the Company on a consolidated basis for the period ended <?=data.financial_report_end_date?>, a copy of all of which is set out in <xref to="unaudited_accounts"/>; and</definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Warranties	means the representations and warranties provided by the Company and the Vendors in this Agreement including, without limitation, in Schedule <xref to="warranties" />;</definition_nonum>
    <numbered_2_para>any reference to a statutory provision shall include such provision and any regulations made in pursuance thereof as from time to time modified or reenacted whether before or after the date of this Agreement so far as such modification or reenactment applies or is capable of applying to any transactions entered into prior to completion and (so far as liability thereunder may exist or can arise) shall include also any past statutory provisions or regulations (as from time to time modified or reenacted) which such provisions or regulations have directly or indirectly replaced;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>any reference to "<b>Accounts</b>" shall include cashflow statements, the directors' and auditors' reports, relevant balance sheets and profit and loss accounts and related notes together with all documents which are or would be required by law to be annexed to the accounts of the company concerned to be laid before the company in general meeting for the accounting reference period in question;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>references to Recitals, Clauses, the Schedules and the Appendices are to recitals and clauses of and the schedules and the appendices to this Agreement and references to this "<b>Agreement</b>" shall mean this Agreement, the Schedules and the Appendices;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>the headings in this Agreement are for convenience only and shall not affect the interpretation hereof;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>unless the context otherwise requires, references to the singular number shall include references to the plural number and vice versa; references to natural persons shall include bodies corporate; and the use of any gender shall include all genders; and</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>in this Agreement, unless specified otherwise:</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the rule known as the ejusdem generis rule shall not apply and accordingly general words introduced by the word "other" shall not be given a restrictive meaning by reason of fact that they are preceded by words indicating a particular class of acts, matters or things; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>general words shall not be given a restrictive meaning by reason of the fact that they are followed by particular examples intended to be embraced by the general words; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the contra proferentum rule of construction of contracts shall not apply.</numbered_3_para>
    <a_left_sidehead xname="conditions_p">CONDITIONS PRECEDENT</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="conditions">Conditions. The obligations of each of the Investors under this Agreement are conditional upon the following matters being fulfilled or done on or prior to the Completion Date:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para xname="restructuring">the Company having undertaken and completed the conversion of all existing convertible debt obligations into ordinary shares of the Company;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the satisfactory completion of a legal, financial and business due diligence review, in the reasonable opinion of the Investors, in respect of the operations, business, management and affairs of the Company;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the Warranties being true, complete and accurate in all material respects as at the Completion Date:</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>there having been no material adverse change (as reasonably determined by the Investor) in respect of</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_4_para>the prospects, operations andor financial condition of the Company; or</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_4_para>the economic, political and investment environment in Singapore and/or the other countries in which the Company carries on business;</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the approval of the Investors board of directors and its shareholders (where necessary) being obtained for the entry into this Agreement and for the transactions contemplated herein;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all necessary governmental or regulatory filings, permits or approvals having been made or obtained in connection with this Agreement and the transactions contemplated herein;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all Key Management joining the Company as full-time employees and signing employment agreements with the Company; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the Company and the Investors reaching mutual agreement on the terms of the Shareholders' Agreement.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="by_completion_date">By Completion Date. The Company hereby undertake to use their best endeavours to ensure the satisfaction of the conditions specified in Clause <xref to="conditions"/>. If any of the conditions specified in Clause <xref to="conditions" /> are not fulfilled (or waived by the Investors) by the Long-Stop Date, this Agreement shall ipso facto cease and determine and none of the Parties shall have any claim against the others for costs, damages, compensation or otherwise.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>SUBSCRIPTION</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>Subject to fulfilment or waiver of the conditions precedent set out in Clause <xref to="conditions_p" />, the Investors shall subscribe for the Seed Preference Shares for cash at <?=data.price_per_share ?> per Seed Preference Share on the Completion Date, on the terms and subject to the conditions set out in this Agreement. The Seed Preference Shares shall be allotted and issued to each of the Investors free from all claims and encumbrances and with all rights, benefits and entitlements attaching thereto as at the Completion Date.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The number of Seed Preference Shares that the Other Investors shall subscribe for are as follows:</numbered_2_para>
    <!-- insert table here -->
    <a_left_sidehead xname="completion">COMPLETION</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="venue">Venue. Completion of the subscription for the Seed Preference Shares shall take place on <?=data.long_stop_date ?> at <?=data.completion_venue ?> or at such other time and place as the Parties may agree in writing.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="subscription_completion">Subscription Completion matters.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para xname="subscription_completion_delivery">At completion, the Company shall deliver to the Investors</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_4_para>the duly executed Shareholders' Agreement;</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_4_para>documentary confirmation that the share capital of the Company shall comprise <?=digitCommas_(activeRound.by_security_type["Ordinary Shares"].TOTAL) ?> Ordinary Shares (including an option pool of <?=data.not_issued ?> Ordinary Shares which may or may not have been issued as at the Completion Date and <?=data.jfdi_share ?> Ordinary Shares issued to JFDI) and <?=digitCommas_(activeRound.by_security_type["Convertible Preference Shares"].TOTAL) ?> Seed Preference Shares;</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_4_para>a copy of the Articles of the Company reflecting the agreed terms and conditions of this Agreement and the Shareholder Agreement; and</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_4_para>the share certificates in respect of the Seed Preference Shares.</numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_3_para xname="designated_bank_account">At completion, the Investors shall, upon delivery of the above documents specified in Clause <xref to="subscription_completion_delivery" /> to the Investors, pay to the Company the aggregate subscription price of <?=data.capTable.getActiveRound("TOTAL") ?> by way of a bank transfer to the Designated Bank Account details as follows:</numbered_3_para>
    <indented_3_para><?= data.company.bank_details ?></indented_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="new_date_for_completion">New date for completion. If any of the provisions of this Clause <xref to="completion"/> are not complied with on the date for completion set by this Clause, the Parties may, by mutual agreement, fix a new date for completion.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>WARRANTIES AND REPRESENTATIONS</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="warranties_as_to_title_seed_preference_shares">Warranties as to title – Seed Preference Shares. The Company represents, warrants and undertakes to and with each of the Investors and its successors in title and assigns (with the intent that the provisions of this Clause shall continue to have full force and effect notwithstanding completion) that:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>the Seed Preference Shares will, when issued, be free and clear of all claims and encumbrances and will entitle the Investors to all rights, benefits and entitlements attaching thereto as at the Completion Date; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the Seed Preference Shares will comprise <!-- where does this percentage come from? --> of the resultant enlarged issued and paid up capital of the Company.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="warranties_as_to_the_company">Warranties as to the Company. The Company represents, warrants and undertakes to and with each of the Investors and its successors in title and assigns (with the intent that the provisions of this Clause shall continue to have full force and effect notwithstanding completion) in relation to the Company in the terms set out in <xref to="warranties" />. The said representations, warranties and undertakings shall be separate and independent and, save as expressly otherwise provided, shall not be limited by reference to any other paragraphs of <xref to="warranties" /> or by anything in this Agreement.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="warranties_as_to_status">Warranties as to Status. The Company represents, warrants and undertakes to and with each of the Investors and its successors in title and assigns that:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>it has the power to enter into, exercise its rights and perform and comply with its obligations under this Agreement;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all actions, conditions and things required to be taken, fulfilled and done (including, without limitation, the obtaining of any necessary consents or licence or the making of any filing or registration) (a) in order to enable it lawfully to enter into, exercise its rights and perform and comply with its obligations under this Agreement and to ensure that those obligations are legally binding and enforceable and (b) for the allotment and issue of the Seed Preference Shares, have been taken, fulfilled and done, or (in the event that the same cannot, due to no act or omission on the part of the Company, be taken, fulfilled andor done at the date hereof) will be taken fulfilled and done as soon as possible;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>its entry into, exercise of its rights and or performance of or compliance with its obligations under this Agreement do not and will not violate, or exceed any power or restriction granted or imposed by (a) any law, regulation, authorisation, directive or order (whether or not having the force of law) to which it is subject, (b) its constitutive documents, where applicable or (c) any agreement to which it is a party or which is binding on it or its assets;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>its obligations under this Agreement are valid, binding and enforceable in accordance with their terms;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>there are no outstanding warrants or options issued by the Company; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the copies of the Unaudited Accounts delivered to each of the Investors are true copies.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="warranties_founding_shareholders">Warranties – Founding Shareholders. Each of the Founding Shareholders hereby jointly and severally represent, warrant and undertake to and with each of the Investors and its successors in title and assigns that:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>he has the power to enter into, exercise its rights and perform and comply with his obligations under this Agreement;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all actions, conditions and things required to be taken, fulfilled and done (including, without limitation, the obtaining of any necessary consents or licence or the making of any filing or registration) (a) in order to enable him lawfully to enter into, exercise his rights and perform and comply with its obligations under this Agreement, and to ensure that those obligations are legally binding and enforceable and (b) for the transfer of the Sale Shares, have been taken, fulfilled and done; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>his entry into, exercise of his rights and or performance of or compliance with his obligations under this Agreement do not and will not violate, or exceed any power or restriction granted or imposed by (a) any law, regulation, authorisation, directive or order (whether or not having the force of law) to which he is subject, or (b) any agreement to which he may be a party or which may be binding on him or his assets;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>they are the legal and beneficial owners of the Equity Shares; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>there are no outstanding claims or liabilities owed by each of the Founding Shareholders to the Company.</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_2_firstbold xname="at_completion">At Completion. The Company represents, warrants and undertakes to and with each of the Investors and its successors in title and assigns that:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>all representations, warranties and undertakings herein contained will be fulfilled down to and will be true and correct at the Completion Date in all material respects as if they had been entered into afresh at such date; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>if, after the signing hereof and before the Completion Date, any event shall occur which results or may result in any of the said representations, warranties or undertakings being unfulfilled, untrue or incorrect in any material respects at completion, the Company shall immediately notify each of the Investors of the same.</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_2_firstbold xname="indemnity">Indemnity. The Company hereby agrees and undertakes to indemnify and keep indemnified and hold harmless each of the Investors and the Investor Directors from and against all losses, liabilities, obligations, damages, judgments, deficiencies, claims, demands, suits, proceedings, arbitrations, assessments, costs and expenses (including, without limitation, expenses of investigation and enforcement of this indemnity and attorneys' fees and expenses on a full indemnity basis), suffered or paid by any of the Investors directly or indirectly, including through application of the assets of the Investors, as a result of or arising out of the Company or Founding Shareholders wilful misconduct or gross negligence.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="communications">Communications. All notices, demands or other communications required or permitted to be given or made hereunder shall be in writing and delivered personally or sent by prepaid registered post or by email sent to the email address set in <xref to="communications_details" />, provided always that the Parties acknowledge that any notice, demand or communication for which there is a procedure prescribed under any applicable law or regulation shall be delivered in accordance with such law or regulation. Any notice, demand or communication delivered in accordance with this Clause <xref to="communications"/> shall be deemed to have been duly served:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of delivery by hand, when delivered;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of electronic mail, only when actually received in readable form, within 4 hours of sending, provided that the sender does not receive a transmission failure report and any electronic communication which becomes effective, in accordance with the foregoing, after 5pm in the place of receipt shall be deemed only to become effective on the following day; or</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of registered post (if despatched to an address within the country of the sender) 5 days or (if despatched by registered air-letter to an address outside the country of the sender) 10 days after posting, and in proving the same it shall be sufficient to show that the envelope containing the same was duly addressed, stamped and posted.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="confidentiality">Confidentiality. Each of the Parties agrees as follows:-</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>to keep strictly secret and confidential, and under no circumstances to disclose to any person or entity which is not a party hereto, any information regarding the terms of this Agreement unless disclosure of such information is expressly permitted by the prior written consent in writing of the other Parties; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>that all communications between the Parties or any of them and all information and other material supplied to or received by any of them from the others which is either marked "confidential" or is by its nature intended to be exclusively for the knowledge of the recipient alone and any information concerning the business transactions or the financial arrangements of the Parties or of any person with whom any of them is in a confidential relationship with regard to the matter in question coming to the knowledge of the recipient shall be kept confidential by the recipient;</numbered_3_para>
    <para_1>unless or until compelled to disclose by judicial or administrative procedures or in the opinion of its counsel, by other requirements of law, or the recipient can reasonably demonstrate that it is or part of it is, in the public domain, whereupon, to the extent that it is public, this obligation shall cease.</para_1>
    <para_1>The obligations contained in this Clause <xref to="confidentiality" /> shall endure, even after the termination of this Agreement, without limit in point of time except to the extent that and until any confidential information enters the public domain as set out above.</para_1>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="release_and_indulgence">Release and Indulgence. Any liability to any Party may in whole or in part be released, compounded or compromised or time or indulgence given by that Party in that Party's absolute discretion as regards any other Party under such liability without in any way prejudicing or affecting the first Party's rights against any other Party or Parties under the same or a like liability whether joint and several or otherwise..</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="remedies">Remedies. No remedy conferred by any of the provisions of this Agreement is intended to be exclusive of any other remedy which is otherwise available at law, in equity, by statute or otherwise, and each and every other remedy shall be cumulative and shall be in addition to every other remedy given hereunder or now or hereafter existing at law, in equity, by statute or otherwise. The election of any one or more of such remedies by any of the Parties shall not constitute a waiver by such Party of the right to pursue any other available remedies.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>Any time, date or period mentioned in any provision of this Agreement may be extended by mutual agreement between the Parties but as regards any time, date or period originally fixed and not extended or any time, date or period so extended as aforesaid, time shall be of the essence.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>Entire Agreement. This Agreement and the documents referred to herein are in substitution for all previous agreements between all or any of the Parties and contain the whole agreement between the Parties relating to the subject matter of this Agreement.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="amendments">Amendments. No amendment or variation of this Agreement shall be effective unless in writing and signed by or on behalf of each of the Parties.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="severance">Severance. If any provision of this Agreement or part thereof is rendered void, illegal or unenforceable by any legislation to which it is subject, it shall be rendered void, illegal or unenforceable to that extent and no further.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="costs_and_expenses">Costs and Expenses. All costs and expenses incurred in the preparation, negotiation and execution of this Agreement and related documents shall (whether or not there is completion), be borne by the Company up to a maximum of S$10,000.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="assignment">Assignment. The rights and obligations under this Agreement may not be assigned by any Party without the consent in writing of all the other Parties.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="further_assurance">Further Assurance. The Parties shall do all such acts and things and execute and sign all such documents and instruments as may be necessary, desirable or expedient to give effect to the terms of, and the commercial understanding of the Parties recorded in, this Agreement and the documents in connection herewith.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="counterparts">Counterparts. This Agreement may be executed in two or more counterparts, all of which together shall constitute one and the same instrument. Any Party may enter into this Agreement by signing any such counterpart and each counterpart may be signed and executed by the Parties and transmitted by facsimile and shall be as valid and effectual as if executed as an original. For the avoidance of doubt, in the case of execution by way of counterparts, this Agreement shall not be deemed to be concluded until the last of such counterparts shall have been executed.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="governing_law">Governing Law. This Agreement (and any dispute, controversy, proceedings or claim of whatever nature arising out of this Agreement or its formation) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore and the Parties irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Republic of Singapore.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="dispute_resolution">Dispute Resolution.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>Notwithstanding any provisions to the contrary in this Agreement, in the event of any dispute or difference arising out of or in connection with this Agreement (including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination) whether during the continuance of this Agreement or at any time after the termination hereof, the Parties shall first attempt to resolve the same by negotiation in good faith or through mediation at the Singapore Mediation Centre ("SMC") between the appointed representatives of the respective Parties.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>In the event that the dispute or difference shall remain unresolved within thirty (30) days upon conclusion of such negotiation or mediation, any Party shall be entitled to refer the dispute to arbitration in Singapore in accordance with the Law Society of Singapore Arbitration Scheme ("LSAS") following the LawSoc Arbitration Rules 2011 for the time being in force, which rules are deemed to be incorporated by reference to this Clause. The arbitral tribunal shall consist of one (1) sole arbitrator, unless the Parties unanimously agree otherwise, to be appointed by the President of the Law Society of Singapore, under the LawSoc Arbitration Rules 2011. The Seat and Venue of the arbitration shall be in the Republic of Singapore, and the language of the arbitration shall be in English. Any award made hereunder shall be final and binding upon the Parties and judgment on such award may be entered in any court or tribunal having jurisdiction thereof.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>Pending the resolution or final determination of the dispute or difference pursuant this Clause <xref to="dispute_resolution" />, the Parties shall procure that the Company shall, as far as practicable, continue to carry on its day-to-day business, having regard to the dispute or difference.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>Notwithstanding the foregoing, each of the Parties reserves its right to immediately commence any interim Court action such as an injunction against any of the other Parties to enforce the terms of this Agreement in a forum of its choice.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>This Clause <xref to="dispute_resolution" /> shall survive the termination of this Agreement for any reason whatsoever.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="rights_of_third_parties">Applicability of the Contracts (Rights Of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore. The Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore shall not under any circumstances apply to this Agreement and any person who is not a party to this Agreement (whether or not such person shall be named, referred to, or otherwise identified, or form part of a class of persons so named, referred to or identified, in this Agreement) shall have no right whatsoever under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore to enforce this Agreement or any of its terms.</numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold xname="waiver_of_immunity">Waiver of Immunity. All the Parties waive generally all immunity they or their respective assets or revenues may otherwise have in any jurisdiction, including immunity in respect of (a) the giving of any relief by way of injunction or order for specific performance or for the recovery of assets or revenues; and (b) the issue of any process against their respective assets or revenues for the enforcement of a judgment or, in an action in rem, for the arrest, detention or sale of any of their respective assets and revenues.</numbered_2_firstbold>

    <schedule_header xname="warranties">Warranties</schedule_header>

    <a_left_sidehead restart="true">Definitions</a_left_sidehead>
    <para_1>For the purposes of this Schedule <xref to="warranties"/> , the following definitions shall apply:-</para_1>
    <definition_nonum>Intellectual Property Rights	means any trademark, pending trademark application, patent, pending patent application, know-how, registered and unregistered design, copyright, trade secrets, licences relating to any of the above or other similar industrial or commercial right;</definition_nonum>

    <a_left_sidehead>Information</a_left_sidehead>
    <para_2>The Recitals are true and all information which has been given by or on behalf of the Company to any of the directors or officials or professional advisers of the Investors in the course of the negotiations leading to this Agreement was when given true, complete and accurate in all respects and after making due and careful enquiries the Company is not aware of any fact or matter not disclosed in writing to the Investors which renders any such information untrue, inaccurate or misleading or the disclosure of which might reasonably affect the willingness of any of the Investors to invest in the Company on the terms of this Agreement or the price at or terms upon which the Investors would be willing to so invest.</para_2>

    <a_left_sidehead xname="accounts">Accounts</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>The unaudited accounts of the Company have been prepared in accordance with the law and on a consistent basis in accordance with accounting principles, standards and practices generally accepted at the date hereof in Singapore so as to give a true and fair view of the state of affairs of the Company at the date of the relevant unaudited accounts and of the profits or losses for the period concerned and as at that date make:-</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>full provision for all actual liabilities;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>proper provision (or note in accordance with good accountancy practice) for all contingent liabilities;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>provision reasonably regarded as adequate for all bad and doubtful debts; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>due provision for depreciation and amortisation and for any obsolescence of assets.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company does not have outstanding any loan capital, nor has factored any of its debts, or engaged in financing of a type which would not require to be shown or reflected in its unaudited accounts or borrowed any money which it has not repaid.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>There are no liabilities (including contingent liabilities) which are outstanding on the part of the Company, other than those liabilities disclosed in the unaudited accounts or which have arisen in the ordinary course of business since the date to which such accounts were prepared. For the avoidance of doubt, no liabilities are owed to the Founding Shareholders.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Changes Since Balance Sheet Date</a_left_sidehead>
    <para_1>Since the Balance Sheet Date as regards the Company:-</para_1>
    <numbered_2_para>its business has been carried on in the ordinary course and so as to maintain the same as a going concern;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>it has not disposed of any assets or assumed or incurred any material liabilities (including contingent liabilities) otherwise than in the ordinary course of carrying on its business;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>its business has not been materially and adversely affected by the loss of any important customer or source of supply or by any abnormal factor not affecting similar businesses to a like extent and the Company, after making due and careful enquiries, is not aware of any facts which are likely to give rise to any such effects;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>no dividend or other distribution has been declared, made or paid to its members except as provided for in the unaudited accounts;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>its turnover has not materially deteriorated;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>no change has been made in the basis of the emoluments or other terms of employment of its Directors or any of its employees who on the Balance Sheet Date were in receipt of remuneration at a rate in excess of S$60,000 per annum;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>it has not borrowed any money (other than as disclosed in the unaudited accounts);</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>no share or loan capital has been allotted or issued or agreed to be issued;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>it has not entered into any unusual, long term or onerous commitments or contracts;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>there has been no material adverse change in its financial position or turnover and no event, fact or matter has occurred or is likely to occur which will or is likely to give rise to any such change;</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>after making due and careful enquiries it has not learnt of any circumstance making bad or doubtful any of its book debts; and</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>there has been no material adverse change in its financial position or prospects.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Litigation</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>Since the Balance Sheet Date no claim sounding in damages has been made against the Company.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company is not at present engaged whether as plaintiff or defendant or otherwise in any legal action, proceeding or arbitration or being prosecuted for any criminal offence.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>There are no circumstances known to the Company likely to lead to any such claim or legal action, proceeding or arbitration ( other than as aforesaid) or prosecution.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has not committed any criminal, illegal or other unlawful act or any breach of statutory duty or any tortious or other act or default which could lead to a claim or proceedings against the Company or give rise to or increase the liability or obligation of the Company or which could entitle any other person to terminate any contract to which the Company is a party.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>There are no investigations, inqurnes or disciplinary proceedings by or before any regulatory, administrative, supervisory or government body concerning the Company, whether on-going, pending or threatened and there are no facts likely to give rise to any such investigation, inquiry or proceedings.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Taxation</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>There is no liability to Taxation in respect of which a Claim could be made and there are no circumstances likely to give rise to such a liability.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>All profits tax, interest tax, salaries tax and property tax, stamp duties, and other charges and levies assessed or imposed by any government or governmental or statutory body which have been assessed upon the Company and which are due and payable on or before completion have been paid.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>In relation to stamp duty assessable or payable in Singapore or elsewhere in the world, as at the date of this Agreement and as at completion, all documents in the enforcement of which the Company may be interested has been duly stamped and no document belonging to the Company now or at completion which is subject to ad valorem stamp duty is or will be unstamped or insufficiently stamped; nor has any relief from such duty been improperly obtained, nor has any event occurred as a result of which any such duty from which the Company has obtained relief, has become payable; and all stamp duty payable upon any transfer of shares in the Company before Completion has been duly paid.</numbered_2_para>

    <numbered_2_para>In relation to goods and services tax and/or value-added or other similar tax, the Company:-</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>has been duly registered and is a taxable person;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>has complied, in all material respects, with all statutory requirements, orders, provisions, directions or conditions;</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>maintains complete, correct and up to date records as is required by the applicable legislation; and</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>has not been required by the relevant authorities of customs and excise to give security.</numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has not paid or, since the Balance Sheet Date, become liable to pay any penalty or interest under any Taxation statute.</numbered_2_para>

    <numbered_2_para>The Company has not been the subject of an investigation, discovery or access order by or involving any Taxation authority and there are no circumstances existing which make it likely that an investigation, discovery or order will be made.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has duly made all returns and given or delivered all notices, accounts and information which on or before the date hereof ought to have been made, given or delivered for the purposes of Taxation and all such returns, notices, accounts and information have to the best knowledge and belief of the Company, after making due and careful enquiries, been correct and made on a proper basis and none of such returns, notices, accounts or information is disputed in any material respect by the fiscal authority concerned and there is no fact known to the Company, after making due and careful enquiries, which might be the occasion of any such dispute or of any Claim for Taxation in respect of any financial period down to and including the Balance Sheet Date not provided for in its unaudited accounts.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Book Debts</a_left_sidehead>
    <para_1>Save as disclosed in the unaudited accounts, none of the book debts which are included in the unaudited accounts or which have subsequently arisen have been outstanding for more than six months from their due dates for payment and all such debts have realised or will realise in the normal course of collection their full value as included in the unaudited accounts after taking into account the provision for bad and doubtful debts made in the unaudited accounts.</para_1>

    <a_left_sidehead>Intellectual Property Rights</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>All Intellectual Property Rights used or required by the Company in connection with its business (including, without limitation, all and any products manufactured, assembled and/or sold or leased or rented by it) are in full force and effect and are vested in and beneficially owned by it.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has copyright in all drawings and design right in all designs relating to its business and all such drawings and designs are in its possession and it has not supplied copies of any such drawings or designs to any other person.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company does not require any patent, trade or service mark, registered design, copyright, design right, licence or other right of any other person in order to manufacture or sell or lease its products or to use the processes employed in its business as presently carried on and none of the activities of the Company infringes any patent or other intellectual property of any kind whatsoever of any other person or gives rise to an obligation to pay any sum in the nature of a royalty.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>No right or licence has been granted to any person by the Company to use in any manner or to do anything which would or might otherwise infringe any of the Intellectual Property Rights; and no act has been done or omission permitted by the Company whereby such Intellectual Property Rights or any of them have ceased or might cease to be valid and enforceable.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The business of the Company as now carried on does not and is not likely to infringe any Intellectual Property Right of any other person (or would not do so if the same were valid) or give rise to a liability pursuant to the laws relating to Intellectual Property Rights and all licences to the Company in respect of any such rights are in full force and effect.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Statutory and Other Requirements, Consents and Licences</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has carried on its business in accordance with applicable laws, regulations and bylaws (including as to the obtaining and maintaining of the requisite licences and permits) in Singapore, each country in which it conducts business and in any other relevant country or jurisdiction, and there is no investigation or enquiry by, or order, decree or judgment of, any court or any governmental agency or regulatory body outstanding or anticipated against the Company or which may have a material adverse effect upon its assets or business.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>All statutory and other requirements applicable to the carrying on of the business of the Company as now carried on (including as to the obtaining and maintaining of the requisite licences and permits), and all conditions applicable to any licences and consents involved in the carrying on of such business, have been complied with and the Company is not aware of any breach thereof or of any intended or contemplated refusal or revocation of any such licence or consent.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>No such requirements, consents and licences have been obtained or granted subject to unusual or onerous conditions and there are no circumstances which indicate that any of such requirements, consents or licences may be revoked or not reserved, in whole or in part, in the ordinary course of events.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Books</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>The statutory records and statutory books of the Company are duly entered up and maintained in accordance with all legal requirements applicable thereto and contain true, full and accurate records of all matters required to be dealt with therein and all such books and all records and documents (including documents of title) which are its property, in its possession or under its control and all accounts, documents and returns required to be delivered for registration or made to the Accounting and Corporate Regulatory Authority of Singapore in Singapore, or the equivalent or corresponding governmental / regulatory institution in any relevant country (including the relevant country of incorporation) have been duly and correctly delivered or made.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>All charges in favour of the Company have (if appropriate) been registered in accordance with the provisions of the Companies Act of Singapore or any relevant act or regulation.</numbered_2_para>

    <a_left_sidehead>Insolvency</a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>No order has been made or petition presented or resolution passed for the winding-up or administration of the Company, nor are there any grounds on which any person would be entitled to have the Company wound-up or placed in administration or judicial management, nor has any person threatened to present such a petition or convened or threatened to convene a meeting of the Company to consider a resolution to wind up the Company or any other resolutions, nor has any step been taken in relation to the Company under the law relating to insolvency or the relief of debtors in any part of the world.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>No distress, execution or other process has been levied on any asset owned or used by the Company, nor has any person threatened any such distress, execution or other process.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>No person has appointed or threatened to appoint or become entitled to appoint a receiver or receiver and manager or other similar officer of the Company's business or assets or any part of them.</numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company has not ceased trading or stopped payment to its creditors generally and there are no grounds on which the Company could be reasonably found to be unable to pay its debts.</numbered_2_para>
    <!-- table of other investors -->

    <schedule_header xname="communications_details">Communications</schedule_header>
    <?!= include("inc_enumerate_signatures", data, {rcpts_to:rcpts_to, _include2: { term: { new_investor: "purchaser" } } } ) ?>

	<chapter_header restart="true" xname="unaudited_accounts">Appendix: Unaudited Accounts</chapter_header>
	
  </Story_Main>
</Root>
