<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>

<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/">
  <CoverTop>
  </CoverTop>
  <CoverMid>
  </CoverMid>
  <CoverMid>
  </CoverMid>
  <CoverBottom_Logotype>
  </CoverBottom_Logotype>
  <CoverBottom_Address>
  </CoverBottom_Address>
  <CoverBottom_series>
  </CoverBottom_series>
  <Firstpage_Sidebar delete_if_empty="true">
  </Firstpage_Sidebar>
  <Story_Main>
    <p>Dated this 8th of December 2014 </p>
    <p>parties </p>
    <p>PARTIES NAMED AND DESCRIBED IN SCHEDULE 2, being the investors of the Company (the "Other Investors"); </p>
    <p>(collectively, Investor_X, Investor_Y and the Other Investors shall be known as the "Investors") </p>
    <p>AND </p>
    <p>Company </p>
    <p>(collectively the "Parties" and each a "Party"). </p>
    <p>WHEREAS: </p>
    <recitals>The Company is an real estate brokering software services provider (the "Business") </recitals>
    <recitals>The Company and the Founding Shareholders have requested the Investors to invest for __N__ Seed preference shares in the Company (the "Preference Shares") and the Investors have agreed to so invest in the Company, on the terms and subject to the conditions set out in an Investment Agreement dated 8 December 2014 (the "Investment Agreement"). </recitals>
    <recitals>This Agreement sets out the terms and conditions whereunder the parties have agreed to regulate their rights and obligations in relation to, and the affairs of, the Company. </recitals>
    <para_1>IT IS HEREBY AGREED as follows:- </para_1>
    <a_left_sidehead>DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION </a_left_sidehead>
    <p>In this Agreement, unless the subject or context otherwise requires:--- </p>
    <numbered_2_para>the following words and expressions shall have the following meanings:- </numbered_2_para>
    <definition_nonum>Act	means the Companies Act (Cap. 50); </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Affiliate	means any party which controls, is controlled by or under the common control of that person, whether directly or indirectly, and "controls" means the ownership of 51% or more of the voting or other controlling interests in the subject person and/or ability to control in fact the business and affairs of that person; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Agreed Proportion	means, in relation to any Shareholder, the proportion as is equal to the proportion in which the number of Shares registered in the name of such Shareholder at any given time bears to the total number of issued Shares at the same given time; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Articles	means the memorandum and articles of association of the Company; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Board	means the board of Directors of the Company; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Business	has the meaning set out in Recital (A); </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Business Day	means a day other than a Saturday, Sunday or a gazetted public holiday in Singapore; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Business Plan	means the business plan to be presented annually by the Company which will include details of the Company's operations, financials, capital expenditure, new geographies, additional product lines and other relevant targets for the Company. For the avoidance of doubt, the first Business Plan shall be delivered to the Investors before Completion; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Completion	means the completion of the subscription for the Preference Shares by the Investors; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Dispose	means, with respect to any Shares, to sell, assign, transfer, pledge, hypothecate or otherwise encumber or dispose of, or to permit the sale, assignment, transfer, pledge, hypothecation, encumbrance or disposal by any other person, and "Disposal" shall be construed in a similar way; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Deadlock Matter	has the meaning set out in Clause 5.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Deadlock Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 5.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Deemed Offer	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Default Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Directors	means the directors for the time being of the Company; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Directors and the sign "S$"	mean the lawful currency of Singapore; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Drag-along Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 9.5; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Drag-along Sale	has the meaning set out in Clause 9.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>encumber	means, with respect to any Shares, the creation of any security interest, charge, mortgage, pledge, lien or other encumbrance affecting title to, ownership of or possession of such Shares, and the terms "
      <b>encumbering</b>" and "
      <b>encumbrance</b>" shall be construed in a similar way; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Expiry Date	has the meaning set out in Clause 7.3; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Founder Directors	has the meaning set out in Clause 3.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Independent Director	has the meaning set out in Clause 3.1.4; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Investor Director	has the meaning set out in Clause 3.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Initiating Shareholders	means Shareholders representing 70% or more of the Ordinary Shares and Preference Shares for the time being, with all Shareholders voting on an as-converted basis; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Investment Agreement	has the meaning set out in Recital (B); </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Investment Amount	means, for each Investor, the amount invested by that Investor for its Preference Shares; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Issuance Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 7.3; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Key Management	refers to employees of the Company who has the authority to directly or indirectly plan and control business operations of the Company; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Non-Defaulting Shareholders	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Ordinary Shares	means the ordinary shares issued and allotted by the Company from time to time pursuant to the Articles; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Preference Shares	has the meaning set out in Recital (B); </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Relevant Business	has the meaning set out in Clause 6.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Restructuring Event	means: </definition_nonum>
    <definition_list_bullets>a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of the Company; or </definition_list_bullets>
    <definition_list_bullets>a merger, amalgamation and/or consolidation of the Company, other than (i) a consolidation with a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company or (ii) a merger effected to change the domicile of the Company; </definition_list_bullets>
    <definition_nonum>Tag-along Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 10.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Tag-along Offer	has the meaning set out in Clause 10.3; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Tag-along Shares	has the meaning set out in Clause 10.2.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Terminated Shareholder	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Termination Allocation Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.3; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Termination Non-Allocation Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.4; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Termination Transfer Price	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Termination Transfer Shares	has the meaning set out in Clause 12.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transfer Notice	has the meaning set out in Clause 8.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transfer Price	has the meaning set out in Clause 8.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transfer Shares	has the meaning set out in Clause 8.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transferor	has the meaning set out in Clause 8.2; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Transferring Founding Shareholder	has the meaning set out in Clause 10.1; </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Valuer	has the meaning set out in Clause 13.1; and </definition_nonum>
    <definition_nonum>Vesting Period	means a period of two years period from the date of Completion. </definition_nonum>
    <numbered_2_para>any reference to a statutory provision shall include such provision and any regulations made in pursuance thereof as from time to time modified or re-enacted whether before or after the date of this Agreement so far as such modification or re-enactment applies or is capable of applying to any transactions entered into prior to completion and (so far as liability thereunder may exist or can arise) shall include also any past statutory provisions or regulations (as from time to time modified or re-enacted) which such provisions or regulations have directly or indirectly replaced; </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>any reference to "
      <b>accounts</b>" shall non-exclusively include cashflow statements, the Directors' and auditors' reports, relevant balance sheets and profit and loss accounts and related notes together with all documents which are or would be required by law to be annexed to the accounts of the Company concerned to be laid before the Company in general meeting for the accounting reference period in question; </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>references to "
      <b>Recitals</b>", "
      <b>Clauses</b>" and "
      <b>Schedules</b>" are to recitals, clauses and schedules of this Agreement and references to this "Agreement" and the Schedules shall mean this Agreement; </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>the headings in this Agreement are for convenience only and shall not affect the interpretation hereof; </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>unless the context otherwise requires, references to the singular number shall include references to the plural number and vice versa, references to natural persons shall include bodies corporate, and the use of any gender shall include all genders; and </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>terms defined in the Investment Agreement and not otherwise defined in this Agreement shall have the same meaning in this Agreement, unless the context otherwise requires. </numbered_2_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>CONDITIONAL AGREEMENT </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>The obligations of the parties under this Agreement shall be conditional upon the completion of the subscription for the Preference Shares being effected in accordance with the terms of the Investment Agreement. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Shareholding. </b>The Parties agree that, subject to any adjustments in the event of any admission of new Shareholders or otherwise pursuant to mutual agreement by the Parties, the Agreed Proportion of each Shareholder shall be as set out against its name below:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <p>(surely we should move this to a schedule) </p>
    <p>NAME OF SHAREHOLDER </p>
    <p>NO. OF ORDINARY SHARES HELD </p>
    <p>NO. OF PREFERENCE SHARES HELD </p>
    <p>PERCENTAGE SHAREHOLDING </p>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Founding Shareholders Share. </b>Unless otherwise approved by the Board, including the Directors to be appointed by the Investors, the Founding Shareholders shall each be granted __N__ Shares to be vested in accordance with the vesting schedule set out in Schedule 3 over the Vesting Period. The Founding Shareholders shall not Dispose of any unvested Shares during the Vesting Period, except with the prior approval of the Investor. Any unvested Shares after the Vesting Period shall be void. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Acceleration of Vesting. </b>Unless otherwise approved by the Board, including the Directors appointed by the Investors, the vesting of the Ordinary Shares stipulated in Clause 2.3 above shall be accelerated if (i) if a Founding Shareholder is terminated for any reason other than for cause, or (ii) in event of a Restructuring Event. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>MANAGEMENT OF THE COMPANY </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>Constitution of the Board: Each of the Parties agrees that the Board shall at all times consist of a maximum of five Directors comprising: </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>two Directors appointed by the Founding Shareholders (the "Founder Directors"); </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>one Director appointed by Investor_X. (the "Investor_X Director"); </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>one Director appointed by Clickstream Ventures Pte. Ltd. (the "Investor_Y Director"); </numbered_3_para>
    <indented_3_para>(the Investor_X Director and Investor_Y Director collectively known as the "Investor Directors"), and </indented_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>one Director (who shall be an independent party) appointed by the mutual agreement of the Founding Shareholders, Investor_X and Investor_Y (the "Independent Director"). </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Removal of Directors. </b>The right of the Shareholders to appoint Director(s) under Clause 3.1 shall include the right to remove such Director(s) from office at any time, and the right to determine from time to time the period which such persons shall hold office as Director. For the avoidance of doubt, the removal of the Independent Director shall require the approval of the Founding Shareholders, Investor_X and Investor_Y. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Appointment and removal. </b>Any appointment or removal of a Director as aforesaid shall be made in writing and be signed by or on behalf of the appointor, and shall be delivered to the registered office for the time being of the Company. Subject to Clauses 3.1 and 3.2, in order to give effect to the provisions of this Clause 3, each of the Shareholders shall exercise all its voting rights for the time being in the Company to give effect to the provisions of this Clause 3. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Alternate Director. </b>A Director shall be entitled at any time and from time to time to appoint any person to act as his alternate and to terminate the appointment of such person and in that connection the provisions of the Articles shall be complied with. Such alternate director shall be entitled while holding office as such to receive notices of meetings of the Board and to attend and vote as a Director at any such meetings at which the Director appointing him is not present and generally to exercise all the powers, rights, duties and authorities and to perform all functions of his appointor. Further, such alternate director shall be entitled to exercise the vote of the Director appointing him at any meetings of the Board and if such alternate director represents more than one Director, such alternate director shall be entitled to one vote for every Director he represents. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Chairman. </b>The Chairman of the Board shall be a Director appointed by an Investor. The Chairman shall have a casting vote with respect to the board resolutions. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Quorum. </b>All meetings of the Board shall be convened and conducted in accordance with the provisions of the Act and the Articles. The quorum for any meeting of the Board shall be two Directors of which at least one (1) shall be a Director appointed by the Founding Shareholders and one (1) shall be one of the Investor Directors. If a quorum is not present half an hour from the time appointed for the holding of a meeting of the Board when it is first convened, the meeting shall be adjourned to the date falling seven (7) Business Days later at the same time and place. At such adjourned meeting, if a quorum of three Directors of which at least two (2) shall be the Directors appointed by the Founding Shareholders and one (1) shall be one of the Directors appointed by an Investor is not present half an hour from the time appointed for the holding of the adjourned meeting, the meeting shall be dissolved. Notice of each adjourned meeting shall be given to all Directors. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Meetings. </b>Meetings of the Board shall be held once every calendar month or at such times as the Board shall determine. Not less than fourteen days' notice (or such shorter period of notice in respect of any particular meeting as may be agreed by the Directors) of each meeting of the Board specifying the date, place, time and the agenda of the meeting shall be given to all Directors. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Voting. </b>Subject to Clauses 3.9, 3.14 and 4, all resolutions of the Board shall be decided by a simple majority of votes of all the Directors (and not just those present at the meeting), notwithstanding that the quorum is satisfied. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Resolutions in writing. </b>Subject to Clause 3.14, a resolution in writing circulated to all the Directors for the time being and signed or approved by a majority of the Board which must include a Founder Director and a Investor Director, shall be as valid and effectual as if it had been passed at a meeting of the Directors duly convened and held. Any such resolution may consist of several documents in like form, each signed by one or more Directors. For the avoidance of doubt, scanned copies of such resolutions in writing shall be accepted as valid for the purposes of this Clause 3.9. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Conference. </b>The Directors may participate in a meeting of the Directors by means of a conference telephone or similar communications equipment by means of which all persons participating in the meeting can hear one another, without a Director being in the physical presence of another Director or Directors, and participation in a meeting pursuant to this Clause shall constitute presence in person at such meeting. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Operations. </b>Subject to Clause 4, the Board shall be responsible for the management and the day-to-day functions of the Company. The Board shall determine the general policies of the Company, including, but not limited to, to the scope of their activities and operations. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Investor Directors' Obligations. </b>Investor_X and Investor_Y (the "Lead Investors") hereby irrevocably agree that the Investor Directors are the nominees of the respective Lead Investors appointing them and accordingly, such Investor Directors shall be entitled to report all matters concerning the Company, including, but not limited to, matters discussed at any board meeting, to the respective Lead Investors and that the Investor Directors may take advice and obtain instructions from the respective Lead Investors. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Expenses. </b>All reasonable fees and expenses incurred by the Directors in connection with their attendance at Board meetings and in connection with the carrying out of their duties and obligations as Directors shall be borne by the Company in accordance with the policies on the reimbursement, payment or otherwise of such fees and expenses for the time being of the Company. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Actions requiring approval of the Investor Directors. </b>Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement and/or in the Articles, each of the Parties agrees and shall procure that the Company shall not, without the prior written consent of the Investor Directors, undertake any of the following actions:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>amend the Articles of the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>amend the remuneration of any member of the Key Management; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>make any distribution of profits amongst the Shareholders by way of dividend, capitalisation of reserves or otherwise (whether in cash or specie); </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>materially change the nature and/or scope of the Business of the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>approval of the Business Plan; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>consummate transactions that materially deviate from the scope of the Business Plan, enter into any contract, agreement or arrangement, or undertake any other action or decision which materially deviates from the scope of the Business Plan </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>provide any security/guarantee in favour of a third party; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>participation, investment or subscription of shares in, or transfer of assets to, any joint venture, consortium, Company, or other body corporate or the establishment and/or incorporation of any new subsidiary or Affiliate of the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>undertake any merger, consolidation, reorganisation or acquisition, or the sale, lease or disposal of all or substantially all of the Company's assets; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>borrow or raise an amount higher than what was agreed within the Business Plan and the creation of any mortgage, pledge or lien over any assets of the Company in respect of such a borrowing; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>increase the issued share capital (convertible or otherwise), issue or grant any option over the unissued share capital, issue a new class of shares in the share capital, or undertake the public listing and quotation of the shares on any stock exchange; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>any business transaction and/or business relationship which is not carried out on an arms length basis; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>undertake liquidation, dissolution, winding up or such other equivalent exercise with respect to the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>appointment and/or removal of auditors, bankers and/or corporate advisors of the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>amend the name or trading name of the Company; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>except as set out in the annual budget, incur any indebtedness of S$20,000 or more in aggregate other than orders made to suppliers in the ordinary course of business. This amount shall be subject to review on a quarterly basis by the Founding Shareholders and shall be amended in line with the profitability of the Business; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>dispose of assets of value above S$20,000 or incur expenses above S$20,000, except as set out in the annual budget, in relation to purchase orders fulfilled to customers or in orders made to suppliers in the ordinary course of business. This amount shall be subject to review on a quarterly basis by the Founding Shareholders and shall be amended in line with the profitability of the Business; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>acquire any freehold or leasehold interest in property, enter into any franchise arrangement or enter into any arrangements where debt of the Company is transferred to a third party in a commercial transaction; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>pass any special resolutions as required under the Act. </numbered_3_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>SHAREHOLDER'S MATTERS </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Notice. </b>Subject to the prov1s1ons of the Act as to special resolutions, special notice and agreement for shorter notice, and to the provisions of the Articles, a general meeting of the Company shall be called by not less than 14 days' notice in writing. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Quorum at general meeting. </b>The quorum at any general meeting shall be such Shareholders holding in aggregate at least two-thirds in number of the total issued Ordinary Shares and Preference Shares at the relevant time. If a quorum is not present half an hour from the time appointed for the holding of a general meeting when it is first convened, the meeting shall be adjourned to the same day in the week next following at the same time and place. At such adjourned meeting, if a quorum is not present half an hour from the time appointed for the holding the adjourned meeting, the meeting shall be dissolved. Notice of each adjourned meeting shall be given to all Shareholders. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Voting rights at general meeting. </b>Subject to Clauses 4.5 and 4.6, all questions arising at a general meeting of the Company shall, unless otherwise required by the Act, be decided by way of a simple majority vote of the Shareholders present and voting on a poll. Each holder of Preference Shares shall, at each general meeting, have the right to a number of votes equal to the number of Ordinary Shares that would be issued upon conversion of such Preference Shares pursuant to Clause 7. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Conference. </b>To the fullest extent permitted by law, the Shareholders may participate in a general meeting of the Company by means of a conference telephone or similar communications equipment by means of which all persons participating in the meeting can hear one another, without a Shareholder being in the physical presence of another Shareholder or Shareholders, and participation in a meeting pursuant to this Clause shall constitute presence in person at such meeting. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Resolutions in writing. </b>Subject to the provisions of the Act and compliance with all applicable laws and regulations relating to shareholders' resolutions in writing, the Company may pass any Shareholders' resolutions by written means. Within 14 days (or such longer period as the Directors may determine) after the text of the resolutions has been sent or made accessible to the Shareholders, if the requisite number of Shareholders holding a majority of the issued and paid-up Shares have given the Company their formal agreement to the resolutions in accordance with the Act or otherwise by applicable law (including by electronic copy, facsimile, cable or telex communication), then the resolution shall be as valid and effectual as if it had been passed at a general meeting of the Shareholders duly convened and held. Any such resolution may consist of several documents in like form, each signed by one or more Shareholders. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Information rights. </b>The Company shall and the Parties shall procure that the Company shall, for so long as the relevant Shareholder shall hold any Shares in the Company:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>produce and deliver to the Shareholders the annual audited accounts of the Company prepared in accordance with the generally accepted accounting principles in Singapore and in compliance with all applicable legislation, within 90 days after the end of each financial year; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>produce and deliver to the Board and the Shareholders monthly management accounts and monthly status reports (including milestone schedules, business plans, projections and forecasts) for the Company within 20 days after the end of the relevant month; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>produce and deliver to the Shareholders the annual budget and business plan of the Company for the next financial year at least 20 days prior to the commencement of such financial year; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>produce and deliver to the Board and the Shareholders such other financial information of the Company as they may reasonably require from time to time. </numbered_3_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>Deadlock </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Occurrence of Deadlock. </b>In the event that a quorum or a resolution of the Shareholders or the Directors for the transaction of any business of the Company cannot be met or passed respectively after 2 successive attempts, any Shareholder shall have the right to declare that a deadlock has occurred by issuing a notice in writing to the other Shareholders (the "Deadlock Notice"). </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Deadlock Resolution. </b>In the event that no resolution is reached after the Deadlock Notice has continued for 60 days, any Shareholder may (upon giving the other Shareholders written notice prior to such expiration) refer the subject matter of the deadlock for resolution (the "Deadlock Matter") pursuant to the dispute resolution mechanism stipulated under Clause 15.14(a), and all the Shareholders shall be obliged to use good faith endeavours to resolve the subject matter of the deadlock via mediation within 30 days of such referral. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Arbitration. </b>In the event that no resolution is reached in relation to the Deadlock Matter within 30 days of referral to the Singapore Mediation Centre, any Shareholder shall be entitled to refer the Deadlock Matter for determination by arbitration in Singapore in accordance with the dispute resolution mechanism stipulated under Clauses 15.14(b) to 15.14(e). </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_para>Notwithstanding the above, the Shareholders shall procure that the Company shall, as far as practicable, continue to carry on its day to day operations, in accordance with Clause 15.14(c). </numbered_2_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>RIGHT TO CONDUCT BUSINESS </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company and each of the Founding Shareholders hereby acknowledge that the Investors and its Affiliates has investments in various companies, some of which may be in competition (whether directly or indirectly) with the Business (the "Relevant Business"). </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company and each of the Founding Shareholders further acknowledge that the Investors and its Affiliates will not be liable for any claims based or arising out of the following: - </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the fact that the Investor is engaged or interested in the Relevant Business; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>any action carried on by any of the Investor's officers and/or representatives to assist in the Relevant Business, regardless of whether (i) such action was undertaken by the Investor's officers and/or representatives as a director of the Relevant Business and/or (ii) has a detrimental effect on the profits of the Company. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company and each of the Founding Shareholders further confirm that the Investors may continue to invest, from time to time, in any Company that is engaged in the Relevant Business or enter into agreements with persons interested in the Relevant Business. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>Each of the Investors hereby undertakes to maintain strict confidentiality in relation to matters concerning the Company. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>Each of the Founding Shareholders hereby irrevocably and unconditionally agrees with and undertakes to the other parties to this Agreement that, for so long as either of them shall hold any share in the Company and for a period of one (1) year thereafter, he will not:- </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>be employed, engaged or interested in the Relevant Business in Singapore; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>carry on for its own account, either alone or in partnership (or be concerned as a director in any Company engaged in), the Relevant Business within Singapore; and </numbered_3_para>
    <indented_3_para_upspace>Provided that while the restrictions in this Clause 6 are considered to be reasonable in all the circumstances it is agreed between the parties that if any one or more of such restrictions shall either taken by itself or themselves together be adjudged to go beyond what is reasonable in all the circumstances for the protection of the Company's and/or the Investor's legitimate interest but would be adjudged reasonable if any particular restriction or restrictions were deleted or if any part or parts of the wording thereof were deleted, restricted or limited in a particular manner then the restrictions shall apply with such deletions, restrictions or limitations, as the case may be. It is expressly further agreed by the Founding Shareholders that the covenant not to compete with the Company in the terms set out above is legitimate and has been given in consideration of the Investors agreeing, at the request of the Company, to enter into the Investment Agreement and this Agreement. </indented_3_para_upspace>
    <numbered_2_para>The Founding Shareholders shall ensure that each member of the Key Management signs an undertaking to comply with the terms of Clause 6.5 above as part of the employment contract. </numbered_2_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>ISSUANCE, CONVERSION OF SHARES AND ANTI-DILUTION </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>In the event the Company issues additional Shares at a price per share lower than the Subscription Price, the existing investment would be deemed to be consummated at such lower valuation. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company grants to each Shareholder a right of first refusal to subscribe pro-rata (as nearly as possible) for any new Shares which the Company, from time to time, proposes to allot and issue. The Company shall give each Shareholder written notice (the "Issuance Notice") describing the new type of Shares or securities, their price and the general terms upon which the Company proposes to issues such Shares or securities. A Shareholder has twenty (20) Business Days commencing on the date of the Issuance Notice to purchase such new Shares or securities at the price and upon the terms specified in the Issuance Notice by written notice to the Company stating the number of Shares or securities it wishes to purchase. If following expiry of the twenty (20) Business Days (the "Expiry Date"), any of the new Shares or securities are not purchased by the Shareholders, such balance Shares or securities shall be offered to those Shareholders who had purchased their full entitlement of such Shares or securities at the same price and terms and such Shareholders shall have the right to purchase such number of these balance Shares or securities in accordance with their respective proportionate Shareholdings to each other. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company may, for the period commencing on the date fallingforty-one (41) Business Days after the date of the Issuance Notice and ending on the date falling sixty (60) Business Days after the date of the Issuance Notice, allot any new Shares or securities not subscribed for by the Shareholders pursuant to Clause 5.1 to any person at a price and upon terms no more favourable than specified in the Issuance Notice. If the Company fails to allow or issue the new Shares or securities within the period set out in this Clause 7.4, the Company shall not thereafter allot or issue the balance new Shares or securities, without first offering such new Shares or securities to the Shareholders in the manner provided for in Clause 7.5. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Optional Conversion. </b>Each Preference Shares shall be convertible to a certain number of Ordinary Shares at any time and from time to time at the option of the Investor in its sole and absolute discretion. Subject to share dividends, splits, consolidations and any adjustments set forth in this Agreement, conversion of each Preference Share shall be based on an initial conversion rate of one (I) Preference Share to one (I) Ordinary Share. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Mandatory Conversion. </b>The Preference Shares shall automatically be converted, based on the prevailing conversion rate at that time if the following events occur:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>if the majority of the holders of Preference Shares, voting together as a class, approves the conversion; or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>if there is a successful initial public offering of the Company. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Anti-dilution. </b>In the event that the Company issues additional Shares (including but not limited to, any class of Shares, warrants, granting of any option to subscribe and/or convertible securities) for a consideration per Share which is less than the Subscription Price (as adjusted for any change in nominal value of shares), the conversion rate for the Preference Shares shall be adjusted on a full ratchet basis. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>TRANSFERS OF SHARES </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Restriction. </b>Subject to the provisions of this Clause 8, the Founding Shareholders shall not mortgage, charge or otherwise encumber all or any part of their interest in the Shares held by them (including the granting of any option) save with the prior written consent of the Investors. Without prejudice to the above, each of the Founding Shareholders and Investors shall have the first right of refusal to purchase any Shares (whether Preference, Ordinary or otherwise) proposed to be sold by any other Shareholder on the same terms on which the Founding Shareholder or Investor (as applicable) propose(s) to transfer such Shares. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Transfers. </b>Subject to Clauses 8.1, 9 and 10, any transfer of Shares shall comply with the following procedure:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Transfer Notice. </b>In the event that any Shareholder (the "Transferor") wishes to transfer any of the Shares held by it (the "Transfer Shares"), it shall by written notice (the "Transfer Notice") offer to sell to the other Shareholder(s) the Transfer Shares at a price (the "Transfer Price") stated in the Transfer Notice. </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Proportionate purchase. </b>Within thirty (30) days of the receipt of the Transfer Notice the other Shareholder(s) shall have the option to purchase at the Transfer Price and on the terms specified in the Transfer Notice, all but not part of the Transfer Shares set out in the Transfer Notice and where there is more than one purchaser: </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <numbered_4_para>the number of Transfer Shares to be purchased between the holders of Preference Shares or holders of Ordinary Shares (as the case may be) shall be in proportion (as nearly as the circumstances permit) to the number of Shares held by such purchasers inter se; and </numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_4_para>the process set out in this Clause 8.2.2 shall be repeated (as applicable) until all Transfer Shares have been taken up or there are no more purchasers. </numbered_4_para>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Delivery and transfer. </b>Upon the exercise of such option the purchaser(s) shall pay to the Transferor the Transfer Price and in exchange therefor the Transferor shall deliver and transfer to the purchaser(s) the legal and beneficial title to the Transfer Shares absolutely and free from all encumbrances and the Transferor shall duly execute and deliver all such documents and do all such things as may be necessary to effect such delivery and transfer of the Transfer Shares. </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Transfer to third party. </b>Subject to the provisions of Clause 8.2.5, if the other Shareholders fail to exercise the option referred to above in respect of all the Transfer Shares, the Transferor may within thirty (30) days of the expiry of the 30-day notice period be at liberty to sell all the Transfer Shares to any third party on terms no more favourable than those specified in the Transfer Notice. Provided Always that the Transferor shall remain and continue to be liable and be responsible for the discharge, observance and performance of all its liabilities and obligations, whether actual or contingent, arising out of or in connection with this Agreement at any time up to and including the date of the transfer of the Transfer Shares and shall remain entitled to all accrued rights and benefits arising out of or in connection with the Transfer Shares. </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Subsequent sale. </b>In the event the Transfer Shares are not sold by the Transferor to a third party within thirty (30) days of the expiry of the 30-day notice period, any subsequent sale or disposal of Shares shall be in accordance with the provisions hereinbefore set out. </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_firstbold>
      <b>Condition of transfer. </b>It shall be a condition precedent to the right of the Transferor to transfer Shares that the transferee (if not already bound by the provisions of this Agreement) executes in such form as may be reasonably required by and agreed between the other Shareholder(s) a deed of ratification and accession substantially in the form set out in Schedule 4 (Deed of Ratification and Accession) under which the transferee shall agree to be bound by the obligations of and shall be entitled to the benefit of this Agreement as if an original Party in place of the Transferor. </numbered_3_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>DRAG-ALONG RIGHTS </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>In the event the Initiating Shareholders agree to the sale of all their Shares in the Company to an independent third party on an arms-length basis, all other Shareholders shall be required to approve, consent to and participate in the sale of all the Shares to the third-party ("Drag-along Sale"), and if the Drag-along Sale is structured as a sale of issued Shares (whether by merger, recapitalisation, consolidation or other disposal), then each Shareholder shall waive all first refusal and other rights in connection with the Drag-along Sale. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>Each Shareholder shall take all necessary and desirable actions in connection with the completion of a Drag-along Sale, including executing agreements and instruments and taking other actions as may be reasonably necessary to provide the representations, warranties, indemnities, covenants, conditions and other provisions and agreements, as the case may be, required to complete the Drag-along Sale. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>If a Shareholder fails for any reason to take any of the actions described above, it shall be deemed to have appointed any Director as its attorney, on its behalf and in its name, with full power, to execute, complete and deliver any document or instrument or to take any other action, including to receive the proceeds of the sale and to give good quittance for the sale price, in order to complete the Drag-along Sale. The Shareholders further agree to confirm and ratify the acts of any Director acting as its attorney under this Clause 9.3. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>A Drag-along Sale shall not be subject to Clause 8. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Initiating Shareholders shall deliver written notice to each other Shareholder setting out in reasonable detail the terms (including price, time and form of payment) of any Drag-along Sale (the "Drag-along Notice"). </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>Without limiting the generality of the provisions above, each Shareholder shall, on or before the date falling ten (10) Business Days after the date of the Drag-along Notice deliver to the Company written notice:- </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>setting out its agreement to the Drag-along Sale (including waiving all first refusal and similar rights); and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>if the Drag-along Sale is structured as a sale of Shares, enclosing share certificates representing its Shares and a transfer form duly executed in blank. </numbered_3_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>TAG-ALONG RIGHTS </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>Without prejudice to Clauses 8 and 9, in the event that either or both of the Founding Shareholders wish to transfer any of their Shares (the "Transferring Founding Shareholder"), such Transferring Founding Shareholder shall give notice in writing (the "Tag- along Notice") to the Investors of such desire. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Tag-along Notice shall specify: </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the name of the transferee to whom the Transferring Founding Shareholder proposes to transfer such Shares; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the number and class of such Shares proposed to be transferred (the "Tag-along Shares"); </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the price in cash for the transfer of each such Tag-Along Share; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all other terms and conditions of such transfer (which shall include the term that settlement of the aggregate price for all the Tag-along Shares shall be made in full in cash on completion). </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Tag-along Notice shall also enclose an offer (the "Tag-along Offer") dated the date of the Tag-along Notice made by the transferee to the Investors (the "Tag-along Investors") to purchase the Shares held by the Investors ("Tag-along Investor Shares") at such time and on the same terms as the Tag-Along Shares, and the sale of the Tag-along Investor Shares shall further include the following terms: </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the transaction price for the Tag-along Investor Shares shall include any consideration payable to the Founding Shareholders; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the Tag-Along Investors shall be entitled to receive the cash and/or Share equivalent of any non-cash component of the consideration received by the Transferring Founding Shareholder on the Tag-along Completion (as defined below); and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>no representations or warranties shall be provided by the Tag-along Investors to the transferee, save in respect of title to the Tag-along Investor Shares and the authority and capacity of the relevant Tag-along Investor, and that no encumbrance has been created or permitted to subsist over any interest in the Tag-along Investor Shares. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Tag-along Investor (if it so desires) may accept the Tag-Along Offer made to it by serving on the transferee (with a copy to the Transferring Founding Shareholder) notice in writing of its acceptance within thirty (30) Business Days of the date of the Tag-along Offer. </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_2_para>If the Tag-along Investor accepts the Tag-along Offer within the said thirty (30) Business Day period, the completion of the sale and purchase of the Tag-along Investor Shares and the completion (the "Tag-along Completion") of the sale and purchase of the relevant number of Shares held by the Transferring Founding Shareholder shall take place within ten (10) Business Days following the expiry of the said thirty (30) Business Day period at the registered office of the Company and on such date within such ten (10) Business Day period as the Transferring Founding Shareholder and the transferee shall agree in writing and notified in writing by the Transferring Founding Shareholder to the Tag-along Investor. </numbered_2_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_para>Each of the Investors and the Company warrants to the other Parties that, at the time this Agreement comes into effect, each of the following statements is true and correct:- </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>it is a corporation duly incorporated and validly existing under the laws of the place of its incorporation; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all action will have been taken so that the execution and delivery of, and the performance by it of its obligations under, this Agreement shall not, as the case may be, (a) conflict with or result in a breach of its memorandum and articles of association or other constitutive documents, (b) infringe, or constitute a default under, any instrument, contract, document or agreement to which it is a party or by which its assets are bound, or (c) result in a breach of any law, rule, regulation, ordinance, order, judgment or decree of or undertaking to any court, government body, statutory authority or regulatory, administrative or supervisory body (including without limitation, any relevant stock exchange or securities council) to which it is a party or by which it or its assets are bound, whether in Singapore or elsewhere; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>it has full power and authority to execute and deliver this Agreement and the agreements contemplated herein, and to consummate the transactions contemplated hereby and thereby and that this Agreement and all such other agreements and obligations entered into and undertaken in connection with the transactions contemplated hereby constitute its valid and legally binding obligations, enforceable against it in accordance with their respective terms. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>Each of the Founding Shareholders warrants to the other Parties that, at the time this Agreement comes into effect, each of the following statements is true and correct: - </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>he has the power to enter into, exercise its rights and perform and comply with his obligations under this Agreement; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>all actions, conditions and things required to be taken, fulfilled and done (including, without limitation, the obtaining of any necessary consents or licence or the making of any filing or registration) (a) in order to enable him lawfully to enter into, exercise his rights and perform and comply with its obligations under this Agreement, and to ensure that those obligations are legally binding and enforceable and (b) for the transfer of the Sale Shares, have been taken, fulfilled and done; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>his entry into, exercise of his rights and/or performance of or compliance with his obligations under this Agreement do not and will not violate, or exceed any power or restriction granted or imposed by (a) any law, regulation, authorisation, directive or order (whether or not having the force of law) to which he is subject, or (b) any agreement to which he may be a party or which may be binding on him or his assets. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_para>The Company hereby undertakes to obtain director's and officer's liability insurance in accordance with the Company's policy, industry practice and statutory requirements. </numbered_2_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>EVENT OF DEFAULT </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Event of default. </b>In the event of:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>a court order or decree being granted for the winding up or dissolution of any Shareholder, if such decree or order shall have continued undischarged or unstayed for a period of sixty (60) days or such Shareholder shall not have applied for the discharge or stay of such decree or order within such 60-day period; or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the entry against such Shareholder of a decree or order of a court having jurisdiction over it adjudicating it a bankrupt or insolvent or approving a petition seeking its reorganisation under any applicable bankruptcy or insolvency law, if such decree or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the assignment by such Shareholder for the benefit of its creditors of all or substantially all of its property or the winding-up or liquidation of its affairs, its admission in writing of its inability to pay its debts generally as they become due or its consent to the appointment of a receiver, liquidator, trustee, curator or assignee in bankruptcy or insolvency; or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the acquisition, pursuant to court order or otherwise, by a creditor of any Shareholder of any rights with respect to such Shareholder's interest in the Company or right to the profits of the Company if such acquisition shall continue undischarged for a period of thirty (30) days and such Shareholder shall not have instituted and diligently prosecuted the necessary legal proceedings for the rescission or discharge of such acquisition; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>a material breach of the terms of this Agreement by a Shareholder and such breach is not cured within ten (10) Business Days of the date the Company gives written notice to such a Shareholder of the material breach, </numbered_3_para>
    <para_1>then this Agreement shall be terminated with respect to such Shareholder (the "Terminated Shareholder") upon notice to the Terminated Shareholder. Notice of such termination may be given by any other Shareholder within 21 days after such Shareholder first becoming aware of the occurrence of an event of default (the "Default Notice"), and the Terminated Shareholder shall be deemed to have constituted the Company as its agent for the sale of all Shares held by the Terminated Shareholder. </para_1>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Deemed Notice. </b>In the event of termination of this Agreement with respect to the Terminated Shareholder pursuant to this Clause 12, the Terminated Shareholder shall be deemed to have served on the other Shareholders (the "Non-Defaulting Shareholders") a transfer notice offering to sell the legal and beneficial ownership of all (and not some ) of its Shares (the "Termination Transfer Shares") to the Non-Defaulting Shareholders in proportion (as nearly as the circumstances permit) to their respective effective shareholdings in the Company inter se (the "Deemed Offer"). Upon such transfer, the terminated Shareholder shall cease to have any equity interest in the Company or to have any rights or obligations under this Agreement except with respect to Clauses 10 and Clause 15.2 and any other provisions hereof expressly stated to survive any such termination. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Acquisition Price. </b>The acquisition price of the Termination Transfer Shares of the terminated Shareholder shall be:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>in event of termination of this Agreement with respect to the Terminated Shareholder due to Clause 12. 1.1 to 12.1.4, the Fair Value of the Termination Transfer Shares (the "Termination Transfer Price"); or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>in event of termination of this Agreement with respect to the Terminated Shareholder due to Clause 12.1.5, shall be the price paid by the Terminated Shareholder hereunder. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Transfer. </b>If the Non-Defaulting Shareholders shall within 30 days of the notice of determination of the Termination Transfer Price apply to the Company in writing for all (and not some only) of the Termination Transfer Shares, the Board shall allocate the Termination Transfer Shares to or amongst the applicants and in the case of competition pro rata (as nearly as possible) according to the proportion of Shares and Shareholder Loans (including accrued interest thereon) each applicant owns in and has granted to the Company, as the case may be. The Parties shall procure that the Company shall, within seven days following the expiry of the said 30-day period, give written notice of such allocations (an "Termination Allocation Notice") to the terminated Shareholder and to the Non-Defaulting Shareholders to whom the Termination Transfer Shares have been allocated, and shall specify in the Termination Allocation Notice the place and time (being not earlier than 14 and not later than 28 days after the date of the Termination Allocation Notice) at which the transfer of the Termination Transfer Shares so allocated shall be completed. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Non-Transfer. </b>If none of the Non-Defaulting Shareholders have applied for the Termination Transfer Shares, the Parties shall procure that the Company shall forthwith give notice of the same (the "Termination Non-Allocation Notice") to the terminated Shareholder and the Non-Defaulting Shareholders. If a Termination Non-Allocation Notice is given by the Company, the Termination Transfer Shares need not be transferred and the terminated Shareholder shall be allowed to keep the Termination Transfer Shares. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Completion of Deemed Offer. </b>The terminated Shareholder shall be bound to transfer the Termination Transfer Shares comprised in a Termination Allocation Notice to the purchasers named therein at the time and place therein specified, free from all Encumbrances and with all rights and advantages attaching thereto, by the delivery of duly executed transfer forms together with the share certificates in respect of such Termination Transfer Shares and, if required by the purchasers, the Stamp Duty Documents and a duly executed assignment in respect of the relevant amount of the Shareholder Loans (in such form as may be required by the purchasers) Provided Always that the terminated Shareholder shall remain and continue to be liable and be responsible for the discharge, observance and performance of all its liabilities and obligations, whether actual or contingent, arising out of or in connection with this Agreement at any time up to and including the date of the transfer of the Termination Transfer Shares and shall remain entitled to all accrued rights and benefits arising out of or in connection with the Termination Transfer Shares. If the terminated Shareholder shall fail to do so, each Director shall be deemed to have been the severally appointed attorney of the terminated Shareholder with full power to execute, complete and deliver, in the name and on behalf of the terminated Shareholder, transfers of the Terminated Transfer Shares and assignments of the relevant amount of Shareholder Loans (including accrued interest thereon) to the purchasers thereof against payment of the Termination Transfer Price to the Company, which shall be held in trust for the terminated Shareholder. The receipt of the Company for the purchase money shall be a good discharge to the Non-Defaulting Shareholder accepting the Termination Transfer Shares, and after the name of such Non-Defaulting Shareholder has been entered in the Register of Members in purported exercise of the aforesaid power, the validity of the proceedings shall not be questioned by any person. Upon a terminated Shareholder transferring all its Shares, it shall procure the immediate resignation of its nominees to the Board. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>No Prejudice to Other Rights. </b>The rights of the Non-Defaulting Shareholder under this Clause 12 shall be in addition and without prejudice to any other rights of the Non-Defaulting Shareholder against the terminated Shareholder at law or in equity including, but not limited to, the right to damages. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>DETERMINATION OF FAIR VALUE </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Appointment of Valuers. </b>For the purposes of determining the Fair Value of the relevant Shares, the Founding Shareholders and the Investors shall each appoint, within 7 days of the Default Notice, an independent valuer or merchant bank (the "Valuers") and the Fair Value shall be the average of the two values determined by the Valuers. The Valuers shall take into consideration:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>the valuation of companies operating businesses or ventures similar to the Business; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>valuing the net assets of the Company (including goodwill and all other intangible assets) as on an arm's length sale between a willing seller and a willing buyer; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>that the Company is carrying on business as a going concern; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>that the Shares to be sold are capable of being transferred without restriction; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>including provisions and adjustments for bad and doubtful debts and otherwise as the Valuer may (on the same bases as those applied in previous audited accounts of the Company) consider appropriate, but excluding any allowance or provision for deferred taxation; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>the application in all other respects of principles and practices consistent with those applied in the previous audited accounts of the Company unless in consistent with any accounting standard or applicable to a Singapore Company, in which case the latter shall prevail. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Determination. </b>The Valuer shall determine the Fair Value and deliver to the Company and the Shareholders a written certificate in respect of its determination within 21 days from its appointment. In such determination, the Valuer shall act as an expert and not as an arbitrator and its determination shall be final and binding on all persons concerned (in the absence of fraud or manifest error). </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Costs. </b>The costs and expenses for the appointment of the Valuer shall be borne (a) in an Event of Default, by the terminated Shareholder, or (b) in any other event, by such party as may be determined by the Board. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <a_left_sidehead>DURATION AND TERMINATION OF AGREEMENT </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Term. </b>This Agreement shall be effective as of the date of this Agreement without limit in point of time and shall cease and determine upon the dissolution of the Company, until and unless earlier terminated by the Parties' mutual written agreement or in accordance with the terms of this Agreement. If any Shareholder shall transfer the entirety of its Shares, it shall be released from its obligations under this Agreement but if at that time there are two or more Shareholders bound by the provisions of this Agreement, this Agreement shall continue in full force and effect as between such continuing Shareholders. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Termination and Winding-Up. </b>Without prejudice to the provisions hereunder, in the event that the Shareholders mutually agree that they no longer wish to carry on the operation of the Company as an on-going concern, the Parties shall take all such steps as may be necessary to procure the passing of a special resolution to voluntarily wind-up the Company on such terms as may be mutually agreed between the Parties. The costs and expenses arising in connection with such winding-up procedure shall be borne by all Shareholders in the Agreed Proportion. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_para>In the event of any liquidation, dissolution, winding up or Restructuring Event of the Company, distributions shall be made in the following priority: </numbered_2_para>
    <numbered_3_para>each Investor shall be entitled to receive, in preference to the Ordinary Shareholders, an amount equal to their Investment Amount plus any declared and unpaid dividends due to each Investor; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>thereafter, if there is any remaining amounts to be distributed, each Shareholder shall be entitled to receive a portion of such remaining amounts on an as-converted basis. </numbered_3_para>
    <a_left_sidehead>MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS </a_left_sidehead>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Communications. </b>All notices, demands or other communications required or permitted to be given or made hereunder shall be in writing and delivered personally or sent by prepaid registered post or by email sent to the email address set out below, provided always that the Parties acknowledge that any notice, demand or communication for which there is a procedure prescribed under any applicable law or regulation shall be delivered in accordance with such law or regulation. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <para_1>To the Founding Shareholders </para_1>
    <para_1>To Investor_X </para_1>
    <para_1>To Investor_Y </para_1>
    <para_1>Any notice, demand or communication delivered in accordance with this Clause 15.1 shall be deemed to have been duly served:- </para_1>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of delivery by hand, when delivered; </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of email, at the time of transmission initiated by the sender, or where applicable, receipt of a notice of delivery generated by the outgoing email server; or </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>in the case of registered post (if despatched to an address within the country of the sender) five (5) days or (if despatched by registered air-letter to an address outside the country of the sender) ten (I0) days after posting, and in proving the same it shall be sufficient to show that the envelope containing the same was duly addressed, stamped and posted. </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Confidentiality. </b>Each of the Parties agrees as follows:- </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para>to keep strictly secret and confidential, and under no circumstances to disclose to any person or entity which is not a Party, any information regarding the terms of this Agreement unless disclosure of such information is expressly permitted by the prior written consent in writing of the other Parties; and </numbered_3_para>
    <numbered_3_para>that all communications between the Parties or any of them and all information and other material supplied to or received by any of them from the others which is either marked "confidential" or is by its nature intended to be exclusively for the knowledge of the recipient alone and any information concerning the business transactions or the financial arrangements of the Parties or of any person with whom any of them is in a confidential relationship with regard to the matter in question coming to the knowledge of the recipient shall be kept confidential by the recipient; </numbered_3_para>
    <para_1>unless or until compelled to disclose by judicial or administrative procedures or in the opinion of its counsel, by other requirements of law, or the recipient can reasonably demonstrate that (a) it is or part of it is, in the public domain, whereupon, to the extent that it is public, this obligation shall cease or (b) it is required to be furnished to the bankers or investor(s) or potential investor(s) of any of the Parties or to any regulatory agencies as part of a initial public offering exercise involving the Company or its related corporation (as defined in the Act), and in such cases, this obligation shall cease only to the extent required under the respective circumstances. </para_1>
    <para_1>The obligations contained in this Clause 15.2 shall endure, even after the termination of this Agreement, without limit in point of time except to the extent that and until any confidential information enters the public domain as set out above. </para_1>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Release and indulgence. </b>Any liability to any Party may in whole or in part be released, compounded or compromised or time or indulgence given by that Party in that Party's absolute discretion as regards any other Party under such liability without in any way prejudicing or affecting the first Party's rights against any other Party or Parties under the same or a like liability whether joint and several or otherwise. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Remedies. </b>No remedy conferred by any of the provisions of this Agreement is intended to beexclusive of any other remedy which is otherwise available at law, in equity, by statute or otherwise, and each and every other remedy shall be cumulative and shall be in addition to every other remedy given hereunder or now or hereafter existing at law, in equity, by statute or otherwise. The election of any one or more of such remedies by any of the Parties shall not constitute a waiver by such Party of the right to pursue any other available remedies. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Time of the essence. </b>Any time, date or period mentioned in any provision of this Agreement may be extended by mutual agreement between the Parties but as regards any time, date or period originally fixed and not extended or any time, date or period so extended as aforesaid, time shall be of the essence. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Entire agreement. </b>This Agreement and the documents referred to herein are in substitution for all previous agreements between all or any of the Parties and contain the whole agreement between the Parties relating to the subject matter of this Agreement. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Amendments. </b>No amendment or variation of this Agreement shall be effective unless in writing and signed by or on behalf of each of the Parties. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Severance. </b>If any provision of this Agreement or part thereof is rendered void, illegal or unenforceable by any legislation to which it is subject, it shall be rendered void, illegal or unenforceable to that extent and no further. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Costs and expenses. </b>Each Party shall bear its own costs and expenses for the purpose of this Agreement and the transactions contemplated therein. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Assignment. </b>No Party shall have the right to assign all or any part of its interest in this Agreement without the prior written consent of the other Parties. This Agreement shall be binding upon and shall insure to the benefit of the Parties and their respective successors and permitted assigns. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Further assurance. </b>The Parties shall do all such acts and things and execute and sign all such documents and instruments as may be necessary, desirable or expedient to give effect to the terms of, and the commercial understanding of the Parties recorded in, this Agreement and the documents in connection herewith. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Counterparts. </b>This Agreement may be executed in two or more counterparts, all of which together shall constitute one and the same instrument. Any Party may enter into this Agreement by signing any such counterpart and each counterpart may be signed and executed by the Parties and transmitted by facsimile and shall be as valid and effectual as if executed as an original. For the avoidance of doubt, in the case of execution by way of counterparts, this Agreement shall not be deemed to be concluded until the last of such counterparts shall have been executed. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Governing law. </b>This Agreement (and any dispute, controversy, proceedings or claim of whatever nature arising out of this Agreement or its formation) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore and the Parties irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Republic of Singapore. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Dispute Resolution. </b>
    </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_3_para_fl>Notwithstanding any provisions to the contrary in this Agreement, in the event of any dispute or difference arising out of or in connection with this Agreement (including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination) whether during the continuance of this Agreement or at any time after the termination hereof, the Parties shall first attempt to resolve the same by negotiation in good faith or through mediation at the Singapore Mediation Centre ("SMC") between the appointed representatives of the respective Parties. </numbered_3_para_fl>
    <numbered_3_para_fl>In the event that the dispute or difference shall remain unresolved within thirty (30) days upon conclusion of such negotiation or mediation, any Party shall be entitled to refer the dispute to arbitration in Singapore in accordance with the Law Society of Singapore Arbitration Scheme ("LSAS") following the LawSoc Arbitration Rules 2011 for the time being in force, which rules are deemed to be incorporated by reference to this Clause. The arbitral tribunal shall consist of one (I) arbitrator, unless the Parties unanimously agree otherwise, to be appointed by the President of the Law Society of Singapore, under the LawSoc Arbitration Rules 201 I. The Seat and Venue of the arbitration shall be in the Republic of Singapore, and the language of the arbitration shall be in English. Any award made hereunder shall be final and binding upon the Parties and judgment on such award may be entered in any court or tribunal having jurisdiction thereof. </numbered_3_para_fl>
    <numbered_3_para_fl>Pending the resolution or final determination of the dispute or difference pursuant this Clause 15.14, the Parties shall procure that the Company shall, as far as practicable, continue to carry on its day-to-day business, having regard to the dispute or difference. </numbered_3_para_fl>
    <numbered_3_para_fl>Notwithstanding the foregoing, each of the Parties reserves its right to immediately commence any interim Court action such as an injunction against any of the other Parties to enforce the terms of this Agreement in a forum of its choice. </numbered_3_para_fl>
    <numbered_3_para_fl>This Clause 15.14 shall survive the termination of this Agreement for any reason whatsoever. </numbered_3_para_fl>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Applicability of the Contracts (Rights Of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore. </b>The Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore shall not under any circumstances apply to this Agreement and any person who is not a party to this Agreement (whether or not such person shall be named, referred to, or otherwise identified, or form part of a class of persons so named, referred to or identified, in this Agreement) shall have no right whatsoever under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Chapter 53B) of Singapore to enforce this Agreement or any of its terms. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <numbered_2_firstbold>
      <b>Prevalence of agreement. </b>This Agreement shall prevail to the extent of any inconsistency with the provisions of the Articles of the Company. </numbered_2_firstbold>
    <schedule_header>Details of Founding Shareholder </schedule_header>
    <schedule_header>Details of Other Investors </schedule_header>
    <schedule_header>Vesting Schedule for each Founding Shareholder </schedule_header>
    <schedule_header>Deed of Ratification and Accession </schedule_header>
    <para_1>THIS DEED OF RATIFICATION AND ACCESSION (the "Deed") is made and issued on [date] by[&#8226;] (Company Registration no. [&#8226;], a company incorporated in Singapore with its registered office at [&#8226;] (the "Company"), in favour of and for the benefit of each and all of the following (other than the Company):- </para_1>
    <bullets>the parties to the shareholders' agreement dated [&#8226;] (the "Shareholders' Agreement") made between, inter alia, XXX, Pte. Ltd. and the Parties listed in Schedule 2 thereto (collectively the "Initial Shareholders"); and </bullets>
    <bullets>all persons and corporations who are or subsequently become shareholders of the Company. </bullets>
    <para_1>WHEREAS:- </para_1>
    <para_1>The Shareholders' Agreement was entered into between the Initial Shareholders to regulate their rights and obligations in relation to, and the affairs of, the Company, a copy of which the Company hereby confirms that it has been supplied with and acknowledges the terms therein. </para_1>
    <para_1>NOW THIS DEED WITNESSES AS FOLLOWS:- </para_1>
    <numbered_1_para>In this Deed, unless the context otherwise requires, words and expressions respectively defined or construed in the Shareholders' Agreement shall have the same meanings when used or referred to herein. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>The Company hereby accedes to and ratifies the Shareholders' Agreement and covenants and agrees with the Initial Shareholders to be bound by the terms of the Shareholders' Agreement as if it had been an original party thereto from the outset and to duly and punctually perform and discharge all liabilities and obligations whatsoever from time to time to be performed or discharged by it under or by virtue of the Shareholders' Agreement in all respects as if named as a party therein. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>Each of the Initial Shareholders covenants and agrees that the Company shall be entitled to all the benefits of the terms and conditions of the Shareholders' Agreement to the intent and effect that the Company shall be deemed, with effect from the date on which the Company executes this Deed, to be a Party to the Shareholders' Agreement. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>This Deed shall hereafter be read and construed in conjunction and as one document with the Shareholders' Agreement and references in the Shareholders' Agreement to "this Agreement", and references in all other instruments and documents executed thereunder or pursuant thereto to the Shareholders' Agreement, shall for all purposes refer to the Shareholders' Agreement incorporating and as supplemented by this Deed. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>A person who is not a party to this Deed shall have no right under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Cap. 53B) of Singapore to enforce any of the provisions in this Deed but this does not affect any right or remedy of a third party which exists or is available apart from that Act. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>All notices to the Company shall be addressed as follows: </numbered_1_para>
    <para_1>data.company.address </para_1>
    <numbered_1_para>This Deed is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore. </numbered_1_para>
    <numbered_1_para>In relation to any legal action or proceedings arising out of or in connection with this Deed and such other documents relating to this Deed, each of the Parties hereby irrevocably submits to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Republic of Singapore, and irrevocably waives any objection on the grounds of forum non conveniens. </numbered_1_para>
    <para_1>IN WITNESS WHEREOF the Parties have hereunto set their hands this Deed has been signed by the [Parties/authorised representatives of the Parties] the day and year first before written. </para_1>
    <para_1>enumerate signatures</para_1>
  </Story_Main>
</Root>
