<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"Shareholders' Agreement", rcpts_to:rcpts_to}) ?>
<Story_Main>
<chapter_header>Shareholders' Agreement</chapter_header>
<centered>Regarding shareholding in Neighbourhood Distribution Pte Ltd</centered>
<centered>hereby referred to as "the Company"</centered>

<chapter_header>INDEX</chapter_header>

<numbered_1_para>Preamble</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Interpretation</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Shareholdings and rights</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Board of Directors</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Provision of information</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Operation of the Company</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Founder Shareholder undertakings</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Miscellaneous provisions</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Confidentiality</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Non-Disparagement</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Notices</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Amendments</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Further assurance</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_1_para>Governing law and dispute resolution</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>Schedule 1: ISSUE OF SHARES</para_1>
<para_1>Schedule 2: TRANSFER OF SHARES</para_1>
<para_1>Schedule 3: PROVISION OF INFORMATION</para_1>
<para_1>Schedule 4: CONSENT MATTERS</para_1>
<para_1>Schedule 5: SHAREHOLDING STRUCTURE</para_1>
<para_1>Schedule 6: VESTING SCHEDULE</para_1>
<para_1>EXHIBIT A: CONTACT DETAILS</para_1>

<para_1><span_smallcaps>THIS SHAREHOLDERS’ AGREEMENT</span_smallcaps> (the “Agreement”) is today entered into by and <span_smallcaps>BETWEEN:</span_smallcaps></para_1>

<?!= include("inc_enumerate_parties", data, rcpts_to, { term:{"new_investor": "Series Seed Investor"} }) ?>

<para_1><span_smallcaps>NOW IT IS AGREED</span_smallcaps> as follows:</para_1>

<numbered_1_firstbold>Preamble</numbered_1_firstbold>

<para_1>The Company has its registered address at <?= data.company.address ?> with registered share capital of <span_smallcaps>S$</span_smallcaps><?= data.amount_raised.TOTAL ?>.</para_1>

<numbered_2_para xname="core_business">The Company is a rental platform.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>This Agreement was made to cater for close and good cooperation between the Shareholders and to contribute to the development of the business of the Company, with the aim to build a strong market position.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_1_firstbold>Interpretation</numbered_1_firstbold>

<numbered_2_para>The Schedules are incorporated into and form part of this Agreement as if set out in full in this Agreement and a reference to "this Agreement" includes a reference to the Schedules.</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>In this Agreement words importing one gender shall be treated as importing any gender, words importing individuals shall be treated as importing corporations (and vice versa) and words importing the singular shall be treated as importing the plural and vice versa:</numbered_2_para>

<para_2_firstbold>Approved Sale. Means a sale or transfer of shares pursuant to the drag-along clauses in Schedule <xref to="exp_drag_along"/>;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Board means the board of directors of the Company from time to time;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Business means the core business of the company, as described in <xref to="exp_core_business"/>;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Ordinary Shares means the shares of the Company's Ordinary Shares that may be outstanding from time to time;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Permitted Disposal means:</para_2_firstbold>
<numbered_4_para>in relation to a corporate entity wholly owned by any of the parties; or</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>a Disposal to any person that is unanimously approved by the parties hereto;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>an Affiliate of a Series Seed Investor, meaning any partnership, limited liability company, corporation or venture capital fund with which the Series Seed Investor is affiliated to</numbered_4_para>

<para_2_firstbold>Shares means the convertible preference shares of the Company, including all Series Seed Preference Shares;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Series Seed Preference Shares means the Series Seed convertible preference shares of the Company;</para_2_firstbold>

<para_2_firstbold>Shares means shares in the capital of the Company, including the Preference Shares and the Ordinary Shares;</para_2_firstbold>

<numbered_1_firstbold>Shareholdings and rights</numbered_1_firstbold>

<numbered_2_para>Immediately before the completion of this Agreement, the share capital in the Company is divided between the Founders and Existing Shareholders as stated in <xref to="exp_pre_investment_capitalization"/>.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>On the date of this Agreement all the above mentioned Shares:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>are fully paid; and</numbered_3_para> 
<numbered_3_para>constitute the entire issued share capital of the Company; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>are legally and beneficially owned by the Shareholders in the numbers set out below; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>are free from any encumbrance, lien, charge (or any agreement or arrangement to create any of them); and other than as set out in <xref to="exp_special_rights_ss">, there are no outstanding options or other rights</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>in favour of any person to acquire any shares or to subscribe for shares in the capital of the Company.</numbered_3_para> 

<para_2>The Company only has two share classes- Ordinary Shares and Preference Shares. Whereby the Series Seed Preference Shares special rights are as described in this agreement.</para_2>

<para_2>The Agreement shall apply for any and all Shares held by any Party and its successors during the term of this Agreement.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Vesting of Founders’ Shares</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>Each Founder Shareholder shall have three years vesting beginning upon the signing of the Shareholders’ Agreement:</para_2>

<para_2><?= f_unrestricted_current ?> vesting immediately, with remaining vesting monthly over the next <? f_term_months ?> months as shown in Schedule <xref to="exp_vesting_schedule"/>. In the event of an acquisition or other change of control of the Company, Founders’ Shares will vest fully.</para_2>

<para_2>This Repurchase Option shall provide that upon the resignation or termination of the employment of or engagement with a Founder (“Outgoing Founder”), with or without cause, the remaining Founders first, and then the Company second or its assignee (to the extent permissible under applicable securities law qualification) retains the option to repurchase at the lower of cost or the current fair market value any unvested shares held by the Outgoing Founder.</para_2>   

<numbered_2_para xname="exp_special_rights_ss">Special rights for Series Seed Preference Shares:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>Liquidation Preference</numbered_3_para> 
<para_3>Upon liquidation of the company, the holders of Series Seed Preferences Shares will be entitled to receive <?= data.liquidation_preference ?> the original issue price. Thereafter, the Preference Shares participate with the Ordinary Shares pro rata on an as-converted basis. A merger, reorganization, change of control, sale of substantially all of the Company’s assets, or similar transaction will be treated as liquidation.</para_3> 

<numbered_3_para>Conversion</numbered_3_para> 
<para_3>The Series Seed Preference Shares are convertible into ordinary shares at a ratio of 1:1 (subject to proportional adjustments for stock splits, stock dividends and the like and subject to the Anti-Dilution protection in <xref to="exp_anti_dilution"/> at any time at the option of the holder.</para_3>

<numbered_3_para>Automatic Conversion</numbered_3_para>
<para_3>Each share of Series Seed Preference shall automatically convert into Ordinary, at the then applicable conversion rate, upon the earlier to occur of (i) the closing of a firmly underwritten public offering on a recognized public stock exchange (a "Qualified Public Offering"), or (ii) the affirmative consent of the holders of 2/3 of the then outstanding shares of Preference Shares.</para_3>

<numbered_3_para>Voting rights</numbered_3_para>
<para_3>The Series Seed Preference Shares vote together with the Ordinary Shares on all matters on an as-converted basis. Approval of a majority of the Series Seed Preference Shares is required to:</para_3>
<numbered_4_para>adversely change rights of the Series Seed Preference Shares;</numbered_4_para> 
<numbered_4_para>change the authorized number of Series Seed Preference shares;</numbered_4_para> 
<numbered_4_para>authorize a new series of Preference Shares having rights senior to or on parity with the Series Seed Preference Shares</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>redeem or repurchase any shares (other than pursuant to the Company’s right of repurchase at original cost);</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>declare or pay any dividend;</numbered_4_para> 
<numbered_4_para>change the number of directors; or</numbered_4_para> 
<numbered_4_para>liquidate or dissolve the Company, including any change of control.</numbered_4_para>

<numbered_3_para xname="exp_anti_dilution">Anti-Dilution protection</numbered_3_para>
<para_3>In the event that the Company issues additional securities at a purchase price less than the original Series Seed Preference conversion price, such conversion price shall be adjusted in accordance with the following formula:</para_3>

<para_3>CP2=CP1*(A+B)/ (A+C)</para_3>
<para_3>CP2= New Series Seed Preference Conversion Price</para_3>
<para_3>CP1= Series Seed Preference Conversion Price in effect immediately prior to new issue</para_3>

<para_3>A = Number of shares of Ordinary Shares deemed to be outstanding immediately prior to new issue (includes all shares of outstanding Ordinary Shares, all shares of outstanding Series Seed Preference Shares on an as converted basis, and all outstanding options on an as-exercised basis)</para_3>

<para_3>B = Aggregate consideration received by the Company with respect to the new issue divided by CP1</para_3>

<para_3>C = Number of shares of issued in the subject transaction</para_3>

<para_3>The following issuances shall not trigger anti-dilution adjustment:</para_3> 
<para_3>(i) securities issuable upon conversion of any of the Series Seed Preference, or as a dividend or distribution on the Series Seed Preference; (ii) securities issued upon the conversion of any debenture, warrant, option, or other convertible security; and (iii) Ordinary Shares issuable upon a stock split, stock dividend, or any subdivision of shares of Ordinary Shares</para_3>

<numbered_2_para>Employee Share Options (ESOP) Scheme</numbered_2_para> 
<para_2>The Shareholders agree that the board shall implement a share option program that will allow a committee (“the Option Committee”) to expand the current share capital with up to <?= data.parties.ESOP[%s] ?> and allocate the new shares to employees, advisors and board members.</para_2>

<para_2>The Option Committee shall be formed within six months after the date of this Agreement. The Option Committee shall have two members. One member appointed by the Series Seed Investors and one by the Founders.</para_2>

<para_2>The Series Seed Investors are not to be diluted from the issuing of shares under this ESOP. When ESOP shares are issued, the company will also issue shares to the Series Seed Investors so that Series Seed Investor’s ownership percentage remains unchanged as per Schedule <xref to="post_investment_capitalization_with_esop"/>. The board will be bound to issue shares according to the Option Committee’s recommendations.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Issue of Shares</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>The Parties agree and shall procure that any new Shares shall be issued in accordance with the provisions of Schedule <xref to="exp_issue_of_shares"/>.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Transfer of Shares</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>The Parties agree that Shares shall and may only be transferred in accordance with the provisions of Schedule <xref to="exp_transfer_of_shares"/>.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Shareholder adherence</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>Each of the Shareholders and the Company shall procure that no Shares are issued or transferred to any person who is not a Party unless and until such person enters into a binding legal agreement pursuant to which he, she or it agrees to be bound by and adhere to the provisions of this Agreement as if he, she or it had been named in this Agreement as a Shareholder.</para_2> 

<numbered_2_para>Exercise of shareholder rights</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>The Parties agree to exercise all rights and powers that he or it may have (whether as a director, shareholder or otherwise) including without limitation the voting rights in the Shareholders’ Meeting in a manner to comply with the objectives and obligations of this Agreement.</para_2>

<para_2>If a Shareholder fails, for any reason, to take any of the actions described in this Agreement within 14 days after having received due notice, it shall be deemed to have appointed any Company director as its attorney, on its behalf and in its name, with full power, to execute, complete and deliver any document or instrument or to take any other action, in order to comply with the objectives and obligations of this Agreement. The Shareholder further agrees to confirm and ratify the acts of any Company director acting as its attorney under this Clause.</para_2>
  
<numbered_1_para>Board of Directors</numbered_1_para>

<numbered_2_para>Members</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>The Board will consist of <?= data.number_directors_TOTAL ?> members. <?= data.number_directors_common ?> directors elected by holders of a majority of Ordinary Shares, <?= data.number_directors_seriesseed ?> elected by holders of a majority of Series Seed Preference Shares (the “Series Seed Director”).</para_2>

<para_2>The board members are elected at the general meeting for one year at the time. The board members will elect the chairman. All ordinary matters will be decided by a majority vote of the board. Consent Matters as specified in Schedule <xref to="exp_consent_matters"/> shall additionally require the affirmative vote of the Series Seed Director.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Meetings</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>No board meeting shall be convened on less than 10 Business Days’ notice. However, when there are objective grounds, the meeting can be convened by giving not less than 24 hours’ notice provided all the directors consents to the meeting being held on short notice. The invitation shall always have the agenda attached. Any documents relating to issues to be considered by the board members shall be received in advance no later than 2 days prior to the fixed date. Invitations to the board meetings shall be sent by email.</para_2>

<para_2>The board shall have at least 4 meetings per year, which can be held by video or audio conference.</para_2>

<para_2>An Annual General Meeting of shareholders will be held each year.</para_2>

<numbered_2_para>Remuneration</numbered_2_para>
<para_2>Representatives of shareholders shall not receive remuneration from the Company for their work as members to the Board.</para_2>

<numbered_1_para>Provision of information</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>The Company undertakes to Series Seed Investors that it shall deliver the information as set out in Schedule <xref to="exp_provision_of_information"/> of this Agreement within the timeframes specified.  The Company undertakes to all Shareholders that it shall deliver within 1 month after such accounts have been finalized, the annual audited/unaudited accounts for the Company.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Operation of the Company</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>The Company agrees and undertakes to each shareholder, except to the extent that this constitutes an unlawful fetter on its statutory powers, to comply with the undertakings set out in Schedule <xref to="exp_consent_matters"/>.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Founder undertakings</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>Whilst he is an employee of the Company, a Founder shall devote the whole of his time and attention to the business of the Company and shall not without the consent of the board, be or become director, or executive officer of any company nor be concerned or interested in any other new businesses.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Miscellaneous provisions</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>The Parties agree that there shall only be one Shareholders’ Agreement governing their investment in the Company. In case of a conflict between this Agreement and any other agreement between any of the Parties, this Agreement shall prevail.</para_1>

<para_1>This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter contemplated, and supersedes all prior oral and written agreements, memoranda or correspondences between the parties relating to this subject matter.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Confidentiality</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>The Parties agree that this Agreement shall be strictly confidential. Information received about a Party shall be kept confidential and may under no circumstances be used to cause damage to the other Party. The obligation to keep information confidential does not apply:</para_1>
<numbered_2_para>where a Party is obligated to provide information according to law, regulation or governmental decision (which in this regard also includes the relevant stock exchanges), or</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>the information is commonly known in the public domain and this is not a result of a breach by the other Party, or</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>to a Party disclosing information to any of its professional advisers, bankers, financiers and investors from time to time; or</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_1_para>Non-Disparagement</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>Each Party agrees that, he nor any of his affiliates, will directly or indirectly, will speak, write, verbalize or otherwise communicate in any way, any remark, comment, message, information, declaration, communication or other statement of any kind, whether verbal, in writing, electronically transferred or otherwise, that might reasonably be construed to be derogatory or critical of, or negative toward, the Company or any of its directors, officers, Affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, agents or representatives.</para_1>

<para_1>Nothing herein shall prevent a Party from making any truthful statement in connection with any legal proceeding or investigation by the Company or any governmental authority.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Notices</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>All notices pursuant to or regarding this Agreement shall be made by email to the board to the email addresses specified in EXHIBIT <xref to="exp_contact_details"/>, or such other email addresses notified by the relevant Party to all other Parties.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Amendments</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>Any amendment to this Agreement are required to be made in writing and requires the consent of Parties who together hold shares representing at least 70 per cent of the total issued share capital of the Company and a majority of the holders of Series Seed Preference Shares.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Further assurance</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>Each Party shall use all reasonable endeavours to execute or procure the execution of any additional documents and to do or procure any other acts or things which may be required to give full effect to this Agreement.</para_1>

<numbered_1_para>Governing law and dispute resolution</numbered_1_para>

<para_1>This Agreement shall be governed by Singapore law and any disputes hereunder shall be referred to arbitration in Singapore. Any dispute arising out of or in connection with this Agreement, including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination that cannot be resolved on an amicable basis shall be conducted under the provisions of the applicable arbitration laws of the Republic of Singapore. This Agreement drafted in the English language shall be the only binding version.</para_1>


<chapter_header xname:"issue_of_shares">Schedule 1: ISSUE OF SHARES</chapter_header>

<numbered_1_para>The Board can decide to increase the share capital in the event this is deemed to be in the best interest of the company.</numbered_1_para>

<numbered_2_para>When the board considers expanding the share capital it should prepare a written proposal outlining the reasons behind the proposal. Thereafter the proposal should be voted over at a board meeting. An affirmative vote of the Series Seed Director will be required for the proposal to pass.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>If the Board of Directors is proposing to issue such Shares wholly or partly for non-cash consideration, the cash value of such consideration for the purposes of this sub-paragraph shall be as reasonably determined by the Board of Directors.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>Shares must be issued in accordance with the stipulations in paragraph <xref to="exp_pro_rata"/> and schedule <xref to="exp_consent_matters"/> of this agreement.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>Series Seed Investors will have the right to participate on a pro rata basis in subsequent issuances of equity securities.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_1_para>Nothing in this clause (Series Seed Investors’ Pro-rata investment rights) applies to a Qualified IPO or to an issue of Shares or securities under the ESOP or securities issued pursuant to the conversion or exercise of warrants.</numbered_1_para>

<numbered_1_para xname="exp_pro_rata">The Company grants to each Series Seed Investor, a right to purchase its Pro Rata Share (based on its percentage of the outstanding Ordinary Shares), calculated on a fully-diluted and as-converted basis of any new Shares or securities (or less) which the Company, from time to time, proposes to sell and issue.</numbered_1_para>  

<numbered_1_para xname="exp_pro_rata_notice_exercise">In the event the Company proposes to issue new Shares or securities, it shall give Series Seed Investor written notice (Issuance Notice) describing the type of new Shares or securities, their price and the general terms upon which the Company proposes to issue them. Series Seed Investors have 10 Business Days commencing on the date of the Issuance Notice (Pro-Rata Purchase Exercise Period) to elect to purchase its Pro Rata Share of new Shares or securities (or less) at the price and upon the terms specified in the Issuance Notice. It shall make that election by providing a written notice to the Company during the Pro-Rata Purchase Exercise Period stating the number of new Shares or securities to be purchased.</numbered_1_para>

<numbered_1_para xname="exp_pro_rata_notice_exercise">No later than 5 Business Days following the expiration of the Pro-Rata Exercise Period, the Company shall give written notice to Series Seed Investors specifying the number of new Shares that Series Seed Investors have agreed to purchase (including, for the avoidance of doubt, when such number is 0).</numbered_1_para>

<numbered_1_para>The Company may, for the period commencing on the date falling 16 Business Days after the date of the Issuance Notice and ending on the date falling 90 Business Days after the date of the Issuance Notice, sell any new Shares or securities not purchased by Series Seed Investors pursuant to the pro-rata rights in Schedule <xref to="exp_pro_rata_notice_exercise"/> to any person, at a price and upon terms no more favourable to the purchasers than specified in the Issuance Notice.  If Company fails to sell or issue the new Shares or securities within the period described in this Schedule <xref to="exp_pro_rata_notice_exercise"/>, the Company shall not thereafter issue or sell the new Shares or securities, without first again offering the Shares or securities to the Series Seed Investors in the manner provided in Schedule <xref to="exp_pro_rata_notice_exercise"/>.</numbered_1_para>


<chapter_header xname="exp_transfer_of_shares">Schedule 2: TRANSFER OF SHARES</chapter_header>


<a_left_sidehead>Transfer</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>Other than pursuant to a Permitted Disposal, or an Approved Sale, any transfer of its Shares by a Shareholder before a Qualified IPO or deemed liquidation event is subject to the following provisions:</para_1>

<para_1>A Shareholder (each, an Offering Party) who wishes to dispose any of its Shares (Offered Shares) as a result of a bona fide offer from any third party (including another Shareholder) (Third Party) must before the Disposal give effect to:</para_1>
<para_1>•	the rights of first refusal of the Shareholders excluding the Offering Party (Other Shareholders) set forth below; or</para_1>
<para_1>•	the Other Shareholders’ co-sale rights set forth below,</para_1>
<para_1>in the manner described and in accordance with the mechanics stated in this Clause.</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead xname="exp_right_of_first_refusal">Rights of First Refusal</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party shall by written notice (a Transfer Notice) to the Company and the Other Shareholders state that it proposes to dispose of its Shares.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>A Transfer Notice constitutes an offer by the Offering Party to sell the Offered Shares to the Other Shareholders at the price stated in the Transfer Notice.  It shall state:</numbered_3_para>
<para_3>- the proposed price per Share;</para_3>
<para_3>- the number of Shares the Shareholder proposed to dispose of;</para_3> 
<para_3>- in reasonable detail the nature and manner of Disposal; and</para_3>
<para_3>- in reasonable detail the identity and contact of the Third Party.</para_3> 

<para_2>A Transfer Notice that does not comply with the requirements above is invalid and has no effect.</para_2>

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party agrees that the Transfer Notice also constitutes the Company as its agent for the sale of the Offered Shares at the sale price stated in the Transfer Notice, for so long as the pre-emptive rights under this Clause have not been exhausted.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party shall not revoke the Transfer Notice or the Company's appointment as its agent as described above without the Shareholders' unanimous approval.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>A Shareholder (other than the Offering Party) who wishes to exercise its rights of first refusal under this Clause (Accepting Shareholder) shall serve written notice (Acceptance Notice) on the Company with copy to the other Shareholders, as applicable on or before the date falling 10 Business Days after the date of the Transfer Notice.  Any Shareholder who shall not have sent such notice will be deemed to have waived its rights of first refusal under this Clause.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>An Acceptance Notice shall state clearly the number of Offered Shares that the relevant Shareholder wishes to purchase, failing which the Acceptance Notice shall be invalid and the Shareholder shall be deemed to have waived its rights of first refusal under this Clause unless the Shareholder cures the defect within 5 Business Days.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>The Company shall on or before the date falling 20 Business Days after the date of the Transfer Notice by notice (Allocation Notice) to the Offering Party and each Accepting Shareholder state the number of Offered Shares allocated to each Accepting Shareholder.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>If there are more than one Accepting Shareholder, then the Company shall allocate the Offered Shares among all Accepting Shareholders as fairly as possible in the circumstances, but in compliance with the following allocation terms:-</numbered_3_para>

<para_3>if the number of Offered Shares is insufficient to fulfil the number of Offered Shares requested by all Accepting Shareholders, then 1) First each Accepting Shareholder who is holding Preference Shares (Accepting Preference Shareholders) shall be allocated in proportion to its Pro-Rata Share of the Offered Shares; then 2) Second each Accepting Shareholder who is holding Ordinary Shares (Accepting Ordinary Shareholders) shall be allocated in proportion to its Pro-Rata Share of the Offered Shares; and</para_3>

<numbered_3_para>the application of the previous provision shall not require an Accepting Shareholder under any circumstances to purchase more Offered Shares than the number stated in its Acceptance Notice.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>the process above shall be repeated (as applicable) first with Accepting Preference Shareholders and second with Accepting Ordinary Shareholders until all Offered Shares have been offered to Accepting Shareholders or there are no more Accepting Shareholders for the remaining Offered Shares.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>The Company shall immediately after the final allocation of the Offered Shares issue a final Allocation Notice to each Accepting Shareholder and the Offering Party, stating:</numbered_3_para>
<para_3>•	each Accepting Shareholder's finally allocated Offered Shares; and</para_3>
<para_3>•	a place and time (being not earlier than 10 and not later than 20 Business Days after the date of the final Allocation Notice) at which the sale and purchase of the Offered Shares shall be completed.</para_3> 

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party shall transfer all Offered Shares at the time and place specified in the final Allocation Notice, against payment by the relevant Accepting Shareholder of the sale price.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>If it fails to transfer the Offered Shares at such time, the Offering Party agrees that it is deemed to have appointed the chairman of the Board as its power of attorney with full power, in the name and on behalf of the Offering Party, to execute, complete and deliver all documents and actions (including giving a receipt for the sale price) to transfer the Offered Shares to the relevant Accepting Shareholder against payment of the sale price.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>On payment of the sale price, the Offering Party agrees that the relevant Accepting Shareholder is deemed to have obtained a good quittance for the payment.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>the Shareholders agree that upon a completion of the Offered Shares sale and purchase described above, the Accepting Shareholder on execution and delivery of the applicable transfer form is entitled to have its Offered Shares being entered in the Company's shareholders' register as the registered holder of the relevant Offered Shares.</numbered_3_para>


<b_left_sidehead>Co-Sale Rights</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para>If any Shareholder does not exercise its rights of first refusal above and notifies the Offering Party in writing (Shareholders’ Notice) on or before the date falling 10 Business Days after the date of the Transfer Notice that it wishes to participate in the sale of the Offered Shares on the same terms and conditions as specified in the Transfer Notice, such Shareholder may participate in the same Disposal and include the number of its Shares equal to its Pro Rata Share of the Offered Shares (which shall then also become “Offered Shares” hereunder) for sale in the same Disposal on the same terms and conditions as specified in the Transfer Notice.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>If a Shareholder exercises its co-sale rights under this Clause (Co-Sale), it shall no longer have the rights of first refusal described in this Clause with respect to the same transaction.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>The Shareholders’ Notice to the Offering Party shall indicate the number of Shares the applicable Shareholder wishes to co-sell.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>The relevant Shareholder(s) shall effect its participation in the co-sale by promptly delivering to the Offering Party for Disposal to the proposed transferee one or more certificates, properly endorsed for transfer and accompanied by transfer documents (where required) duly executed by the relevant Shareholders).</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party shall deliver the share certificate and transfer documents that the relevant Shareholder delivers to it to the proposed transferee in completion of the Disposal of the Offered Shares pursuant to the terms of the Transfer Notice, and the Offering Party shall immediately upon receipt remit to the relevant Shareholder the sale proceeds due to such Shareholder.</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>If any proposed transferee of the Offered Shares prohibits the participation of the relevant Shareholder’s exercising of its co-sale rights or otherwise refuses to accept Shares from such Shareholder, the Offering Party shall not sell to the proposed transferee any Shares unless and until, simultaneously with the sale, the Offering Party purchases from the affected Shareholder, at the price and upon the terms described in the Transfer Notice, such Shareholder's Shares which would have been subject to the co-sale rights under this Clause (Co-Sale Rights).</numbered_3_para> 

<numbered_3_para>The Offering Party may:</numbered_3_para> 
<para_3>•	after giving effect to the rights of first refusal; and</para_3>
<para_3>•	including in the proposed Disposal any relevant Shareholders’ co-sale Shares
in accordance with this Clause, dispose of the Offered Shares to any other third party on terms no more favourable to the third party than those stated in the Transfer Notice.</para_3>

<b_left_sidehead>The Company shall not approve or register any transfers of Shares unless it is:</b_left_sidehead>
<numbered_3_para>effected in accordance with this Clause; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the transferee of the Shares, if not already a party, has ratified this Agreement to the Company's reasonable satisfaction.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>Permitted Disposal.  Any Shareholder may make a Permitted Disposal without the consent of the Board or any other Shareholder but with a 15-day prior written notice to the Company and the other Shareholders.</numbered_3_para> 

<a_left_sidehead xname="exp_drag_along">Drag Along – value target</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>If a majority of the holders of Preference Shares agree to a sale or liquidation of the Company at any time after the date of signing of the Shareholders’ Agreement at a valuation of the Company which is equal to or greater than <span_smallcaps>S$</span_smallcaps>40,000,000 the holders of the remaining Preference and Ordinary Shares shall consent to and raise no objections to such sale and, if required, sell their shares on the same terms.</para_1>

<a_left_sidehead xname="exp_drag_along">>Drag Along – time trigger</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>If a majority of the holders of Preference Shares and the common shareholders agree to a sale or liquidation of the Company at any time after 3 years from the date of signing of the Shareholders’ Agreement, the holders of the remaining Preference and Ordinary Shares shall consent to and raise no objections to such sale and, if required, sell their shares on the same terms.</para_1>

<a_left_sidehead xname="exp_drag_along">Drag Along – by majority decision</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>If the holders of at least 51 per cent in aggregate of the Ordinary Shares and 2/3 of the holders of Preference Shares (the “Selling Shareholders”) wish to transfer the Shares held by them (the "Sale Shares") to an independent, bona fide and arm's length third party purchaser (the "Third Party Purchaser"), the holders of the remaining Preference and Ordinary Shares shall consent to and raise no objections to such sale and, if required, sell their shares on the same terms.</para_1>

<a_left_sidehead>Exercising Drag Along rights</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>An offer to purchase the Sale Shares shall specify:</para_1>
<numbered_2_para>the number of Sale Shares;</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>the price per Sale Share; and</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>the identity of the Third Party Purchaser.</numbered_2_para>

<para_1>Having received an offer for the Sale Shares, then the Selling Shareholders shall have the option (the "Drag Along Option") to require, in accordance with this agreement, all of the other holders of Shares (the "Other Shareholders") to transfer all their Shares with full title guarantee to such Third Party Purchaser provided that:</para_1>

<para_2>No Sale Shares may be sold to a Third Party Purchaser at a price which is lower than that specified in the Offer Notice; and so that, if the Selling Shareholders are proposing to transfer such Sale Shares wholly or partly for non-cash consideration, the cash value of such consideration for the purposes of this sub-paragraph shall (if not agreed by the Parties) be as reasonably determined by a firm of independent accountants, whose determination shall be final and binding on the Selling Shareholders.</para_2> 

<para_2>The Selling Shareholders may exercise the Drag Along Option by giving notice to that effect (a "Drag Along Notice") to all the Other Shareholders.  A Drag Along Notice shall specify that the Other Shareholders are required to transfer all of their Shares pursuant to this agreement to the Third Party Purchaser, the price at which the Shares are to be transferred, the proposed date of transfer and the identity of the third party purchaser.</para_2> 

<para_2>A Drag Along Notice shall be irrevocable and shall lapse if for any reason the Selling Shareholders shall not sell their Shares to the Third Party Purchaser within 60 days after the date of the Drag Along Notice.  A further Drag Along Notice may be served following the lapse of any particular Drag Along Notice.</para_2>

<para_2>The Other Shareholders shall be obliged to sell their Shares at the price specified in the Drag Along Notice, which shall attribute an equal value to each of the Shares.</para_2>

<para_2>Upon any person, following the issue of a Drag Along Notice, becoming a member of the Company pursuant to the exercise of a pre-existing option to acquire Shares or otherwise (a “New Member”), a Drag Along Notice shall be deemed to have been served upon the New Member on the same terms as the previous Drag Along Notice who shall be bound to sell and transfer all such Shares acquired by him to the Third Party Purchaser and the provisions of this agreement shall apply to the New Member.</para_2>

<para_2>The liability of each Shareholder in such transaction is several (and not joint) and does not exceed the Shareholder's pro rata portion of any claim and the consideration to be paid to the Shareholder’s in such transaction will be allocated as if the consideration were the proceeds to be distributed to the Company's Shareholders in a liquidation under the Company's then-current Certificate of Incorporation. Each Shareholder shall indemnify the purchaser only to the extent of its own representations & warranties.</para_2>

<para_2>Completion of the sale of the Other Shareholders' Shares shall take place on the same date as the date proposed for completion of the sale of the Selling Shareholders' Shares.</para_2>

<para_2>Each of the Other Shareholders shall on the date of service of the Drag Along Notice be deemed to have irrevocably appointed each of the Selling Shareholders separately to be his attorney to execute any stock transfer and to do such other things as may be necessary or desirable to accept, transfer and complete the sale of the Shares pursuant to this agreement and after the Third Party Purchaser (or such person as he may direct) is registered as the holder of the Shares the validity of the proceedings shall not be questioned by any person.</para_2> 

<para_2>Restrictions contained in this Agreement in Schedule <xref to="exp_right_of_first_refusal"/> shall not apply on any sale and transfer of Shares to the Third Party Purchaser named in a Drag Along Notice.</para_2>

<a_left_sidehead>Tag Along</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>No sale, transfer or other disposition of 50 per cent or more in aggregate of the issued Shares or of any interest in any of those Shares to a bona fide and arm's length Third Party Purchaser shall be permitted unless and until the Third Party Purchaser shall have offered to purchase all of the Shares in the Company held by members who are unconnected with the Third Party Purchaser (the "Remaining Members").</para_1>

<para_1>The offer to be made by the Third Party Purchaser shall be in writing and capable of acceptance by the members for not less than 14 days from the date of the offer.  The offer shall be deemed to have been irrevocably rejected by a member if that member shall not accept the offer in accordance with its terms, conditions and provisions and the specified period for acceptance of the offer.</para_1>

<para_1>The price for the Remaining Members' Shares shall be no less than the highest price offered by the Third Party Purchaser for the other Shares.</para_1>
 
<chapter_header xname="exp_provision_of_information">Schedule 3: PROVISION OF INFORMATION</chapter_header>

<para_1>The Company undertakes to Series Seed Investors that it shall deliver to each such shareholder:</para_1> 

<numbered_2_para>If the Company fails to comply with its obligations under this Schedule. Any Shareholder or Series Seed Investors can appoint an independent accountant or accountants or other professional advisers of its own choosing to investigate the affairs of the Company to obtain the information required and if such accountants or other advisers are so appointed:</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_3_para>the Company shall and shall procure that their respective accountants shall afford to such person(s) such assistance and co-operation (including, without limitation, access to the accounting and other books and records of the Group) as he or they may request; and</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>the costs of and incidental to such appointment shall be borne entirely by the Company.</numbered_3_para>

<para_1>The Company undertakes to all Series Seed Investors that it shall deliver to each such shareholder:</para_1>

<numbered_2_para><? if (data.financial_submission_deadline) { ?> within 3 months of the end of each calendar year<?}?>, a copy of the management reporting packages and management accounts together, being the unaudited balance sheet, cash flow, and profit and loss statements for the Company, and annual budget.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para><? if (data.financial_submission_deadline) { ?>within 3 months after such accounts have been finalised, the annual accounts for the Company<?}?>; and</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>such operating, business and financial information concerning the Company as may be reasonably requested from time to time (including, without limitation copies of the Company's bank statements) and a copy of all board minutes and papers which are circulated to the directors prior to each board meeting as soon as practicable following a written request.</numbered_2_para>


<chapter_header xname="exp_consent_matters">Schedule 4: CONSENT MATTERS</chapter_header>

<para_1>The Company will not without the written consent of the Series Seed Investor, which may be provided by the Series Seed Investor’s nominee director at any directors' meeting, do or agree or commit to do any of the following:</para_1>

<numbered_2_para>any amendment or change of the rights, preferences, privileges and powers of, or the restrictions provided for the benefit of, the Series Seed Preference Shares</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>any action that creates preferences or priority as to dividends or assets senior to or on a parity with the Series Seed Preference Shares;</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>any material amendment of the Constitution;</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>the sale of all or substantially all the Company's assets or merger or consolidation of the Company with any other entity;</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>the liquidation, termination or dissolution of the Company;</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>the declaration or payment of a dividend;</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>any change in number of Directors;</numbered_2_para> 

<numbered_2_para>any increase of the registered capital of the Company or any creation or issuance or allotment or redemption of any class of shares or securities convertible into or exchangeable or exercisable for any shares in the capital of the Company, other than in connection with a Qualified IPO;</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>change the principal business of the Company, enter new lines of business, or exit the current line of business;</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>any single expenditure which exceeds <span_smallcaps>S$</span_smallcaps>50,000.</numbered_2_para>


<chapter_header>Schedule 5: SHAREHOLDING STRUCTURE</chapter_header>



<b_left_sidehead xname="exp_pre_investment_capitalization">Pre-investment capitalization</b_left_sidehead>

<para_1>
<Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="4" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(newIssues.holders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="110" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="76" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>ID</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Address</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="90" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Number of Shares Held</cell_c></Cell>
<? Logger.log("corpsec-allotment: newIssues.holders = %s", newIssues.holders); ?>
<? for (var hh in newIssues.holders) { with(newIssues.holders[hh]) { ?>
<? var new_investors = data.parties.new_investor.filter(function(ni){return (ni.name == hh)});
  var new_investor;
  if (new_investors.length) {
    new_investor = new_investors[0];
    Logger.log("corpsec-allotment: newIssues.holders :: new_investor = %s (%s %s)", new_investor.name, new_investor.idtype, new_investor.id);
  } else {
	Logger.log("corpsec-allotment: unable to find party new_investor named %s", hh);
	continue;
  }
?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="110" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= hh ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="76" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= new_investor.idtype ?> <span_ucnum><?= new_investor.id ?></span_ucnum></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= new_investor.address ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="90" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= shares ?> <?= new_investor.share_type ||data.security_type_short_plural ?> for <?= newIssues.holders[hh]._orig_money ? money : "no consideration" ?><?= new_investor.commitment_comment ? new_investor.commitment_comment : "" ?></cell_c></Cell>
<? } } ?>
</Table>
</para_1>


<b_left_sidehead xname="exp_post_investment_capitalization_with_esop">Post-investment capitalization (with Share Option of <?= data.parties.ESOP[%s] ?>)</b_left_sidehead>



<chapter_header xname="exp_vesting_schedule">Schedule 6: VESTING SCHEDULE</chapter_header>

<? var activeRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound(); ?>
<? for (var bstk in activeRound.by_security_type) { var bstv = activeRound.by_security_type[bstk]; ?>
<?   Logger.log("keyHolders: round=%s, by_security_type:%s has keys keys %s", activeRound.name, bstk, bstv); ?>
<? } ?>
<? var keyHolders  = data.parties.key_holder ?>
<? var previousRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getPreviousRound(); ?>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="8" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(keyHolders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Shares</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Vesting Commencement</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Vesting Class</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Currently Vested</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Currently Restricted</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Cliff Date</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Acceleration</cell_c></Cell>

<? for (var hh in keyHolders) {
  Logger.log("keyHolders: outputting based on data.parties.key_holder[%s] = %s", hh, keyHolders[hh].name);
  with(keyHolders[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= name ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!= data.capTable.investorHoldingsInRound(name, previousRound) ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_commencement ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c>Class F Shares</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_unrestricted_current ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_restricted_current ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_cliff_end_date ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= acceleration ?></cell_c></Cell>

<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>

<chapter_header xname="exp_contact_details">Exhibit A: Contact Details</chapter_header>

<para_1>
<Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="2" aid:trows="7" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Company Address</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.company.address ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Email</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.company.email ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Attention</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.company.signatory_name || data.company.name ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>New Investor Address</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.new_investor.address ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Email</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.new_investor.email ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Attention</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.new_investor.signatory_name || data.new_investor.name ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Existing Investor Address</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.existing_investor.address ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Email</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.existing_investor.email ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Attention</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.existing_investor.signatory_name || data.existing_investor.name ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Founders Address</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.parties.founders.address ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Email</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.parties.founders.email ?></cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="122" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Attention</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="274" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl><?= data.parties.founders.signatory_name || data.parties.founders.name ?></cell_fl></Cell>
</Table>
</para_1>

<chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>

   <?!= include("inc_enumerate_signatures", data, {rcpts_to:rcpts_to, _include2: { term: { new_investor: "Series Seed Investor" } } }
) ?>

</Story_Main>
</Root>
