<a_left_sidehead orig_num="15" xname="15_drag_along_rights">Drag-Along Rights</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para orig_num="15.1">In the event of an Equity Sale, each Shareholder shall:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para orig_prefix="a">if the Equity Sale is in respect of 100% of the Shares, transfer all of its Shares; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para orig_prefix="b">if the Equity Sale is in respect of less than 100% of the Shares (the "Equity Sale Shares"), transfer its Shareholding Proportion of the Equity Sale Shares,</numbered_3_para>
<p comment="MAY NEED FIXING">and for this purpose, shall promptly deliver to the Company (who shall be deemed to be constituted the agent of the Shareholders for the Equity Sale in accordance with the Amended Articles) for transfer to the third party purchaser(s) one or more share transfer forms, properly executed for transfer, which represent the number of Shares such Shareholder is to transfer, together with the relevant share certificate(s) and a working sheet signed by a Director or secretary of the Company, computing the net asset value per share of the Company, for the purposes of stamping the said transfer.</p>
<numbered_2_para orig_num="15.2">Upon completion of the Equity Sale upon such terms and conditions as approved, the Company shall remit to the respective Shareholder its portion of the proceeds to which such Shareholder is entitled by reason of its participation in the Equity Sale.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para orig_num="15.3">In the event that any Shareholder fails to complete the sale of its Shares on the completion of the Equity Sale, any Director shall be deemed to have been appointed attorney of such Shareholder with full power to execute, complete and deliver, in the name and on behalf such Shareholder, transfers of such Shareholder's Shares to the third party purchaser(s) against payment of the purchase price for the Shares to the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para orig_num="15.4">On payment of the purchase price to the Company, the Company shall cancel the share certificate(s) representing the Shares issued in favour of the Shareholders and:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para orig_prefix="a">issue and deliver new share certificate(s) for the Shares to the third party purchaser(s); and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para orig_prefix="b">if relevant, issue and deliver to each Shareholder, new share certificate(s) in respect of their remaining Shares.</numbered_3_para>
<p>The Company shall forthwith pay the purchase price into a separate bank account in the Company's name and shall hold such price for the account of the Shareholders. For the purposes of calculating the purchase price due to Preference Shareholders, for the avoidance of doubt any sale pursuant to the drag along rights under this Clause <xref to="15_drag_along_rights"></xref> (Drag-Along Rights) shall with respect to the Amended Constitution be deemed a Liquidation Event (as such term is defined under the Amended Constitution).</p>
