
  <a_left_sidehead orig_num="14" xname="14_tag_along_rights">Tag-Along Rights</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.1" xname="14.1_after_compliance_with_the_procedures_set">If any Shareholder ("Transferring Shareholder") intends to sell to a bona fide third party ("Third Party Purchaser") or accept an offer from a Third Party Purchaser to sell all or any part of its Shares held by the Transferring Shareholder such that on completion of such transaction or a series of related transactions, the Third Party Purchaser will hold more than 5% of the voting shares in the capital of the Company, the Shareholder shall, after complying with the rights of first refusal provisions in the Constitution, promptly give written notice (the "Notice of Transfer") simultaneously to <?=data.tags_notice_to ? data.tags_notice_to+" and " : ""?>the Company. The Notice of Transfer shall describe in reasonable detail the terms and conditions of the proposed Transfer, including without limitation, the number of Shares proposed to be Transferred ("Transferred Shares"), the nature of such Transfer, the consideration to be paid per Transferred Share, and the name and address of the Third Party Purchaser. Upon receipt of the Notice of Transfer the Company shall forward the Notice of Transfer to its members, advising them of their rights:</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.2" xname="14.2_each_preference_shareholder_shall_have_t">Each <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder shall have the right, exercisable upon written notice (the "Notice of Participation") to the Company within thirty (30) days after the receipt of the Notice of Transfer, to inform the Company in writing whether it elects to participate in the Transfer by the Transferring Shareholder on the same terms and conditions as set forth in the Notice of Transfer (such <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder who elects to participate in the Transfer by the Transferring Shareholder, the "Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder"). The Notice of Participation shall indicate the number of Shares the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder elects to Transfer pursuant to this Clause <xref to="14.2_each_preference_shareholder_shall_have_t"></xref>, up to that number of Shares equal to the product obtained by multiplying (a) the aggregate number of Shares set forth in the Notice of Transfer by (b) the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder's Shareholding Proportion at the time of the Transfer. Each Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder shall promptly deliver to the Company (who shall be deemed to be constituted the agent of the Transferring Shareholder and the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders for the transfer in accordance with the Amended Articles) for transfer to the Third Party Purchaser one or more share transfer forms, properly executed for transfer, which represent the number of Shares which the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder elects to transfer, together with the relevant share certificates and a working sheet signed by a Director or the secretary of the Company computing the net asset value per share of the Company, for the purposes of stamping the said Transfer. To the extent one or more of the other <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders exercises such right of participation in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth above, the number of Shares that the Transferring Shareholder may Transfer in the transaction shall be correspondingly reduced.</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.3">To the extent any other <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder fails to elect to participate in the Transfer by the Transferring Shareholder, such <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder shall be deemed to have consented to the Transfer by the Transferring Shareholder on the terms and conditions and to the Third Party Purchaser set forth in the Notice of Transfer. The Company shall (as agent for the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders) Transfer the number of Shares which the Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders have elected to Transfer to the Third Party Purchaser on the terms set out in the Notice of Transfer. Any proposed Transfer on terms and conditions more favourable than those described in the Notice of Transfer or to a transferee not identified in such notice, as well as any subsequent proposed Transfer of any of the Shares held by the Transferring Shareholder, shall again be subject to the tag-along rights of the other <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders and the transfer restrictions set out in this Agreement and shall require compliance by the Transferring Shareholder with the procedures described in this Clause <xref to="14_no_member_shall_be_entitled_to_receive"></xref> (Tag-Along Rights). The exercise or non-exercise of the rights of a <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder hereunder to participate in one or more sales by a Transferring Shareholder shall not adversely affect such <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder's rights to participate in subsequent sales of Shares by any Shareholder pursuant to this Clause <xref to="14_tag_along_rights"></xref> (Tag-Along Rights).</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.4">Upon consummation of the Transfer of the Shares pursuant to the terms and conditions  specified in the Notice of Transfer, the Transferring Shareholder or the Company, as the case maybe, shall remit to each Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder that portion of the proceeds to which such Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder is entitled by reason of its participation in such Transfer. To the extent that the Third Party Purchaser prohibits such assignment or otherwise refuses to purchase Shares from a Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder exercising its tag-along rights hereunder, the Transferring Shareholder shall not Transfer to the Third Party Purchaser any of its Shares unless and until, simultaneously with such Transfer, the Transferring Shareholder or the Third Party Purchaser shall purchase the Shares from such Tagging <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholder on the same terms and conditions specified in the Notice of Transfer.</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.5">Notwithstanding the foregoing, tag-along rights shall not apply to any Transfer by a Shareholder pursuant to a bona fide loan transaction with a financial institution that creates a mere security interest, and the provisions of Clause <xref to="13.6_it_shall_be_a_condition_precedent_to_the"></xref> shall apply mutatis mutandis.</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.6">Any purported Transfer by a Shareholder in violation of this Agreement shall be null and void and of no force and effect and the purported transferees shall have no rights or privileges in or with respect to the Company or the Shares purported to have been so transferred. The Company shall refuse to recognise any such Transfer and shall not reflect in its records any change in ownership of such Shares purported to have been so Transferred.</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="14.7">The tag-along rights of the <?= data.security_type ?> Shareholders under this Clause <xref to="14_tag_along_rights"></xref> (Tag-Along Rights) shall cease upon the closing of a Qualified IPO or a Trade Sale.</numbered_2_para>

