<? // don't add a data.xml_declaration here because this file is an include, not a standalone template. ?>
<a_left_sidehead xname="ss.coi seriesseed">Series Seed Preferred Stock</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>The Directors may from time to time issue shares of <b>Series Seed Preferred Stock</b> in the capital of the Company, in one or more series, each of such series to consist of such number of shares and to have such terms, rights, powers and preferences, and the qualifications and limitations with respect thereto, as stated or expressed herein.</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead>Definitions</b_left_sidehead>

<para_1>As used in this Section <xref to="ss.coi seriesseed" />, the following terms have the meanings set forth below:</para_1>

<definition_nonum>Board Composition	means for so long as at least 25% percent of the initially issued shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock remain outstanding,</definition_nonum>
<definition_list>the holders of record of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock exclusively and as a separate class, are entitled to elect <?= data.number_directors_seriesseed ?> director(s) of the Company (the "Series Seed Director(s)");</definition_list>
<definition_list>the holders of record of the shares of Common Stock, exclusively and as a separate class, shall be entitled to elect <?= data.number_directors_common ?> director(s) of the Company; and</definition_list>
<definition_list>any additional directors will be elected by the affirmative vote of the majority, within each class, counted on an as-converted basis, of the Series Seed Preferred Stock and Common Stock.</definition_list>
<definition_list>For administrative convenience, the initial Series Seed Director may also be appointed by the Board in connection with the approval of the initial issuance of Series Seed Preferred Stock without a separate action by the holders of a majority of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</definition_list>

<definition_nonum>Original Issue Price	means <?= data.ss_price_per_share || data.price_per_share ?> per share for the Series Seed Preferred Stock.</definition_nonum>

<definition_nonum>Requisite Holders	means the holders of at least a majority of the outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</definition_nonum>

<definition_nonum>Substantial Holder	means a Series Seed Shareholder who holds Ordinary Shares (and/or would hold Ordinary Shares if such Shareholder’s Series Seed Shares were fully converted at the then applicable conversion rate) constituting at least 5% of the then total number of Ordinary Shares issued in the capital of the Company (on a fully diluted and as converted basis at the then applicable conversion rate)</definition_nonum>

<? if (data.auto_conversion) { ?>
<para_1>All shares of any Preferred Stock of the Company are hereby designated "Series Seed Preferred Stock".</para_1>
<? } ?>

<b_left_sidehead>Liquidation</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi preferredholders">Payments to Holders of Preferred Stock. In the event of any voluntary or involuntary liquidation, dissolution, or winding up of the Company or any Deemed Liquidation Event (as defined below), before any payment shall be made to the holders of Common Stock by reason of their ownership thereof, the holders of shares of Preferred Stock then outstanding must be paid out of the funds and assets available for distribution to its stockholders, an amount per share equal to the greater of (a) the Original Issue Price for such share of Preferred Stock, plus any dividends declared but unpaid thereon, or (b) such amount per share as would have been payable had all shares of Preferred Stock been converted into Common Stock pursuant to Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" /> immediately prior to such liquidation, dissolution or winding up or Deemed Liquidation Event.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<para_2>If upon any such liquidation, dissolution, or winding up or Deemed Liquidation Event of the Company, the funds and assets available for distribution to the stockholders of the Company are insufficient to pay the holders of shares of Preferred Stock the full amount to which they are entitled under this Regulation <xref to="ss.coi preferredholders" />, the holders of shares of Preferred Stock will share ratably in any distribution of the funds and assets available for distribution in proportion to the respective amounts that would otherwise be payable in respect of the shares of Preferred Stock held by them upon such distribution if all amounts payable on or with respect to such shares were paid in full.</para_2>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Payments to Holders of Common Stock. In the event of any voluntary or involuntary liquidation, dissolution, or winding up or Deemed Liquidation Event of the Company, after the payment of all preferential amounts required to be paid to the holders of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock as provided in <xref to="ss.coi preferredholders" />, the remaining funds and assets available for distribution to the stockholders of the Company will be distributed among the holders of shares of Common Stock, pro rata based on the number of shares of Common Stock held by each such holder.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<c_left_sidehead xname="ss.coi liquidation">Deemed Liquidation Events</c_left_sidehead>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fl>Definition. Each of the following events is a <b><i>“Deemed Liquidation Event”</i></b> unless the Requisite Holders elect otherwise by written notice received by the Company at least five (5) days prior to the effective date of any such event:</numbered_4_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_5_para_fltab>a merger or consolidation in which (i) the Company is a constituent party or (ii) a subsidiary of the Company is a constituent party and the Company issues shares of its capital stock pursuant to such merger or consolidation, except any such merger or consolidation involving the Company or a subsidiary in which the shares of capital stock of the Company outstanding immediately prior to such merger or consolidation continue to represent, or are converted into or exchanged for equity securities that represent, immediately following such merger or consolidation, at least a majority, by voting power, of the equity securities of (1) the surviving or resulting party or (2) if the surviving or resulting party is a wholly owned subsidiary of another party immediately following such merger or consolidation, the parent of such surviving or resulting party; provided that, for the purpose of this Section, all shares of Common Stock issuable upon exercise of options outstanding immediately prior to such merger or consolidation or upon conversion of Convertible Securities (as defined below) outstanding immediately prior to such merger or consolidation shall be deemed to be outstanding immediately prior to such merger or consolidation and, if applicable, deemed to be converted or exchanged in such merger or consolidation on the same terms as the actual outstanding shares of Common Stock are converted or exchanged; or</numbered_5_para_fltab>

<numbered_5_para_fltab>the sale, lease, transfer, exclusive license or other disposition, in a single transaction or series of related transactions, by the Company or any subsidiary of the Company of all or substantially all the assets of the Company and its subsidiaries taken as a whole, or, if substantially all of the assets of the Company and its subsidiaries taken as a whole are held by such subsidiary or subsidiaries, the sale or disposition (whether by merger or otherwise) of one or more subsidiaries of the Company, except where such sale, lease, transfer or other disposition is to the Company or one or more wholly owned subsidiaries of the Company.</numbered_5_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fl>Amount Deemed Paid or Distributed. The funds and assets deemed paid or distributed to the holders of capital stock of the Company upon any such merger, consolidation, sale, transfer or other disposition described in this Section <xref to="ss.coi liquidation" />will be the cash or the value of the property, rights or securities paid or distributed to such holders by the Company or the acquiring person, firm or other entity. The value of such property, rights or securities shall be determined in good faith by the Board.</numbered_4_firstbold_fl>

<b_left_sidehead>Voting</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>General. On any matter presented to the stockholders of the Company for their action or consideration at any meeting of stockholders of the Company (or by written consent of stockholders in lieu of meeting), each holder of outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock may cast the number of votes equal to the number of whole shares of Common Stock into which the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock held by such holder are convertible as of the record date for determining stockholders entitled to vote on such matter. Fractional votes shall not be permitted and any fractional voting rights available on an as-converted basis (after aggregating all shares into which shares of Preferred stock held by each holder could be converted) will be rounded to the nearest whole number (with one-half being rounded upward). Except as provided by law or by the other provisions of these Regulations, holders of Series Seed Preferred Stock shall vote together with the holders of Common Stock as a single class on an as-converted basis, shall have full voting rights and powers equal to the voting rights and powers of the holders of Common Stock, and shall be entitled, notwithstanding any provision of these Regulations, to notice of any stockholder meeting in accordance with the Bylaws of the Company.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Election of Directors. The holders of record of the Company’s capital stock are entitled to elect directors as defined under Board Composition. Any director elected as provided in the preceding sentence may be removed without cause by the affirmative vote of the holders of the shares of the class, classes, or series of capital stock entitled to elect the director or directors, given either at a special meeting of the stockholders duly called for that purpose or pursuant to a written consent of stockholders. At any meeting held for the purpose of electing a director, the presence in person or by proxy of the holders of a majority of the outstanding shares of the class, classes, or series entitled to elect the director constitutes a quorum for the purpose of electing the director.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi stockprotection">Protective Provisions. At any time when at least 25% of the initially issued shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock remain outstanding, the Company shall not, either directly or indirectly by amendment, merger, consolidation or otherwise, do any of the following without (in addition to any other vote required by law or these Regulations) the written consent or affirmative vote of the Requisite Holders, given in writing or by vote at a meeting, consenting, or voting (as the case may be) separately as a single class:</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>alter the rights, powers or privileges of the Series Seed Preferred Stock set forth in these Regulations in a way that adversely affects the Series Seed Preferred Stock</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>increase or decrease the authorized number of shares of any class or series of capital stock</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>authorize or create (by reclassification or otherwise) any new class or series of capital stock having rights, powers, or privileges set forth in the certificate of incorporation of the Company, as then in effect, that are senior to or on a parity with any series of Series Seed Preferred Stock</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>redeem or repurchase any shares of Common Stock or Series Seed Preferred Stock (other than pursuant to employee or consultant agreements giving the Company the right to repurchase shares upon the termination of services pursuant to the terms of the applicable agreement)</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>declare or pay any dividend or otherwise make a distribution to holders of Series Seed Preferred Stock or Common Stock</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>increase or decrease the number of directors of the Company </numbered_4_para_fltab>

<? if (data.ss_reserved) { ?>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>obtain any loans or incur indebtedness (including the giving of any guarantees)</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>set or change salaries or any remuneration of the Key Holders as defined in the Series Seed Investment Agreement of <?= data.investment_agreement_date ?></numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>agree to remunerate any employee or contractor more than S$5,000 per month</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<? } ?>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>liquidate, dissolve, or wind-up the business and affairs of the Company, effect any Deemed Liquidation Event, or consent, agree or commit to do any of the foregoing without conditioning such consent, agreement or commitment upon obtaining the approval required by this Section <xref to="ss.coi stockprotection" /></numbered_4_para_fltab>

<? if (data.ss_yet_more_protective_provisions) { ?>
<numbered_4_para_fltab><?= data.ss_yet_more_protective_provisions ?></numbered_4_para_fltab>
<? } ?>

<b_left_sidehead xname="ss.coi conversion">Conversion</b_left_sidehead>

<para_1>The holders of the Series Seed Preferred Stock have the following conversion rights (the <b><i>“Conversion Rights”</i></b>):</para_1>

<c_left_sidehead>Right to Convert</c_left_sidehead>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fltab xname="ss.coi conversionratio">Conversion Ratio. Each share of Series Seed Preferred Stock is convertible, at the option of the holder thereof, at any time, and without the payment of additional consideration by the holder thereof, into such number of fully paid and nonassessable shares of Common Stock as is determined by dividing the Original Issue Price for the series of Series Seed Preferred Stock by the Conversion Price for that series of Series Seed Preferred Stock in effect at the time of conversion. The <b><i>"Conversion Price"</i></b> for each series of Series Seed Preferred Stock means the Original Issue Price for such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock, which initial Conversion Price, and the rate at which shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock may be converted into shares of Common Stock, is subject to adjustment as provided in these Regulations.</numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>Termination of Conversion Rights. Subject to Section <xref to="ss.coi conversionnotice" /> in the case of a Contingency Event herein, in the event of a liquidation, dissolution, or winding up of the Company or a Deemed Liquidation Event, the Conversion Rights will terminate at the close of business on the last full day preceding the date fixed for the first payment of any funds and assets distributable on such event to the holders of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi fractional">Fractional Shares. No fractional shares of Common Stock will be issued upon conversion of the Series Seed Preferred Stock. In lieu of any fractional shares to which the holder would otherwise be entitled, the Company shall pay cash equal to such fraction multiplied by the fair market value of a share of Common Stock as determined in good faith by the Board. Whether or not fractional shares would be issuable upon such conversion will be determined on the basis of the total number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock the holder is at the time converting into Common Stock and the aggregate number of shares of Common Stock issuable upon such conversion.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<c_left_sidehead>Mechanics of Conversion.</c_left_sidehead>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fltab xname="ss.coi conversionnotice">Notice of Conversion. To voluntarily convert shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock into shares of Common Stock, a holder of Series Seed Preferred Stock shall surrender the certificate or certificates for the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (or, if such registered holder alleges that any such certificate has been lost, stolen or destroyed, a lost certificate affidavit and agreement reasonably acceptable to the Company to indemnify the Company against any claim that may be made against the Company on account of the alleged loss, theft or destruction of such certificate), at the office of the transfer agent for the Series Seed Preferred Stock (or at the office of the secretary of the Company if the Company serves as its own transfer agent), together with written notice that the holder elects to convert all or any number of the shares of the Series Seed Preferred Stock represented by the certificate or certificates and, if applicable, any event on which the conversion is contingent (a <b><i>“Contingency Event”</i></b>).</numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>

<para_2_indented_66>The conversion notice must state the holder’s name or the names of the nominees in which such holder wishes the certificate or certificates for shares of Common Stock to be issued. If required by the Company, certificates surrendered for conversion shall be endorsed or accompanied by a written instrument or instruments of transfer, in form reasonably satisfactory to the Company, duly executed by the registered holder or such holder’s attorney duly authorized in writing.
The close of business on the date of receipt by the transfer agent (or by the Company if the Company serves as its own transfer agent) of the certificates (or lost certificate affidavit and agreement) and notice (or, if later, the date on which all Contingency Events have occurred) will be the time of conversion (the <b><i>“Conversion Time”</i></b>), and the shares of Common Stock issuable upon conversion of the shares represented by such certificate shall be deemed to be outstanding of record as of such time.
The Company shall, as soon as practicable after the Conversion Time, (a) issue and deliver to the holder, or to the holder’s nominees, a certificate or certificates for the number of full shares of Common Stock issuable upon the conversion in accordance with the provisions of these Regulations and a certificate for the number (if any) of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock represented by the surrendered certificate that were not converted into Common Stock, (b) pay in cash such amount as provided in Section <xref to="ss.coi fractional" /> in lieu of any fraction of a share of Common Stock otherwise issuable upon such conversion and (c) pay all declared but unpaid dividends on the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock converted.</para_2_indented_66>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>Effect of Conversion. All shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock that shall have been surrendered for conversion as provided in these Regulations shall no longer be deemed to be outstanding and all rights with respect to such shares will immediately cease and terminate at the Conversion Time, except only the right of the holders thereof to receive shares of Common Stock in exchange therefor, to receive payment in lieu of any fraction of a share otherwise issuable upon such conversion as provided in Section <xref to="ss.coi fractional" />, and to receive payment of any dividends declared but unpaid thereon. Any shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock so converted shall be retired and cancelled and may not be reissued.</numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>

<numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>No Further Adjustment. Upon any conversion of shares of Pre-ferred Stock, no adjustment to the Conversion Price of the applicable series of Series Seed Preferred Stock will be made with respect to the converted shares for any declared but unpaid dividends on such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock or on the Common Stock delivered upon conversion.</numbered_4_firstbold_fltab>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi stocksplits">Adjustment for Stock Splits and Combinations. If the Company at any time or from time to time after the date on which the first share of a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock is issued by the Company (such date referred to herein as the <b><i>“Original Issue Date”</i></b> for such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock) effects a subdivision of the outstanding Common Stock, the Conversion Price for each series of Series Seed Preferred Stock in effect immediately before that subdivision shall be proportionately decreased so that the number of shares of Common Stock issuable on conversion of each share of that series will be increased in proportion to the increase in the aggregate number of shares of Common Stock outstanding. If the Company at any time or from time to time after the Original Issue Date for a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock combines the outstanding shares of Common Stock, the Conversion Price for each series of Series Seed Preferred Stock in effect immediately before the combination will be proportionately increased so that the number of shares of Common Stock issuable on conversion of each share of such series shall be decreased in proportion to such decrease in the aggregate number of shares of Common Stock outstanding. Any adjustment under this Section <xref to="ss.coi stocksplits" /> becomes effective at the close of business on the date the subdivision or combination becomes effective.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi adjustmentcertain">Adjustment for Certain Dividends and Distributions. If the Company at any time or from time to time after the Original Issue Date for a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock makes or issues, or fixes a record date for the determination of holders of Common Stock entitled to receive, a dividend or other distribution payable on the Common Stock in additional shares of Common Stock, then and in each such event the Conversion Price for such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock in effect immediately before the event will be decreased as of the time of such issuance or, in the event a a record date has been fixed, as of the close of business on such record date, by multiplying such Conversion Price then in effect by a fraction:</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_4_para_fltab>the numerator of which is the total number of shares of Common Stock issued and outstanding immediately prior to the time of the issuance or the close of business on the record date, and</numbered_4_para_fltab>
<numbered_4_para_fltab>the denominator of which is the total number of shares of Common Stock issued and outstanding immediately before the time of such issuance or the close of business on the record date plus the number of shares of Common Stock issuable in payment of such dividend or distribution.</numbered_4_para_fltab>
<para_1>Notwithstanding the foregoing, (i) if such record date has have been fixed and the dividend is not fully paid or if such distribution is not fully made on the date fixed therefor, such Conversion Price shall be recomputed accordingly as of the close of business on such record date and there-after such Conversion Price shall be adjusted pursuant to this Section <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentcertain" /> as of the time of actual payment of such dividends or distributions; and (ii) no such adjustment shall be made if the holders of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock simultaneously receive a dividend or other distribution of shares of Common Stock in a number equal to the number of shares of Common Stock that they would have received if all outstanding shares of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock had been converted into Common Stock on the date of the event.</para_1>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi adjustmentothers">Adjustments for Other Dividends and Distributions. If the Company at any time or from time to time after the Original Issue Date for a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock shall makes or issues, or fixes a record date for the determination of holders of Common Stock entitled to receive, a dividend or other distribution payable in securities of the Company (other than a distribution of shares of Common Stock in respect of outstanding shares of Common Stock), then and in each such event the Company shall make, simultaneously with the distribution to the holders of Common Stock, a dividend or other distribution to the holders of the series of Series Seed Preferred Stock in an amount equal to the amount of securities as the holders would have received if all outstanding shares of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock had been converted into Common Stock on the date of such event.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi adjustmentmisc">Adjustment for Reclassification, Exchange and Substitution. If at any time or from time to time after the Original Issue Date for a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock the Common Stock issuable upon the conversion of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock is changed into the same or a different number of shares of any class or classes of stock of the Company, whether by recapitalization, reclassification, or otherwise (other than by a stock split or combination, dividend, distribution, merger or consolidation covered by Sections <xref to="ss.coi stocksplits" />, <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentcertain" />, <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentothers" /> or <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentmerger" /> or by Section <xref to="ss.coi liquidation" /> regarding a Deemed Liquidation Event), then in any such event each holder of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock may thereafter convert such stock into the kind and amount of stock and other securities and property receivable upon such recapitalization, reclassification or other change by holders of the number of shares of Common Stock into which such shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock could have been converted immediately prior to such recapitalisation, reclassification or change.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Adjustment for Merger or Consolidation. Subject to the provisions of Section <xref to="ss.coi liquidation" />, if any consolidation or merger occurs involving the Company in which the Common Stock (but not a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock) is converted into or exchanged for securities, cash, or other property (other than a transaction covered by Sections <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentcertain" />, <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentothers" /> or <xref to="ss.coi adjustmentmisc" />), then, following any such consolidation or merger, the Company shall provide that each share of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock will thereafter be convertible, in lieu of the Common Stock into which it was convertible prior to the event, into the kind and amount of securities, cash, or other property which a holder of the number of shares of Common Stock of the Company issuable upon conversion of one share of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock immediately prior to the consolidation or merger would have been entitled to receive pursuant to the transaction; and, in such case, the Company shall make appropriate adjustment (as determined in good faith by the Board) in the application of the provisions in this Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" /> with respect to the rights and interests thereafter of the holders of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock, to the end that the provisions set forth in this Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" />(including provisions with respect to changes in and other adjustments of the Conversion Price of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock) shall thereafter be applicable, as nearly as reasonably may be, in relation to any securities or other property thereafter deliverable upon the conversion of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Certificate as to Adjustments. Upon the occurrence of each adjustment or readjustment of the Conversion Price of a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock pursuant to this Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" />, the Company at its expense shall, as promptly as reasonably practicable but in any event not later than 15 days thereafter, compute such adjustment or readjustment in accordance with the terms of these Regulations and furnish to each holder of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock a certificate setting forth the adjustment or readjustment (including the kind and amount of securities, cash, or other property into which such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock is convertible) and showing in detail the facts upon which such adjustment or readjustment is based. The Company shall, as promptly as reasonably practicable after the written request at any time of any holder of any series of Series Seed Preferred Stock (but in any event not later than 10 days thereafter), furnish or cause to be furnished to such holder a certificate setting forth (a) the Conversion Price of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock then in effect and (b) the number of shares of Common Stock and the amount, if any, of other securities, cash, or property which then would be received upon the conversion of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi mandatory">Mandatory Conversion. Upon either (a) the closing of the sale of shares of Common Stock to the public in a firm-commitment underwritten public offering pursuant to a prospectus filed under the Securities and Futures Act or (b) the date and time, or the occurrence of an event, specified by vote or written consent of the Requisite Holders at the time of such vote or consent, voting as a single class on an as-converted basis (the time of such closing or the date and time specified or the time of the event specified in such vote or written consent,the <b><i>“Mandatory Conversion Time”</i></b>), (i) all outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock will automatically convert into shares of Common Stock, at the applicable ratio described in Section <xref to="ss.coi conversionratio" /> as the same may be adjusted from time to time in accordance with Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" /> and (ii) such shares may not be reissued by the Company.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss.coi procedural">Procedural Requirements. The Company shall notify in writing all holders of record of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock of the Mandatory Conversion Time and the place designated for mandatory conversion of all such shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock pursuant to Section <xref to="ss.coi mandatory" />.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<para_2>Unless otherwise provided in these Regulations, the notice need not be sent in advance of the occurrence of the Mandatory Conversion Time.
Upon receipt of the notice, each holder of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock shall surrender such holder’s certificate or certificates for all such shares (or, if such holder alleges that such certificate has been lost, stolen or destroyed, a lost certificate affidavit and agreement reasonably acceptable to the Company to indemnify the Company against any claim that may be made against the Company on account of the alleged loss, theft or destruction of such certificate) to the Company at the place designated in such notice, and shall thereafter receive certificates for the number of shares of Common Stock to which such holder is entitled pursuant to this Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" />.
If so required by the Company, certificates surrendered for conversion shall be endorsed or accompanied by written instrument or instruments of transfer, in form reasonably satisfactory to the Company, duly executed by the registered holder or such holder’s attorney duly authorized in writing.
All rights with respect to the Series Seed Preferred Stock converted pursuant to Section <xref to="ss.coi mandatory" />, including the rights, if any, to receive notices and vote (other than as a holder of Common Stock), will terminate at the Mandatory Conversion Time (notwithstanding the failure of the holder or holders thereof to surrender the certificates at or prior to such time), except only the rights of the holders thereof, upon surrender of their certificate or certificates (or lost certificate affidavit and agreement) therefor, to receive the items provided for in the next sentence of this Section <xref to="ss.coi procedural" />.
As soon as practicable after the Mandatory Conversion Time and the surrender of the certificate or certificates (or lost certificate affidavit and agreement) for Series Seed Preferred Stock, the Company shall issue and deliver to such holder, or to such holder’s nominee(s), a certificate or certificates for the number of full shares of Common Stock issuable on such conversion in accordance with the provisions hereof, together with cash as provided in Section <xref to="ss.coi fractional" />in lieu of any fraction of a share of Common Stock otherwise issuable upon such conversion and the payment of any declared but unpaid dividends on the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock converted.
Such converted Series Seed Preferred Stock shall be retired and cancelled and may not be reissued as shares of such series, and the Company may thereafter take such appropriate action (without the need for stockholder action) as may be necessary to reduce the authorized number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (and the applicable series thereof) accordingly.</para_2>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Dividends. The Company shall declare all dividends pro rata on the Common Stock and the Series Seed Preferred Stock on a pari passu basis according to the number of as-converted shares of Common Stock held by such holders. For this purpose each holder of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock will be treated as holding the greatest whole number of shares of Common Stock then issuable upon conversion of all shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock held by such holder pursuant to Section <xref to="ss.coi conversion" />.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Redeemed or Otherwise Acquired Shares. Any shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock that are redeemed or otherwise acquired by the Company or any of its subsidiaries will be automatically and immediately cancelled and retired and shall not be reissued, sold or transferred. Neither the Company nor any of its subsidiaries may exercise any voting or other rights granted to the holders of Series Seed Preferred Stock following any such redemption.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Waiver. Any of the rights, powers, privileges and other terms of the Series Seed Preferred Stock set forth herein may be waived prospectively or retrospectively on behalf of all holders of Series Seed Preferred Stock by the affirmative written consent or vote of the holders of the Requisite Holders.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Notice of Record Date. In the event:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>the Company takes a record of the holders of its Common Stock (or other capital stock or securities at the time issuable upon conversion of the Series Seed Preferred Stock) for the purpose of entitling or enabling them to receive any dividend or other distribution, or to receive any right to subscribe for or purchase any shares of capital stock of any class or any other securities, or to receive any other security; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>of any capital reorganization of the Company, any reclassification of the Common Stock of the Company, or any Deemed Liquidation Event; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>of the voluntary or involuntary dissolution, liquidation or winding-up of the Company,</numbered_3_para>
<para_1>then, and in each such case, the Company shall send or cause to be sent to the holders of the Series Seed Preferred Stock a written notice specifying, as the case may be, (i) the record date for such dividend, distribution, or right, and the amount and character of such dividend, distribution or right, or (ii) the effective date on which such reorganization, reclassification, consolidation, merger, transfer, dissolution, liquidation or winding-up is proposed to take place, and the time, if any is to be fixed, as of which the holders of record of Common Stock (or such other capital stock or securities at the time issuable upon the conversion of the Series Seed Preferred Stock) will be entitled to exchange their shares of Common Stock (or such other capital stock or securities) for securities or other property deliverable upon such reorganization, reclassification, consolidation, merger, transfer, dissolution, liquidation or winding-up, and the amount per share and character of such exchange applicable to the Series Seed Preferred Stock and the Common Stock. The Company shall send the notice at least 20 days before the earlier of the record date or effective date for the event specified in the notice.</para_1>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Notices. Except as otherwise provided herein, any notice required or permitted by the provisions of this Section <xref to="ss.coi seriesseed" /> to be given to a holder of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock must be mailed, postage prepaid, to the post office address last shown on the records of the Company, or given by electronic communication, and will be deemed sent upon such mailing or electronic transmission.</numbered_2_firstbold>

<? if (data.preemptive_rights_for_new_issues == false) { ?>
<b_left_sidehead>Preemptive Rights</b_left_sidehead>
<numbered_3_para_fl>No stockholder of the Company has a right to purchase shares of capital stock of the Company sold or issued by the Company except to the extent that such a right may from time to time be set forth in a written agreement between the Company and the stockholder.</numbered_3_para_fl>
<? } ?>

