<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"Series Seed Investment Agreement", rcpts_to:rcpts_to}) ?>
<Story_Main>
<chapter_header>Series Seed Preferred Stock Investment Agreement</chapter_header>
<para_1>This Series Seed Preferred Stock Investment Agreement (this "Agreement") is dated as of the Agreement Date and is between the Company, the Purchasers and the Key Holders:</para_1>

<?!= include("inc_enumerate_parties", data, rcpts_to, { term:{"new_investor": "purchaser"} }) ?>

<para_1>The parties agree as follows:</para_1>
<numbered_1_firstbold>Definitions. Capitalized terms used and not otherwise defined in this Agreement or the Exhibit and Schedules thereto have the meanings set forth in Exhibit A.</numbered_1_firstbold>
<numbered_1_firstbold>Investment. Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, including the Agreement Terms set forth in Exhibit B, (i) each Purchaser shall purchase at the applicable Closing and the Company shall sell and issue to each Purchaser at such Closing that number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock set forth opposite such Purchaser's name on Schedule 1, at a price per share equal to the Purchase Price (subject to any applicable discounts when all or a portion of such Purchase Price is being paid by cancellation of indebtedness of the Company to such Purchaser) and (ii) each Purchaser, the Company, and each Key Holder agrees to be bound by the obligations set forth in this Agreement and to grant to the other parties hereto the rights set forth in this Agreement.</numbered_1_firstbold>
<numbered_1_firstbold>Entire Agreement. This Agreement (including the Exhibits and Schedules hereto), together with the Amended Constitution and the Shareholders' Agreement, constitute the full and entire understanding and agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof, and any other written or oral agreement relating to the subject matter hereof existing between the parties is expressly canceled.</numbered_1_firstbold>

<para_1><span_smallcaps>S$</span_smallcaps> or $	means the lawful currency for the time being of the Republic of Singapore.</para_1>
<para_2>Except where the context otherwise requires, words importing the singular include the plural and vice versa, words importing a gender include every gender and references to persons include bodies corporate or unincorporated, any state or any agency thereof and any other entity.
Headings, marginal sidenotes, and graphic art are for ease of reference only and have no legal effect. Reference to Sections are to Sections of this Agreement and references to this Agreement include any amendments or supplementals thereto.
Except where the context otherwise requires, references to any person include its successors and permitted assignees. Except where the context otherwise requires, Sections which refer to the "Company" shall apply mutatis mutandis to subsidiaries or successors of the Company which may from time to time be established.
References in this Agreement to a time of day are to Singapore time.
This Agreement shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore.</para_2>

<centered>[Remainder of Page Intentionally Left Blank]</centered>


<chapter_header>EXHIBIT A: DEFINITIONS</chapter_header>

<a_left_sidehead restart="true">OVERVIEW DEFINITIONS.</a_left_sidehead>
<para_2_hanging>"Agreement Date" means <?= data.investment_agreement_date ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Company" means <?= data.company.name ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Governing Law" means the laws of <?= data.jurisdiction ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Dispute Resolution Jurisdiction" means the courts of <?= data.jurisdiction ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"State of Incorporation" means <?= data.jurisdiction ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Stock Plan" means <?= data.stock_plan ?>.</para_2_hanging>

<a_left_sidehead>BOARD COMPOSITION DEFINITIONS.</a_left_sidehead>
<para_2_hanging>"Common Board Member Count" means <?= data.number_directors_common ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Mutual Consent Board Member Count" means <?= data.number_directors_jointly ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Series Seed Board Member Count" means <?= data.number_directors_seriesseed ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Common Control Holders" means the Key Holders who are then providing services to the company as employees or as volunteers.</para_2_hanging>

<a_left_sidehead>TERM SHEET DEFINITIONS.</a_left_sidehead>
<para_2_hanging>"Purchase Price" means <?= data.price_per_share ?> per share (subject to any discounts applicable where all or a portion of such Purchase Price is being paid by cancellation of indebtedness of the Company to such Purchaser).</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Total Series Seed Investment Amount" means $<?= data.amount_raising ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Unallocated Post-Money Option Pool Percent"</b> means <?= data.capTable.getRound("TOTAL").new_investors.ESOP.percentage ?>%.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Purchaser Counsel Reimbursement Amount" means $<?= data.purchaser_counsel_reimbursement_amount ?>.</para_2_hanging>

<a_left_sidehead>RESULTING CAP TABLE DEFINITIONS.</a_left_sidehead>
<? var activeRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound(); ?>
<? var previousRound = activeRound.getPreviousRound(); ?>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Common Shares Issued and Outstanding Pre-Money"</b> means <?= digitCommas_(activeRound.by_security_type["Ordinary Shares"].TOTAL) ?> shares.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Series Seed Shares Issued and Outstanding Pre-Money"</b> means <?= digitCommas_(previousRound.by_security_type["Series Seed Shares"].TOTAL) ?> shares.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Class F Shares Issued and Outstanding"</b> means <?= digitCommas_(activeRound.by_security_type["Class F Shares"].TOTAL) ?> shares.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Total Post-Money Shares Reserved for Option Pool"</b> means <?= digitCommas_(data.capTable.getRound("TOTAL").ESOP.reserved()) ?> shares.</para_2_hanging>
<para_2_hanging>"Number of Issued And Outstanding Options" means <?= data.issued_and_outstanding_options ?>.</para_2_hanging>
<? // TODO: this needs to be fixed -- we need more sophistication in tracking the allocation and issue of ESOP shares. see https://github.com/legalese-io/legalese-io.github.io/issues/77 ?>
<para_2_hanging><b>"Unallocated Post-Money Option Pool Shares"</b> means <?= digitCommas_(data.capTable.getRound("TOTAL").ESOP.reserved()) ?> shares.</para_2_hanging>
<para_1>
</para_1>
<centered></centered>
<centered></centered>
<centered>[Remainder of Page Intentionally Left Blank]</centered>
<centered>
</centered>



<chapter_header>Schedule 1: Purchasers &amp; Key Holders</chapter_header>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Purchasers</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<? var newIssues = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getNewIssues(); ?>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="3" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(newIssues.holders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>New Issues</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Consideration</cell_c></Cell>

<? for (var hh in newIssues.holders) { with(data._entitiesByName[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= hh ?>

<?= address ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!= data.capTable.getActiveRound().new_investors[hh]._inWords ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= data.capTable.getActiveRound().new_investors[hh].money ?></cell_c></Cell>
<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Key Holders and Vesting Schedules</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<? var activeRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound(); ?>
<? for (var bstk in activeRound.by_security_type) { var bstv = activeRound.by_security_type[bstk]; ?>
<?   Logger.log("keyHolders: round=%s, by_security_type:%s has keys keys %s", activeRound.name, bstk, bstv); ?>
<? } ?>
<? var keyHolders  = data.parties.key_holder ?>
<? var previousRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getPreviousRound(); ?>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="8" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(keyHolders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Shares</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Vesting Commencement</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Vesting Class</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Currently Vested</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Currently Restricted</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Cliff Date</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Acceleration</cell_c></Cell>

<? for (var hh in keyHolders) {
  Logger.log("keyHolders: outputting based on data.parties.key_holder[%s] = %s", hh, keyHolders[hh].name);
  with(keyHolders[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= name ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!= data.capTable.investorHoldingsInRound(name, previousRound) ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="70" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_commencement ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c>Class F Shares</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_unrestricted_current ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_restricted_current ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="50" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= f_cliff_end_date ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="60" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= acceleration ?></cell_c></Cell>

<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>




<chapter_header>Exhibit B: Agreement Terms</chapter_header>

<a_left_sidehead xname="ssia_purchase" restart="true">Purchase and Sale of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</a_left_sidehead>

<b_left_sidehead>Conditions Precedent.</b_left_sidehead>

<para_1>The obligations of the parties under this agreement are subject to the following condition precedent being fulfilled or waived:</para_1>

<numbered_3_para>The Company shall adopt and file with the relevant government authority the Company's restated constitutional documents in substantially the form of Exhibit C attached to this Agreement (the "Amended Constitution").</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>The Company's shareholders give their approval for the issuance of the Series Seed Preference Shares and issuance of Ordinary Shares pursuant to conversion of the Series Seed Preference Shares.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_3_para>The Company notifies its existing members and note-holders of their pre-emption rights, and receives all waivers necessary.</numbered_3_para>

<b_left_sidehead>Sale and Issuance of Series Seed Preferred Stock</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>Each investor listed as a "Purchaser" on Schedule 1 (each, a "Purchaser") shall purchase at the applicable Closing and the Company agrees to sell and issue to each Purchaser at such Closing that number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock of the Company ("Series Seed Preferred Stock") set forth opposite such Purchaser's name on Schedule 1, at a purchase price per share equal to the Purchase Price.</numbered_3_para_fl>

<b_left_sidehead>Closing; Delivery.</b_left_sidehead>
<numbered_3_para_fl>The initial purchase and sale of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock hereunder shall take place remotely via the exchange of documents and signatures on the Agreement Date or the subsequent date on which one or more Purchasers execute counterpart signature pages to this Agreement (which date is referred to herein as the "Effective Date").</numbered_3_para_fl>

<numbered_3_para_fl>Each Purchaser shall within 10 business days of the Effective Date deliver the Purchase Price to the Company. The "Initial Closing" means the date on which all due payments have been received from the Purchasers, by check payable to the Company, by wire transfer to a bank account designated by the Company, by cancellation or conversion of indebtedness of the Company to Purchaser or by any combination of such methods.</numbered_3_para_fl>

<? if (! data.no_additional_closings) { ?>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss_additional_closing_period">Additional Closings. At any time and from time to time during the ninety (90) day period immediately following the Initial Closing (the "Additional Closing Period"), the Company may, at one or more additional closings (each an <b>"Additional Closing"</b> and together with the Initial Closing, each, a "Closing"), without obtaining the signature, consent or permission of any of the Purchasers in the Initial Closing or any prior Additional Closing, offer and sell to other investors (the "New Purchasers"), at a per share purchase price equal to the Purchase Price, up to that number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock that is equal to that number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock equal to the quotient of (x) Total Series Seed Investment Amount divided by (y) the Purchase Price, rounded up to the next whole share (the "Total Shares Authorized for Sale") less the number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock actually issued and sold by the Company at the Initial Closing and any prior Additional Closings. New Purchasers may include persons or entities who are already Purchasers under this Agreement. The Company and each of the New Purchasers purchasing shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock at each Additional Closing will execute counterpart signature pages to this Agreement and each New Purchaser will, upon delivery by such New Purchaser and acceptance by the Company of such New Purchaser's signature page and delivery of the Purchase Price by such New Purchaser to the Company, become a party to, and bound by, this Agreement to the same extent as if such New Purchaser had been a Purchaser at the Initial Closing and each such New Purchaser shall be deemed to be a Purchaser for all purposes under this Agreement as of the date of the applicable Additional Closing.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<? } ?>

<numbered_3_para_fl><? if (data.from_closing_to_certificate == "immediately") {?>At<?} else {?>Promptly following<?}?>  <?if(data.no_additional_closings){?>the Initial<?}else{?>each<?}?> Closing, if required by the Company's governing documents, the Company shall deliver to each Purchaser participating in such Closing:</numbered_3_para_fl>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>a certificate representing the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock being purchased by such Purchaser; and</numbered_4_para_fltab>
<numbered_4_para_fltab>evidence that the electronic register of members maintained by the appropriate government body has been updated to reflect the issuance of the Series Seed Preferred Shares to the Purchaser.</numbered_4_para_fltab>




<a_left_sidehead xname="ssia_rw_coy">Representations and Warranties of the Company.</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>The Company<?
if (data.warrants_by_key_holders_also){?> and each Key Holder, severally and not jointly,<?}
?> hereby represents and warrants to each Purchaser that, except as set forth on the Disclosure Schedule attached as Exhibit D to this Agreement (the "Disclosure Schedule"), if any, which exceptions shall be deemed to be part of the representations and warranties made hereunder, the following representations are true and complete as of the date of the Agreement Date, except as otherwise indicated.</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead>Organization, Good Standing, Corporate Power and Qualification.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company is a corporation duly organized, validly existing and in good standing under the laws of the State of Incorporation and has all corporate power and corporate authority required (a) to carry on its business as presently conducted and as presently proposed to be conducted and (b) to execute, deliver and perform its obligations under this Agreement. The Company is duly qualified to transact business as a foreign corporation and is in good standing under the laws of each jurisdiction in which the failure to so qualify or be in good standing would have a material adverse effect on the business, assets (including intangible assets), liabilities, financial condition, property, or results of operations of the Company.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Capitalization.</b_left_sidehead>
<numbered_3_para_fl>The authorized capital of the Company consists, immediately prior to the Agreement Date (unless otherwise noted), of the following:</numbered_3_para_fl>
<numbered_4_para_fltab>The common stock of the Company (the "Common Stock"), of which that number of shares of Common Stock equal to (a) the Common Shares Issued and Outstanding Pre-Money are issued and outstanding as of immediately prior to the Agreement Date, (b) the number of shares of Common Stock which are issuable on conversion of shares of the Series Seed Preferred Stock have been reserved for issuance upon conversion of the Series Seed Preferred Stock and (c) the Total Post-Money Shares Reserved for Option Pool have been reserved for issuance pursuant to the Stock Plan, and of such Total Post-Money Shares Reserved for Option Pool, that number of shares of Common Stock equal to the Number of Issued And Outstanding Options are currently subject to outstanding options and that number of shares of Common Stock equal to the Unallocated Post-Money Option Pool Shares remain available for future issuance to officers, directors, employees, volunteers, and consultants pursuant to the Stock Plan. The ratio determined by dividing (x) the Unallocated Post-Money Option Pool Shares by (y) the Fully-Diluted Share Number (as defined below) is equal to the Unallocated Post-Money Option Pool Percent. All of the outstanding shares of Common Stock are duly authorized, validly issued, fully paid and nonassessable and were issued in material compliance with all applicable securities laws. The Stock Plan has been duly adopted by the Board of Directors of the Company (the "Board") and approved by the Company's stockholders. For purposes of this Agreement, the term "Fully-Diluted Share Number" shall mean that number of shares of the Company's capital stock equal to the sum of (i) all shares of the Company's capital stock (on an as-converted basis) issued and outstanding, assuming exercise or conversion of all options, warrants and other convertible securities and (ii) all shares of the Company's capital stock reserved and available for future grant under any equity incentive or similar plan.</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>The Class F Preferred Stock of the Company (the "Class F Shares"), of which, immediately prior to the Effective Date of this agreement, there will be <?= digitCommas_(activeRound.by_security_type["Class F Shares"].TOTAL) ?> shares.</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_4_para_fltab>The Series Seed Preferred Stock of the Company (the "Preferred Stock"), <?
if (previousRound.by_security_type["Series Seed Shares"].TOTAL == 0) {?>
none of which is issued and outstanding immediately prior to the Agreement Date
<? } else { ?>
of which, immediately prior to the Effective Date of this agreement, there will be <?= digitCommas_(previousRound.by_security_type["Series Seed Shares"].TOTAL) ?> shares.<?}?>
</numbered_4_para_fltab>

<numbered_3_para_fl>There are no outstanding preemptive rights, options, warrants, conversion privileges or rights (including but not limited to rights of first refusal or similar rights), orally or in writing, to purchase or acquire any securities from the Company including, without limitation, any shares of Common Stock, or Preferred Stock, or any securities convertible into or exchangeable or exercisable for shares of Common Stock or Preferred Stock, except for the conversion privileges of the Series Seed Preferred Stock pursuant to the terms of the Amended Constitution.</numbered_3_para_fl>
<numbered_3_para_fl>The Key Holders set forth in Schedule 1 (each a "Key Holder") hold that number of shares of the Company's stock set forth opposite each such Key Holder's name in Schedule 1 (such shares, the "Key Holders' Shares"), some or all of which may be subject to vesting and/or the Company's repurchase right on the terms specified in Schedule 1 (the "Key Holders' Vesting Schedules"). Except as specified in Schedule 1, the Key Holders do not own or have any other rights to any other securities of the Company.</numbered_3_para_fl>
<para_2>The Key Holders' Vesting Schedules specify for each Key Holder (i) the vesting commencement date for each issuance of shares to or options held by such Key Holder, (ii) the number of shares or options held by such Key Holder that are currently vested, (iii) the number of shares or options held by such Key Holder that remain subject to vesting and/or the Company's repurchase right and (iv) the terms and conditions, if any, under which the Key Holders' Vesting Schedules would be accelerated.</para_2>
<? if (false) { // pending https://github.com/seriesseed/equity/issues/40 ?>
<para_2>Other than the Key Holders' Shares, which vest pursuant to the applicable Key Holders' Vesting Schedules,</para_2>
<numbered_4_para_fltab>all options granted and other Stock outstanding vest as follows: twenty-five percent (25%) of the shares vest one (1) year following the vesting commencement date, with the remaining seventy-five percent (75%) vesting in equal installments over the next three (3) years and
no stock plan, stock purchase, stock option or other agreement or understanding between the Company and any holder of any equity securities or rights to purchase equity securities provides for acceleration or other changes in the vesting provisions or other terms of such agreement or understanding as the result of (i) termination of employment (whether actual or constructive), (ii) any merger, consolidated sale of stock or assets, change in control or any other transaction(s) by the Company, or (iii) the occurrence of any other event or combination of events.</numbered_4_para_fltab>
<? } ?>

<b_left_sidehead>Subsidiaries.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company does not currently own or control, directly or indirectly, any interest in any other corporation, partnership, trust, joint venture, limited liability company, association, or other business entity. The Company is not a participant in any joint venture, partnership or similar arrangement.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Authorization.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>All corporate action has been taken, or will be taken prior to the applicable Closing, on the part of the Board and stockholders that is necessary for the authorization, execution and delivery of this Agreement by the Company and the performance by the Company of the obligations to be performed by the Company as of the date hereof under this Agreement. This Agreement, when executed and delivered by the Company, shall constitute the valid and legally binding obligation of the Company, enforceable against the Company in accordance with its terms except (a) as limited by applicable bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, moratorium, fraudulent conveyance, or other laws of general application relating to or affecting the enforcement of creditors' rights generally, or (b) as limited by laws relating to the availability of specific performance, injunctive relief, or other equitable remedies.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Valid Issuance of Shares.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, when issued, sold and delivered in accordance with the terms and for the consideration set forth in this Agreement, will be duly authorized, validly issued, fully paid and nonassessable and free of restrictions on transfer other than restrictions on transfer under this Agreement, applicable laws and liens or encumbrances created by or imposed by a Purchaser. Based in part on the accuracy of the representations of the Purchasers in Section <xref to="ssia_rw_p"/> of this Agreement and subject to filings pursuant to the Companies Act, as amended (the "Companies Act"), the offer, sale and issuance of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock to be issued pursuant to and in conformity with the terms of this Agreement and the issuance of the Common Stock, if any, to be issued upon conversion thereof for no additional consideration and pursuant to the Amended Constitution, will be issued in compliance with all applicable securities laws. The Common Stock issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock has been duly reserved for issuance, and upon issuance in accordance with the terms of the Amended Constitution, will be duly authorized, validly issued, fully paid and nonassessable and free of restrictions on transfer other than restrictions on transfer under this Agreement, applicable laws and liens or encumbrances created by or imposed by a Purchaser. Based in part upon the representations of the Purchasers in Section <xref to="ssia_rw_p"/> of this Agreement, the Common Stock issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock will be issued in compliance with all applicable laws.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Litigation.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>There is no pending action, suit, proceeding, arbitration, mediation, complaint, claim, charge or investigation before any court, arbitrator, mediator or governmental body or, to the Company's knowledge, currently threatened in writing (a) by or against the Company or (b) by or against any consultant, officer, director or key employee of the Company arising out of his or her consulting, employment or board relationship with the Company or that could otherwise materially impact the Company.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Intellectual Property.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company owns or possesses sufficient legal rights to all Intellectual Property (as defined below) that is necessary to the conduct of the Company's business as now conducted and as presently proposed to be conducted (the "Company Intellectual Property") without any violation or infringement (or in the case of third-party patents, patent applications, trademarks, trademark applications, service marks, or service mark applications, without any violation or infringement known to the Company) of the rights of others. No product or service marketed or sold (or proposed to be marketed or sold) by the Company violates or will violate any license or infringes or will infringe any rights to any patents, patent applications, trademarks, trademark applications, service marks, trade names, copyrights, trade secrets, licenses, domain names, mask works, information and proprietary rights and processes (collectively, "Intellectual Property") of any other party, except that with respect to third-party patents, patent applications, trademarks, trademark applications, service marks, or service mark applications the foregoing representation is made to the best knowledge (after due inquiry) of the Company and each Key Holder only. Other than with respect to commercially available software products under standard end-user object code license agreements, there is no outstanding option, license, agreement, claim, encumbrance or shared ownership interest of any kind relating to the Company Intellectual Property, nor is the Company bound by or a party to any options, licenses or agreements of any kind with respect to the Intellectual Property of any other person. The Company has not received any written communications alleging that the Company has violated or, by conducting its business, would violate any of the Intellectual Property of any other person.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Employee and Consultant Matters.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>Each current and former employee, volunteer, consultant and officer of the Company has executed an agreement with the Company regarding confidentiality, proprietary information, Intellectual Property and non-competition substantially in the form or forms made available to the Purchasers or delivered to the counsel for the Purchasers. No current or former employee, volunteer, or consultant has excluded any work or invention from his or her assignment of inventions and Intellectual Property. To the Company's and each Key Holder's best knowledge (after due inquiry), no such employee, volunteer, or consultant is in violation thereof. To the Company's and each Key Holder's best knowledge (after due inquiry), none of its employees, officers, or volunteers is obligated under any judgment, decree, contract, covenant or agreement that would materially interfere with such employee's ability to promote the interest of the Company or that would interfere with such employee's ability to promote the interests of the Company or that would conflict with the Company's business.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Compliance with Other Instruments.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company is not in violation or default (a) of any provisions of the Amended Constitution, (b) of any judgment, order, writ or decree of any court or governmental entity, (c) under any agreement, instrument, contract, lease, note, indenture, mortgage or purchase order to which it is a party that is required to be listed on the Disclosure Schedule, or, (d) to its knowledge, of any provision of statute, rule or regulation materially applicable to the Company. The execution, delivery and performance of this Agreement and the consummation of the transactions contemplated by this Agreement will not result in any such violation or default, or constitute, with or without the passage of time and giving of notice, either (i) a default under any such judgment, order, writ, decree, agreement, instrument, contract, lease, note, indenture, mortgage or purchase order or (ii) an event which results in the creation of any lien, charge or encumbrance upon any assets of the Company or the suspension, revocation, forfeiture, or nonrenewal of any material permit or license applicable to the Company.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Title to Property and Assets.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company owns its properties and assets free and clear of all mortgages, deeds of trust, liens, encumbrances and security interests except for statutory liens for the payment of current taxes that are not yet delinquent and liens, encumbrances and security interests which arise in the ordinary course of business and which do not affect material properties and assets of the Company. With respect to the property and assets it leases, the Company is in material compliance with each such lease.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Agreements.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>Except for this Agreement, there are no agreements, understandings, instruments, contracts or proposed transactions to which the Company is a party that involve (a) obligations (contingent or otherwise) of, or payments to, the Company in excess of $50,000, (b) the license of any Intellectual Property to or from the Company other than licenses with respect to commercially available software products under standard end-user object code license agreements or standard customer terms of service and privacy policies for Internet sites, (c) the grant of rights to manufacture, produce, assemble, license, market, or sell its products to any other person, or that limit the Company's exclusive right to develop, manufacture, assemble, distribute, market or sell its products, or (d) indemnification by the Company with respect to infringements of proprietary rights other than standard customer or channel agreements (each, a "Material Agreement"). The Company is not in material breach of any Material Agreement. Each Material Agreement is in full force and effect and is enforceable by the Company in accordance with its respective terms, except as may be limited by (i) applicable bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization or others laws of general application relating to or affecting the enforcement of creditors' rights generally, or (ii) the effect of rules of law governing the availability of equitable remedies.</numbered_3_para_fl>


<b_left_sidehead>Liabilities.</b_left_sidehead>

<numbered_3_para_fl>The Company has no liabilities or obligations, contingent or otherwise, in excess of $25,000 individually or $100,000 in the aggregate.</numbered_3_para_fl>



<a_left_sidehead xname="ssia_rw_p">Representations and Warranties and Covenants of the Purchasers.</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>Each Purchaser hereby represents and warrants to the Company, severally and not jointly, as follows.</para_1>

<numbered_2_firstbold>Authorization. The Purchaser has full power and authority to enter into this Agreement. This Agreement, when executed and delivered by the Purchaser, will constitute a valid and legally binding obligation of the Purchaser, enforceable in accordance with their terms, except (a) as limited by applicable bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, moratorium, fraudulent conveyance, and any other laws of general application relating to or affecting the enforcement of creditors' rights generally, or (b) the effect of rules of law governing the availability of equitable remedies.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Purchase Entirely for Own Account. This Agreement is made with the Purchaser in reliance upon the Purchaser's representation to the Company, which by the Purchaser's execution of this Agreement, the Purchaser hereby confirms, that the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock to be acquired by the Purchaser will be acquired for investment for the Purchaser's own account, not as a nominee or agent, and not with a view to the resale or distribution of any part thereof, and that the Purchaser has no present intention of selling, granting any participation in, or otherwise distributing the same. By executing this Agreement, the Purchaser further represents that the Purchaser does not presently have any contract, undertaking, agreement or arrangement with any person to sell, transfer or grant participations to such person or to any third person, with respect to any of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock. The Purchaser has not been formed for the specific purpose of acquiring the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Disclosure of Information. The Purchaser has had an opportunity to discuss the Company's business, management, financial affairs and the terms and conditions of the offering of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock with the Company's management. Nothing in this Section <xref to="ssia_rw_p"/>, including the foregoing sentence, limits or modifies the representations and warranties of the Company in Section <xref to="ssia_rw_coy"/> of this Agreement or the right of the Purchasers to rely thereon.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Restricted Securities. The Purchaser understands that the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock have not been, and will not be, registered under the Securities and Futures Act (the "Securities Act"), by reason of a specific exemption from the registration provisions of the Securities Act which depends upon, among other things, the bona fide nature of the investment intent and the accuracy of the Purchaser's representations as expressed herein. The Purchaser understands that the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock are "restricted securities", that the transfer of restricted securities is limited by law and by the Amended Constitution, and that the Purchaser must be prepared to hold the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock indefinitely, or until the Company is acquired or goes public. The Purchaser acknowledges that the Company has no obligation to register or qualify the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, or the Common Stock into which it may be converted, for resale. The Purchaser further acknowledges that if an exemption from registration or qualification is available, it may be conditioned on various requirements including, but not limited to, the time and manner of sale, the holding period for the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, and on requirements relating to the Company which are outside of the Purchaser's control, and which the Company is under no obligation and may not be able to satisfy.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>No Public Market. The Purchaser understands that no public market now exists for the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, and that the Company has made no assurances that a public market will ever exist for the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Legends. The Purchaser understands that the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock and any securities issued in respect of or exchange for the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, may bear any one or more of the following legends: (a) any legend set forth in, or required by, this Agreement; (b) any legend required by the securities laws of any state to the extent such laws are applicable to the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock represented by the certificate so legended; and (c) the following legend:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<indented_3_para>"THE SHARES REPRESENTED BY THIS CERTIFICATE HAVE BEEN ACQUIRED FOR INVESTMENT AND NOT WITH A VIEW TO, OR IN CONNECTION WITH, THE SALE OR DISTRIBUTION THEREOF.<? if (! data.shorter_legend) { ?>  NO TRANSFER MAY BE EFFECTED WITHOUT A PROSPECTUS BEING LODGED WITH THE MONETARY AUTHORITY OF SINGAPORE, OR AN OPINION OF COUNSEL IN A FORM REASONABLY SATISFACTORY TO THE COMPANY THAT SUCH LODGMENT IS NOT REQUIRED.<? } ?>"</indented_3_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Accredited and Sophisticated Purchaser. The Purchaser is an accredited investor as defined in Section 4A of the Securities Act. The Purchaser is an investor in securities of companies in the development stage and acknowledges that Purchaser is able to fend for itself, can bear the economic risk of its investment, and has such knowledge and experience in financial or business matters that it is capable of evaluating the merits and risks of the investment in the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock. If other than an individual, Purchaser also represents it has not been organized for the purpose of acquiring the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>No General Solicitation. Neither the Purchaser nor any of its officers, directors, employees, volunteers, agents, stockholders or partners has either directly or indirectly, including through a broker or finder (a) engaged in any general solicitation with respect to the offer and sale of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, or (b) published any advertisement in connection with the offer and sale of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Exculpation Among Purchasers. The Purchaser acknowledges that it is not relying upon any person, other than the Company and its officers and directors, in making its investment or decision to invest in the Company. The Purchaser agrees that neither any Purchaser nor the respective controlling persons, officers, directors, partners, agents, volunteers, or employees of any Purchaser shall be liable to any other Purchaser for any action heretofore taken or omitted to be taken by any of them in connection with the purchase of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Residence. If the Purchaser is an individual, then the Purchaser resides in the state identified in the address of the Purchaser set forth on the signature page hereto and/or on Schedule 1; if the Purchaser is a partnership, corporation, limited liability company or other entity, then the office or offices of the Purchaser in which its principal place of business is identified in the address or addresses of the Purchaser set forth on the signature page hereto and/or on Schedule 1. In the event that the Purchaser is not a resident of Singapore, such Purchaser hereby agrees to make such additional representations and warranties relating to such Purchaser's status as a non-Singapore resident as reasonably may be requested by the Company and to execute and deliver such documents or agreements as reasonably may be requested by the Company relating thereto as a condition to the purchase and sale of any shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock by such Purchaser.</numbered_2_firstbold>


<a_left_sidehead xname="ssia_general">GENERAL PROVISIONS.</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_s_and_a">Successors and Assigns. The terms and conditions of this Agreement shall inure to the benefit of and be binding upon the respective successors and assigns of the parties. Nothing in this Agreement, express or implied, is intended to confer upon any party other than the parties to this Agreement or their respective successors and assigns any rights, remedies, obligations, or liabilities under or by reason of this Agreement, except as expressly provided in this Agreement.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Governing Law. This Agreement is governed by the Governing Law, regardless of the laws that might otherwise govern under applicable principles of choice of law.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Counterparts; Facsimile or Electronic Signature. This Agreement may be executed and delivered by facsimile or electronic signature and in two or more counterparts, each of which will be deemed an original, but all of which together will constitute one and the same instrument.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Titles and Subtitles. The titles and subtitles used in this Agreement are used for convenience only and are not to be considered in construing or interpreting this Agreement. References to sections or subsections within this set of Agreement Terms shall be deemed to be references to the sections of this set of Agreement Terms contained in Exhibit B to the Agreement, unless otherwise specifically stated herein.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_notices">Notices. All notices and other communications given or made pursuant to this Agreement must be in writing and will be deemed to have been given upon the earlier of actual receipt or: (a) personal delivery to the party to be notified, (b) when sent, if sent by facsimile or electronic mail during normal business hours of the recipient, and if not sent during normal business hours, then on the recipient's next business day, (c) five days after having been sent by registered or certified mail, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, or (d) one business day after deposit with a nationally recognized overnight courier, freight prepaid, specifying next business day delivery, with written verification of receipt. All communications must be sent to the respective parties at their address as set forth on the signature page or Schedule 1, or to such address, facsimile number or electronic mail address as subsequently modified by written notice given in accordance with this Section <xref to="ss_notices" />.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>No Finder's Fees. Each party severally represents to the other parties that it neither is nor will be obligated for any finder's fee or commission in connection with this transaction. Each Purchaser shall indemnify, defend, and hold harmless the Company from any liability for any commission or compensation in the nature of a finder's or broker's fee arising out of this transaction (and the costs and expenses of defending against such liability or asserted liability) for which the Purchaser or any of its officers, employees, volunteers, or representatives is responsible. The Company shall indemnify, defend, and hold harmless each Purchaser from any liability for any commission or compensation in the nature of a finder's or broker's fee arising out of this transaction (and the costs and expenses of defending against such liability or asserted liability) for which the Company or any of its officers, employees, volunteers, or representatives is responsible.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Attorneys' Fees. If any action at law or in equity (including arbitration) is necessary to enforce or interpret the terms of this Agreement, the prevailing party will be entitled to reasonable attorneys' fees, costs, and necessary disbursements in addition to any other relief to which the party may be entitled. Each party shall pay all costs and expenses that it incurs with respect to the negotiation, execution, delivery, and performance of the Agreement; provided, however, that the Company shall, at the Closing, reimburse the fees and expenses of one counsel for Purchasers, for a flat fee equal to the Purchaser Counsel Reimbursement Amount.</numbered_2_firstbold>

<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_a_and_w">Amendments and Waivers. Except as specified in Section <xref to="ss_additional_closing_period" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/>, any term of this Agreement may be amended, terminated or waived (either generally or in a particular instance and either retroactively or prospectively) only with the written consent of the Company and the Purchasers holding a majority of the then-outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (or Common Stock issued on conversion thereof).<?
if(data.verbose_a_and_w) {?> Notwithstanding the foregoing, the addition of a party to this Agreement pursuant to a transfer of Shares in accordance with Section <xref to="ss_s_and_a" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/> will not require any further consent.<?
}?> Any amendment or waiver effected in accordance with this Section <xref to="ss_a_and_w" /> will be binding upon the Purchasers, the Key Holders, each transferee of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (or the Common Stock issuable upon conversion thereof) or Common Stock from a Purchaser or Key Holders, as applicable, and each future holder of all such securities, and the Company.<?
if(data.verbose_a_and_w) {?> It is specifically intended that entering into the Next Financing Agreements in a form substantially similar to the form agreements set as forth as Model Legal Documents on http://www.nvca.org shall be considered an amendment to this Agreement provided that it is done in accordance with this Section <xref to="ss_a_and_w" />.<?}?></numbered_2_firstbold>

<numbered_2_firstbold>Third Parties' Rights. Nothing in this Agreement is intended to grant to any third party any right to enforce any term of this Agreement or to confer on any third party any benefits under this Agreement for the purposes of the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act <span_smallcaps>53b</span_smallcaps> and any re-enactment thereof, the application of which legislation is hereby expressly excluded.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Severability. The invalidity or unenforceability of any provision of this Agreement will in no way affect the validity or enforceability of any other provision.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Delays or Omissions. No delay or omission to exercise any right, power or remedy accruing to any party under this Agreement, upon any breach or default of any other party under this Agreement, will impair any such right, power or remedy of such non-breaching or non-defaulting party nor will it be construed to be a waiver of any such breach or default, or an acquiescence therein, or of or in any similar breach or default thereafter occurring; nor will any waiver of any single breach or default be deemed a waiver of any other breach or default theretofore or thereafter occurring. Any waiver, permit, consent or approval of any kind or character on the part of any party of any breach or default under this Agreement, or any waiver on the part of any party of any provisions or conditions of this Agreement, must be in writing and shall be effective only to the extent specifically set forth in such writing. All remedies, either under this Agreement or by law or otherwise afforded to any party, are cumulative and not alternative.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_termination">Termination. Unless terminated earlier pursuant to the terms of this Agreement, notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, this Agreement (excluding any then-existing obligations) will terminate upon the closing of a Deemed Liquidation Event as defined in the Company's Amended Constitution, as amended from time to time; but notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, Section <xref to="ssia_purchase" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/>, Section <xref to="ssia_rw_coy" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/>, Section <xref to="ssia_rw_p" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/>, and this Section <xref to="ssia_general" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/> will survive any termination of this Agreement.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Dispute Resolution. Each party (a) hereby irrevocably and unconditionally submits to the personal jurisdiction of the Dispute Resolution Jurisdiction for the purpose of any suit, action, or other proceeding arising out of or based upon this Agreement; (b) shall not commence any suit, action or other proceeding arising out of or based upon this Agreement except in the Dispute Resolution Jurisdiction; and (c) hereby waives, and shall not assert, by way of motion, as a defense, or otherwise, in any such suit, action or proceeding, any claim that it is not subject to the personal jurisdiction of the Dispute Resolution Jurisdiction, that its property is exempt or immune from attachment or execution, that the suit, action or proceeding is brought in an inconvenient forum, that the venue of the suit, action or proceeding is improper or that this Agreement, or the subject matter hereof and thereof may not be enforced in or by the Dispute Resolution Jurisdiction.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<centered></centered>
<centered></centered>
<centered>[Page Intentionally Left Blank]</centered>
<centered>
</centered>
<chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>
<para_1><span_smallcaps>In witness whereof</span_smallcaps> the parties hereto have executed this Agreement as of the date and year first written above.</para_1>

  <?!= include("inc_enumerate_signatures", data, {rcpts_to:rcpts_to, _include2: { term: { new_investor: "purchaser" } } } ) ?>

<chapter_header>Exhibit C: Form of Restated Charter</chapter_header>

<?!= include("jfdi_articles_2015", data) ?>
<?!= include("seriesseed_coi", data) ?>

<chapter_header>Exhibit D: Disclosure Schedule</chapter_header>
<para_1>See next page &#8211; if no next page, then there are no disclosures.</para_1>
<para_1>This Disclosure Schedule (this "Disclosure Schedule") is delivered by the Company in connection with the sale of shares of the Company's Series Seed Preferred Stock on or about the Agreement Date by the Company. This Disclosure Schedule is arranged in sections corresponding to the numbered and lettered sections contained in Exhibit B of the Agreement, and the disclosures in any section of this Disclosure Schedule qualify other sections in Exhibit B of the Agreement to the extent it is reasonably apparent from a reading of the disclosure that such disclosure is applicable to such other sections. Where any representation or warranty is limited or qualified by the materiality of the matters to which the representation or warranty are given, the inclusion of any matter in this Disclosure Schedule does not constitute an admission by the Company that such matter is material. Unless otherwise defined herein, any capitalized terms in this Disclosure Schedule have the same meanings assigned to those terms in the Agreement. Nothing in this Disclosure Schedule constitutes an admission of any liability or obligation of the Company to any third party, or an admission against the Company's interests.</para_1>
</Story_Main>
</Root>

<!--  LocalWords:  hereto sidenotes supplementals mutatis
-->
<!--  LocalWords:  mutandis Pre xmlns hereunder issuable co
-->
<!--  LocalWords:  nonassessable Holder's nonrenewal donees
-->
<!--  LocalWords:  legended Exculpation unaudited acquirer
-->
<!--  LocalWords:  rata Designees Designee Finder's
-->
<!--  LocalWords:  finder's unenforceability materiality
-->
