<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<!--This contract is for a:
- short term (no longer than 3 months) contractor.
- fixed term, with  option for renewal.
- not an employment agreement.-->

<CoverTop>
<cover_title>Contract for Service</cover_title>
<cover_company_name>

<?= data.parties.company[0].name ?></cover_company_name>
<cover_company_id><?= data.parties.company[0].idtype ?> <?= data.parties.company[0].id ?></cover_company_id>
<cover_company_name>
<?= data.parties.contractor[0].name ?></cover_company_name>
<cover_company_id><?= data.parties.contractor[0].idtype ?> <?= data.parties.contractor[0].id ?></cover_company_id>
</CoverTop>
<CoverMid>
</CoverMid>

<CoverBottom_Logotype>
</CoverBottom_Logotype>

<CoverBottom_Address>
</CoverBottom_Address>

<CoverBottom_series>
<centered>version 1.0.0</centered>
</CoverBottom_series>

<Firstpage_Sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>

<Story_Main><chapter_header>Contract for Service</chapter_header>
<!--Parties to the contract-->
<para_1>This contract for service is generated on <textvar name="Output Date"/> ("<b>Contract</b>").</para_1>
<para_1><span_smallcaps>between</span_smallcaps>:-</para_1>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.contractor[0]) ?> (the "<b>Contractor</b>"), and</parties>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?> (the "<b>Company</b>")</parties>
<para_1>(each a "<b>Party</b>" and collectively, the "<b>Parties</b>")</para_1>
<!--
Recitals (non-binding)
-->
<para_1><span_smallcaps>Whereas:-</span_smallcaps></para_1>
<recitals>The Company is desirous of engaging the Contractor and the Contractor agrees to be engaged for her services in the capacity of a <?= data.role ?> according to the terms and subject to the conditions set out in this Contract.</recitals>

<!--Start of contract and legend for guiding interpretation and definitions. Nothing that is undefined should be capitalised unless it is a proper noun-->

<para_1><span_smallcaps>Now it is hereby agreed</span_smallcaps> as follows:-</para_1>
<a_left_sidehead>Definitions &amp; Interpretation</a_left_sidehead>
<para_1>In this Contract, unless the subject or context otherwise requires:-</para_1>
<definition>Business	means any of the business, undertakings, services, assets, and activities which the Company may now and/or hereafter engage, including those relating t and/or arising from <?= data.company.business_activity ?> and all of the Company's actual or demonstrably anticipated research and development activities;</definition>
<definition>Company	shall include any of its affiliates, subsidiaries, successors, and assigns;</definition>
<definition>Company Account	means the Company's bitcoin account with the wallet address located at <b><?= data.company.bitcoin_address ?></b>;</definition>
<definition>Company Property	means Work, Rights, and the like of whatsoever nature including all copies thereof, made, compiled, acquired, conceived, developed, reduced to practice, or expressed in tangible form by Contractor (whether directly or indirectly) during the Engagement Term, as a result (whether directly or indirectly) of anything done by Contractor in pursuance of, relating to, or arising out of this Contract, and/or based (whether directly or indirectly) on any Confidential Information, whether or not patentable, registrable, and/ or copyrightable, and shall include any applications for and/or of any of those rights, that is assigned or that may be assigned to the Company under this Contract or otherwise;</definition>
<definition>Contractor Account	means the Contractor's bitcoin account with the wallet address located at <b><?= data.contractor_account ?></b>;</definition>
<definition>Competitor	means any third party engaged in and/or carrying on business activities which are similar to and/or competitive with the Business;</definition>
<definition>Confidential Information	means all information and data (whether recorded or not, and if recorded, in whatever form on whatever media) relating to all or any part of the Business or the Company, including the organisation, operations, dealings, property, assets, technology, activities, services, personnel, know-how, trade secrets, past or present customers or users, financial affairs, management, administration, technical information, Rights or other proprietary business designations used and/or owned by the Company, together with analyses, compilations, studies, or other documents and/or materials that contain or otherwise reflect such information and data, which is confidential to the Company or is treated as confidential;</definition>
<definition>Effective Date	means the earliest date on which all Parties have executed this Contract;</definition>
<definition>Engagement Term	means the <?= data.company.engagement_term?> period beginning on the Effective Date until such date when this Contract is terminated or determined according to the terms hereunder;</definition>
<definition>Fees	means the fees payable by Company to Contractor as set out under Clause <xref to="Fees"/>, for the provision of Services set out under this Contract;</definition>
<definition>First Payment Date	means the date as defined under Clause <xref to="First Payment Date"/>;</definition>
<definition>GitHub	means the Company's GitHub repository at <?=data.company.github_url?>;</definition>
<definition>Rights	means (i) trade marks, service marks, registered designs, trade and business names (including domain names and email address names), unregistered trade marks and service marks, copyrights, database rights, know-how, rights in designs, Work, and patents, including applications of and for any of those rights, in whatever form on whatever media including computer output, computer program, and computer service; (ii) rights under licenses, consents, orders, statutes or otherwise in relation to a right under (i); and rights of the same or similar effect or nature as, or to those in (i) and/or (ii) above;</definition>
<definition>Services	means the services to be provided by Contractor to the Company as set out under Clause <xref to="Services"/>;</definition>
<definition>Slack	means the Company's SLACK application at legalese.slack.com; and </definition>
<definition>Work	means all notes, memoranda, records, correspondence, inventions, discoveries, designs, processes, formulæ, innovations, developments, improvements, copyright works (including without limitation, files, computer software, computer programs, articles, reports, drawings, technical drawings, blueprints, advertisements, sales materials, plans, and logos) and the like (including all copies thereof) made, compiled, acquired, discovered, conceived, developed, reduced into practice or expressed in tangible form by the Contractor (whether solely or jointly with other persons, and whether directly or indirectly) (i) arising out of, relating to, or in pursuance of this Contract, or (ii) relating to the Business, finances, or affairs of the Company, or any member of the Company, or (iii) which constitutes works for hire based (whether directly or indirectly) on any item of the Confidential Information, whether or not patentable, registrable, and/ or copyrightable, and shall include any applications for and/or any of those rights.</definition>
<para_1>Capitalised terms not otherwise defined under this Contract, shall bear the same meaning as that ascribed to them under the Company's Constitution (as may be amended from time to time).</para_1>

<!--Interpretation-->

<para_1>Unless otherwise stated or where the context otherwise requires:- </para_1>
<para_2>words importing the singular include the plural and vice versa;</para_2>
<para_2>words importing a gender include every gender;</para_2>
<para_2>references to persons include bodies corporate or unincorporated, any state or any agency thereof, and any other entity, and vice versa;</para_2>
<para_2>headings, marginal sidenotes, and graphic art are for ease of reference only and shall have no legal effect;</para_2>
<para_2>reference to Clauses are to clauses of this Contract, and references to this Contract include any schedules, amendments, and supplementals thereto;</para_2>
<para_2>references to any person include its successors and permitted assigns;</para_2>
<para_2>references to a time of day are to Singapore time, and '<b>$</b>' or '<b>dollars</b>' denotes Singapore dollars; and</para_2>
<para_2>references to a statutory provision include such provision and any regulations made in pursuance thereof as from time to time modified and/or re-enacted whether before or after the Effective Date so far as such modification and/or re-enactment applies or is capable of applying to and/or in connection with this Contract.</para_2>

<!--Service to be provided-->

<a_left_sidehead>Scope of Service</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para xname="Fees">In consideration of the fees of <b><?= data.total_service_fees ?></b> ("<b>Fees</b>") to be paid by the Company to Contractor, Contractor hereby agrees to provide Services as an independent contractor -- specifically in the role of <b><?= data.role ?></b> -- to the Company in accordance with the terms hereunder.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para xname="First Payment Date">During the Engagement Term, Fees shall be paid by Company to Contractor in equal monthly installments. The first of such payments shall be made within 7 days of the Effective Date, such date to be determined at the Company's sole and absolute discretion (<b>"First Payment Date"</b>), and shall be for the period of one (1) month from the Effective Date. Thereafter, subsequent payments shall be made monthly in advance on the first day of each month of the Engagement Term.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Company's payment of Fees to Contractor shall be via a transfer from Company's Account to Contractor's Account, or such other means as Parties may agree upon prior notice and acceptance in writing.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>This Contract shall become effective upon the Effective Date and determine <b><?= data.engagement_term ?></b> therefrom, unless otherwise terminated under this Contract.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para xname="Renewal">This Contract may be extended on identical terms for a maximum of <?= data.engagement_term ?> upon signed mutual agreement in writing between the Parties. In such event, Engagement Term shall be extended accordingly.</numbered_2_para>

<!--clarifying the relationship between the parties so that the contractor shall be in no way be interpreted as being an employee of the company-->

<a_left_sidehead>Relationship between the Parties</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>The Parties acknowledge and accept that, during the Engagement Term and after, to the fullest extent permissible under applicable laws, regulations, and rules:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor shall provide Services to the Company on her own account as a self-employed independent contractor and nothing in this Contract shall be construed as creating a joint venture, partnership, franchise, agency, employer/employee, or similar relationship between the Parties, or as authorising either Party to act as the  agent of the other;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor shall be solely and independently responsible for acquiring and controlling the tools, equipment, means, details, manner, methods, working place, and such other factors of production as it may require to provide the Services and/or fulfill its obligations under this Contract; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor has the right to perform and/or provide the Services (subject to Clause <xref to="Services"/>) from any place and at such times as the Contractor shall determine in her own discretion;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Company shall not be responsible for any taxes (including any withholding taxes) with respect to Contractor's Fees hereunder; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor shall have no claim against the Company hereunder or otherwise for vacation pay, sick leave, retirement benefits, social security, employee's compensation, health or disability benefits, unemployment insurance benefits, or employee benefits of any kind.</numbered_3_para>

<!--Services-->

<a_left_sidehead xname="Services">Services</a_left_sidehead>
<!--TODO: at some point we should automate these into the form so that they can be easily replaced for different roles-->
<numbered_2_para>During the Engagement Term, Contractor shall devote her time, energy, abilities and resources as may be necessary, expedient, and efficient, to resolve the issues and/or milestones set out at GitHub within any timeframes specified therein. Company may from time to time, suggest (but not compel or direct) priorities for such issues and/or milestones via Slack, GitHub, or emails. ("<b>Services</b>").</numbered_2_para>

<!--
Reps and warranties
-->

<a_left_sidehead>Representations &amp; Warranties</a_left_sidehead>
<!--Company reps and warranties-->
<numbered_2_para>Company hereby represents and warrants that:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>it has the power and capacity to enter into this Contract;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>it will make timely payment of the Fees when such Fees are due;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>it shall use reasonable endeavours to notify Contractor of any changes to its procedures affecting Contractor's obligations under this Contract; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>it shall provide such other assistance to the Contractor as the Company (at its sole and absolute discretion) may deem reasonable and/or appropriate.</numbered_3_para>

<!--Contractor reps and warranties-->

<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby represents and warrants to the Company that:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>she has the power, capacity, competence, ability, and experience to enter into this Contract, perform the Services, and fulfill her obligations under this Contract;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>her performance of the Services and fulfillment of her obligations under this Contract does not and will not breach any other agreement to which she is a party and that she has not and will not during the Engagement Term, enter into any oral or written agreement in conflict with any of the provisions under this Contract;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>any and all undertaking, commencement, or progress made pursuant to this Contract with respect to the milestones and/or issues listed at GitHub shall be promptly communicated (at least within 2 days of such progress) to the Company via Slack and/or within GitHub itself;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>save where relating to Confidential Information and communicated to Contractor between director(s) of the Company, she acknowledges and accepts that all  communications (including instructions, direction, suggestions, promises, assurances, confirmations) not expressed in non-private Slack channels shall be invalid and unenforceable;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Services shall be performed in accordance with and shall not violate any applicable laws, rules, and regulations (including any of the Company's policies as may be communicated to Contractor from time to time) and Contractor has obtained all permits and/or permissions and done all such acts as may be required to comply with such applicable laws, rules, and regulations;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Company shall not, and shall not be required to supervise the Contractor;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Company shall not, and shall not be required to hire, supervise, or pay any assistants or additional persons to help Contractor perform the Services and her obligations under this Contract; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor shall be solely responsible for paying for all ordinary, extraordinary, and necessary expenses (whether of itself or otherwise).</numbered_3_para>
<!--
Clarification about works for hire
-->
<a_left_sidehead>Company Property</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor acknowledges and accepts that, to the fullest extent permissible under applicable laws, rules, and regulations, during the Engagement Term and after, Company Property, including any and all materials prepared by Contractor under this Contract shall be considered proprietary to the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Where any such materials, Work and/or Rights may not be deemed as Company Property under applicable laws, rules, and regulations, Contractor hereby assigns to the Company all of its right, title, interest in and to such materials, Work and Rights. Contractor shall also without compensation and forthwith upon demand, whether during the Engagement Term or otherwise, execute and deliver to the Company any instruments of transfer or take such other action as may be requested by Company, as may be required to secure and ensure protection of such of the Company's rights and interest, and/or effect such transfer to the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>Such actions include without limitation, signing of documents and giving testimony required in the course of the Company applying for or maintaining any patent or copyright or Rights, or in the course of any litigation or other legal proceeding related to any Company Property, Rights and/or Works anywhere in the world.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>For example, but without limiting the generality of the foregoing, Contractor agrees to execute all applications, specifications, oaths, assignments, recordations, and all other instruments which the Company shall deem necessary in order to apply for, obtain, maintain and transfer such rights and in order to assign and convey to the Company, its successors, assigns and nominees the sole and exclusive rights, title and interest in and to such Rights, Works, Company Property, and any copyrights, patents, or other intellectual property rights relating thereto and that her obligation to execute or cause to be executed, when it is in her power to do so, any such instrument or papers shall continue after the termination of this Contract until the expiration of the last such intellectual property right to expire in any country of the world.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>If, under applicable laws, rules, and regulations, Contractor is unable to assign all or any part of such rights to the Company, or if approval of such assignment is required from a government authority and such approval is not granted, Contractor hereby licenses to the Company such rights as cannot be assigned, so that the Company shall have the complete right to use and right to exploit the Company Property (and any modified and derivative works thereof). The license of rights under this Clause shall be perpetual, free of charge, sub-licensable, irrevocable, exclusive (excluding both the Contractor and all third parties), worldwide and transferable.</numbered_2_para>
<!--Clause below might not be enforceable in Singapore because this is effectively a POA (which has to executed as a deed)-->
<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby irrevocably designates and appoints the Company and its duly authorized officers and agents as her agent and attorney in fact, in the event the Company is unable because of the Contractor's mental or physical incapacity or unavailability or for any other reason to secure the Contractor's signature to apply for or to pursue any application for any Singapore or foreign patents or copyright registrations covering the Rights, Works and/or Company Property, to act for and on her behalf and stead to execute and file any such applications and to do all other lawfully permitted acts to further the application for, prosecution, issuance, maintenance or transfer of letters patent or copyright registrations thereon with the same legal force and effect as if originally executed by the Contractor.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor agrees not to exercise any rights and/or interests in the Company Property that pursuant to applicable law, regulations, and rules, cannot be assigned or licensed to the Company pursuant to the foregoing, including but not limited to right to claim authorship and the right not to suffer false attribution of authorship, except with the prior written consent of the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>During the Engagement Term and after, where Contractor intends to integrate and/or incorporate any of her Rights and/or previous Work in furtherance of her performance of the Services and/or her obligations under this Contract, such proposal shall be first communicated in writing to and accepted by the Company prior to any such intended integration and/or incorporation. Where Company, in its sole and absolute discretion, consents to such integration and/or incorporation, Contractor shall hereby grant Company an exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable license to use, distribute, modify, publish, sub-license, and/or otherwise exploit such integration and/or incorporation in connection with the Business of the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<!--
Non-compete / conflicts of interest
-->
<a_left_sidehead>Conflicts of Interest</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor acknowledges that as an independent contractor, she is free to engage in other activities, including any activities in the role of <b><?= data.role ?></b> during the Engagement Term <i><b>PROVIDED</b></i> that Contractor shall not accept work, enter into agreements, and/or undertake obligations inconsistent and/or incompatible with Contractor's obligations and provision of Services under this Contract.</numbered_2_para>
<!--
Rights, Work and IP rights
-->
<a_left_sidehead>Rights, Work, &amp; Confidential Information</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>The Company does not give any warranty or representation to Contractor as to the accuracy and/or completeness of Confidential Information, and Company shall not be liable to Contractor for damages, claims, or losses resulting from the use of Confidential Information.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Save where expressly permitted under this Contract, Contractor shall not, without the prior written consent of the Company, whether during the Engagement Term or after, (i) use, copy, reproduce, or otherwise exploit any Company Property or Confidential Information; or (ii) distribute, publish, copy, reproduce, or otherwise disclose any Confidential Information or Company Property to any person for or in connection with anything other than for fulfilling Contractor's obligations under this Contract.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby undertakes and agrees that during the Engagement Term and after, she shall protect the Company Property and Confidential Information using the same standard of care she applies to her own proprietary and/or confidential information and data (but no less than reasonable care) and to the extent reasonably practicable and permitted by applicable laws, regulations, and rules, procure and ensure that the Confidential Information and Company Property is stored, handled, and maintained in such a way as to prevent unauthorised disclosure.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Nothing in this Contract, whether by implication or otherwise, directly or indirectly, shall or be construed as granting or conferring Contractor any Rights, rights to Work, or rights to any Confidential Information or Company Property.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby acknowledges and accepts that Company Property and Confidential Information and all rights therein are and shall remain the sole and exclusive property of the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby agrees and undertakes to:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>hold in strictest confidence the Confidential Information;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>take all steps to prevent any unauthorised reproduction, duplication, and/or copying of Confidential Information and the Company Property by any person;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>take all steps to ensure that documents and items of work-in-progress that embody the Company Property or Confidential Information are kept and/or maintained securely (including without limitation, using disk encryption and two-factor authentication protection whenever possible);</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not reproduce, adapt, modify, translate, manufacture, market, publish, distribute, sell, license (or sublicense), transfer, rent, lease, transmit, broadcast, display, or use Company Property or Confidential Information (including any portion or copy thereof) in any form, in a fashion beyond the Company's control;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not create derivative works from, provide access electronically to, or enter into computer memory beyond the Company's control, the Company Property or Confidential Information (including any portion or copy thereof) in any form;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not apply for, or apply to register, any patent, copyright, trademark or other industrial property right or intellectual property right in or related to Confidential Information or Company Property, in Singapore or any other country or region; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not cause other persons to do any of the above.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>For the avoidance of doubt, Confidential Information shall not include any information or data which:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>at the date of its disclosure can be proved by documentary evidence to be information which is publicly available or which subsequently becomes publicly available other than by consequence of breach of this Contract by Contractor or breach of any confidentiality obligations by a third party; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>at the date of its disclosure can be proved by documentary evidence to be already rightfully available and/or in the possession to Contractor prior to receipt from Company, and that had not been acquired (directly or indirectly) from the Company or any person known to Contractor as being under an obligation of confidence; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>is compelled to be disclosed by applicable laws, regulations, and rules of a competent jurisdiction to which Contractor is subject, or by a court of competent jurisdiction, regulator, or any competent supervisory or regulatory body to which Contractor may be subject, <b>provided</b> that to the extent permissible under applicable laws, regulations and rules, prior to any such disclosure, Contractor shall promptly inform Company and take Company's instructions as to the form, nature and/or purpose of any proposed disclosure; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>is developed by Contractor independently without the use and/or reference to Confidential Information.</numbered_3_para>
<!--
Termination
-->
<a_left_sidehead>Termination of Contract</a_left_sidehead>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Termination by Notice</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>The Company shall be entitled to terminate this Contract (without prejudice to and in addition to any other remedy) upon the issuance of not less than 14 days' written notice to Contractor at any time.</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_2_para>The Contractor shall be entitled to terminate this Contract by giving the Company no less than 1 months' prior written notice.</numbered_2_para>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Termination by summary notice</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>The Company shall be entitled (but not obliged) at any time to terminate the Contract with immediate effect by summary notice and without any payment of Fees or compensation whatsoever, and without prejudice to and in addition to any other remedy, in the event that:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor commits any serious or material breach of her obligations hereunder; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>where Contractor has repeatedly breached her obligations hereunder, Contractor has, after Company's written warning and 14-day period (where applicable) to remedy such breach, failed to remedy such breach to Company's sole and absolute satisfaction; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor commits any act or engages in any conduct which brings or would bring herself or the Company into disrepute; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor commits or engages in any act of misconduct, willful disobedience of lawful orders, breach of confidentiality obligations under this Contract, or violates any laws and/or regulations in any jurisdiction from which the Services are provided; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor is convicted of any criminal offence other than an offence which in the absolute opinion of the Company does not adversely affect Contractor's position as an independent contractor, its provision of the Services, or its fulfilment of its obligations under this Contract; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor (in the absolute opinion of the Company) becomes of unsound mind and/or incapacitated to provide the Services and/or perform its obligations hereunder; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Contractor makes or has a bankruptcy application or petition served on her or makes any arrangement or composition with her creditors generally; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>it becomes illegal for the Company to engage the Services of Contractor.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>The termination of this Contract howsoever arising shall not affect such of the terms hereof as are expressed to operate or have effect thereafter, and shall be strictly without prejudice to any right of action or remedy already accrued to the Company in respect of any breach or default by them.</numbered_2_para>

<!--Effects of Termination-->

<a_left_sidehead>Effects of Termination or Determination</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>Upon determination and/or termination of this Contract for whatever reason, Contractor shall:-</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>immediately relinquish all access and/or rights given to her due to her engagement under this Contract;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not at any time thereafter, represent herself (whether actively or by omission, directly or indirectly) as being in any way connected or affiliated to the Company or engaged in any Business or affairs of the Company;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>promptly return to the Company all tangible forms of Confidential Information and Company Property, including any and all copies and extracts thereof, and delete any such items in the Contractor's personal possession and personal access; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>not make or retain any copies or extracts of any Confidential Information or Company Property, and agree to provide written confirmation to the Company of such undertaking.</numbered_3_para>
<!--boilerplates-->
<a_left_sidehead>General Provisions</a_left_sidehead>

<!--electronic signatures & communications - in SG does not extend to deeds, POAs, instruments-->

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Electronic signatures &amp; communications</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>The Parties agree that this Contract may be electronically signed, and electronic signatures appearing on this Contract shall be taken as the same as handwritten signatures for the purposes of validity, enforceability, and admissibility. The Parties also hereby consent to transact and conduct their affairs under this Contract using electronic communications, to receive notices, and disclosures electronically, and to utilise electronic signatures in lieu of paper documents.</numbered_2_para>

<!--governing law & jurisdiction-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Governing law &amp; jurisdiction</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>This Contract for Service shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore without regard to the principles of conflict of laws, and Parties hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Singapore.</numbered_2_para>
<!--dispute reso - litigation preferred as it saves money and time without having to separately seek to enforce the settlement/arbitration judgment.-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Dispute resolution</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>Parties hereby irrevocably agree that the courts of Singapore shall have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any disputes, claims, controversies, or differences arising out of or in connection with this Contract.</numbered_2_para>
<!--Notices-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Notices</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>Notices under this Contract shall be given in writing via the Parties' respective email addresses (or such other address as Parties may notify the other in writing):-</numbered_2_para>
<para_2><b>Contractor</b> at <?= data.contractor_email ?></para_2>
<para_2><b>Company</b> at <?= data.contract_email ?></para_2>
<numbered_2_para>Any notices given in accordance with this Contract shall be deemed to have been served on the day on which such notice was successfully delivered via email.</numbered_2_para>
<!--
Entire agreement
-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Entire agreement</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>This Contract shall supersede any terms and/or agreements previously in force between the Parties. This Contract constitutes the entire agreement and understanding between the Parties as to its subject matter, and <b>Contractor hereby acknowledges that this Contract has not been entered into in reliance upon any representation, warranty, or undertaking not expressly set out in this Contract, or referred to in this Contract as forming part of the Contract, and there are no representations, understandings or agreements relative hereto which are not fully expressed herein.</b></numbered_2_para>
<!--Severance-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Severance</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>If any provision of this Contract or part thereof is rendered void, illegal or unenforceable by any law, regulations, and rules to which it is subject, it shall be rendered void, illegal or unenforceable to that extent and no further.</numbered_2_para>
<!--NO 3rd party rights-->
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>No third party rights</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>The Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Cap. 53B) of Singapore shall not under any circumstances apply to this Contract and any person who is not a party to this Contract (whether or not such person shall be named, referred to, or otherwise identified, or form part of a class of persons so named, referred to or identified, in this Contract) shall have no right whatsoever under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act (Cap. 53B) of Singapore to enforce this Agreement or any of its terms.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>No assignment</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor's rights and obligations under this Agreement may not be assigned without the prior written consent of the Company.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Further assurance</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor hereby agrees with and undertakes to the Company that she shall do all such other acts and things and to sign and execute (or process the signing and execution of) all such documents and instruments as may be necessary or expedient or requested by the Company to give effect to the terms of this Contract.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Survival</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>The termination or determination of this Contract howsoever arising shall not operate to affect such of the provisions hereof which in accordance with their terms are expressed to operate or have effect after the termination or determination of this Contract. For the avoidance of doubts, provisions that shall survive the termination and/or determination of this Contract include without limitation, those relating to Confidential Information, Rights, Work, effect of termination or determination, and Company Property.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>No contra proferentum</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>Contractor acknowledges that, in executing this Contract she has had the opportunity (whether or not actually undertaken) to seek the advice of independent legal counsel, and she has read and understood all of the terms and provisions of this Contract. In the interpretation of this Contract or any part thereof, no rule of construction shall apply to the disadvantage of any Party on the basis that that Party (i) prepared this Contract or any part of it; or (ii) seeks to rely on this Contract or any part of it.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>No waiver</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>No failure on the part of any Party to exercise and no delay on the part of any Party in exercising any right hereunder will operate as a release or waiver thereof, nor will any single or partial exercise of any right under this Contract preclude any other or further exercise of it.</numbered_2_para>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Counterparts</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_2_para>This Contract may be executed in one or more counterparts, and such counterparts may be exchanged by electronic transmission (including by email), each of which will be deemed an original, but all of which together constitute one and the same agreement. For the avoidance of doubt, in the case of execution by way of counterparts, this Contract shall not be deemed to be concluded until the last of such counterparts shall have been executed and delivered to the other Party.</numbered_2_para>
<!--
Signing block
-->
<chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>
<para_1>Intending to be bound by this Contract for Service the Parties hereby set their hands:</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>The Contractor<?= data.parties.contractor.length == 1 ? "" : "s" ?></b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<? for (var i = 0; i < data.parties.contractor.length; i++) { ?>
<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.parties.contractor[i]) ?>
<? } ?>
<b_left_sidehead_nonum>For and on behalf of the Company <?= data.company.name ?></b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.company) ?>
</Story_Main>
</Root>
