<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/" templateSpec="eula.indt">
  <Story_Main>
	<cover_title>Welcome to Legalese</cover_title>
	
<chapter_header override="startParagraph=StartParagraph.ANYWHERE">Legalese End-User Software License Agreement</chapter_header>

	<para_1><span_smallcaps>This agreement</span_smallcaps> is made this <? if (data.agreement_date) { ?><?= data.agreement_date ?><?} else {?><textvar name="Output Date" /><?}?> between:---</para_1> 

	<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?> ("<?= data.company.short_name?>") and</parties>
<? if (data.user.address) {?>
	<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.user) ?> (you, the <b>"User"</b>)</parties>
<? } else { ?>
    <parties><?= data.user.name ?> &lt;<?=data.user.email?>&gt; (you, the <b>"User"</b>)</parties>
<? } ?>
	<para_1>(collectively, the <b>"Parties"</b> and each a <b>"Party"</b>.</para_1>

<para_1>Please read this Agreement carefully. By copying, installing, or using all or any portion of this Software, User accepts all the terms and conditions of this Agreement. User agrees that this Agreement is like any written negotiated agreement signed by User. This Agreement is enforceable against User. If User does not agree to the terms of this Agreement, User shall not be authorised to use this Software.</para_1>


	<para_1><span_smallcaps>Whereas:-</span_smallcaps></para_1>

	<recitals>User desires to copy, install, and/or use this Software; and</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">Legalese desires to demonstrate its software capabilities; but</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">Legalese does not want to get into trouble with the law or with User.</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">User has on <b>insert time/date stamp from form submission here</b>, confirmed the following:-</recitals>
	<bullets>The Software does not perform any validation or fact checking on behalf of User:  what User types in the Software is exactly what will appear in any of the documents generated.</bullets>
	<bullets>Once signed PDFs have been generated on the Software, no further changes can be made to any documents so generated.</bullets>
	<bullets>As documents generated by the Software <b>may</b> be or become <b>legally binding documents</b>, it is strongly advised that User proceeds with caution.</bullets>	
	<bullets>Legalese is <b>not an attorney or a legal adviser</b>. The Software and Legalese (including any of its employees and associates)<b> does not give nor purport to give</b> any legal advice whatsoever. Legalese provides User with the Software and access to self-help materials which are aimed at helping User draft and generate its own documents. For legal advice or review, please seek the assistance of an attorney. </bullets>
	<bullets>User understands and accepts Legalese's <a hhref="http://www.legalese.io/tos.html?from=eula">Terms of Service</a> and <a hhref="http://www.legalese.io/tos-pp.html?from=eula">Legalese's Privacy Policy</a></bullets>

	<para_1><span_smallcaps>The Parties agree</span_smallcaps> as follows:-</para_1>

	<a_left_sidehead>Definitions and Interpretation</a_left_sidehead>

<definition>Google Docs	refers to the suite of Internet-based applications from Google, that includes word processing, spreadsheet, presentations, form creation, and cloud storage.</definition>

<definition>Legalese	means Legalese.io Pte. Ltd., a wholly owned subsidiary of JFDI.Asia Pte. Ltd.</definition>

<definition>PDF	refers to Portable Document Format, an open standard file format maintained by the International Organisation for Standardisation.</definition>

<!-- consider using a SaaS definition because most of this stuff runs in Google Apps or InDesign on Meng's server. -->
<!-- http://www.oracle.com/us/products/applications/crmondemand/software-service-us-439842.pdf -->
<!-- http://www.bl.uk/aboutus/foi/transparency/contracts/Contract%20SMC8263.pdf -->

<definition xname="software">Software	means (a) all of the information with which this Agreement is provided, including but not limited to: (i) all software files and other computer information; (ii) any proprietary scripting logic embedded within exported file formats or used in an [in an online service? need technical help here]; (iii) sample and stock documents, images, and other artistic works made available by Legalese on Legalese's website [***hyperlink this] and not obtained from Legalese through a separate service (unless otherwise noted within that service) or from another party (“Content Files”); (iv) related explanatory written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (v) any software, text, or template content hosted on third-party services including without limitation Google Drive, Github, or such other online or electronic documentation and Internet-based services; and (b) any modified versions and copies of, upgrades, updates, and additions to such information, provided to User by Legalese at any time, to the extent not provided under separate terms (collectively, “Updates”). </definition>

<definition>Third-Party Online Services	means third parties offering goods, information, software and/or services. </definition>

<definition>User	means you and any legal entity that obtained the Software and on whose behalf it is used; for example, and as applicable, your employer.</definition>

<definition>XML	refers to extensible markup language, a technical standard developed by the World Wide Web Consortium.</definition>

<numbered_2_para>The headings in this Agreement are for convenience only and shall not affect the interpretation hereof.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>Unless the context otherwise requires, references to the singular number shall include references to the plural number and vice versa, references to natural persons shall include bodies corporate, and the use of any gender shall include all genders.</numbered_2_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Approved Use</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software (as defined in <xref to="software" />) provided by Legalese is intended to automate the customisation and generation of documents in different formats, including without limitation, <span_smallcaps>XML, PDF</span_smallcaps>, Google Docs, Microsoft Word, and <span_smallcaps>docx</span_smallcaps>. The Software is provided by Legalese on an "as is" basis. Access to and use of any output files and/or documentation created with the Software is entirely at User's own risk.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>For the avoidance of doubt, should any document (or part thereof) customised and/or generated (whether in full or in part) using the Software be used for final execution, lodgment, filing, seal, signature, or delivery, the User hereby irrevocably affirms that User:-</numbered_2_para>
	<numbered_3_para>does so personally for himself only in any matter or proceeding to which he is a party; or</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is legal counsel (by whatever name called) in an entity acting solely for the entity in a matter to which it is a party; or</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is a qualified lawyer currently entitled and certified to practise law in the relevant jurisdiction; or</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is a person explicitly exempted from the requirements limiting the practise of law to qualified lawyers in the relevant jurisdiction.</numbered_3_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Third-Party Online Services</a_left_sidehead>
	<numbered_2_para>The Software may rely upon or facilitate (i) your access to websites maintained by Legalese or its affiliates; (ii) or Third-Party Online Services. Such Third-Party Online Services include without limitation, Google Drive, Adobe EchoSign, Adobe Document Cloud, DocuSign, HelloSign, and may be offered for a fee, or for an expectation of a fee, gain, or reward. User's access to and use of any website or Third-Party Online Services is governed by the terms, conditions, disclaimers, and/or notices found on such site or otherwise associated with such services. User agrees that such Third-Party Online Services are independent of both the Software and Legalese.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software may be offered in affiliation with technical support services, business advisory services, corporate secretarial services, information services, or advertising ("Commercial Services"). The User agrees that:</numbered_2_para>
	<numbered_3_para>such services are independent of Legalese and the Software;</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>use of the Software does not automatically entitle the User to Commercial Services; and</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>any use of Commercial Services shall not be construed as being made in satisfaction of any expectation of fee, gain, or reward arising from use of the Software.</numbered_3_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>No Warranty</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software is provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis. Use of the Software is strictly at the User's own risk. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the Software is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained by you from Legalese or through the Software will create any warranty not expressly stated herein. Without limiting the foregoing, Legalese does not warrant that the content provided on or accessed via the Software is accurate, reliable, or correct; that the Software will meet your requirements; that the Software will be available at any particular time or location, uninterrupted or secure; that any defects or errors will be corrected; or that the Software is free of viruses or other harmful components. Any content downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the Software is downloaded at User's own risk and User shall be solely responsible for any damage to its computer system or loss of data that results from such download or use of the Software. </numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>For the avoidance of doubt, Legalese does not warrant, endorse, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any product or service that may be advertised or offered by a third party through the Software or any hyperlinked website or service, and Legalese will not be a party to or in any way monitor transaction between you and third-party providers of products or services. </numbered_2_para>

<a_left_sidehead>Disclaimer</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event shall Legalese, its affiliates, agents, directors, officers, employees, suppliers, or licensors be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, consequential, or exemplary damages, including without limitation damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses, that result from the use of or inability to use the Software. Under no circumstances will Legalese be responsible for any damage, loss, or injury resulting from hacking, tampering or other unauthorised access or use of the Software or your account or the information therein contained.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Legalese assumes no liability or responsibility for (i) any errors, mistakes, omissions, or inaccuracies of content; (ii) any personal injury or property damage, of any nature whatsoever, arising out of, in connected with, or resulting from your access to or use of the Software; (iii) any bugs, viruses, trojan horses, or the like that may be transmitted to or through the Software by any third party; (iv) any loss or damage incurred as a result of the use of any content posted, emailed, transmitted, or otherwise made available through the Software; and/or (v) any user content or the defamatory, offensive, or illegal conduct of any third party. This limitation of liability clause applies whether the alleged liability is based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability, or any other basis, even of Legalese has been advised of the possibility of such damage. This limitation of liability clause shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by law in the applicable jurisdiction.  

The Software is not intended to substitute for legal or other professional advice. Templates and contracts, whether generic or customised, may fail to meet the User's needs. Use of the Software does not create a solicitor-client relationship between the User and Legalese, or between the User and anyone else.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>Legalese recommends, and the User understands, that only after consulting a qualified lawyer regarding the particulars of the User's situation, should the User use Legalese to prepare documents under the guidance of such a lawyer. (Unless, of course, the User <i>is</i> a qualified lawyer.)</numbered_2_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Limitation of Liability</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>In no event unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing will Legalese, any copyright holder, or any other party who modifies and/or conveys the program as permitted above, be liable to the User for damages, including any general, special, incidental or consequential damages arising out of the use or inability to use the program (including but not limited to embarrassment in commerce, loss of money, loss of data, or data being rendered inaccurate or losses sustained by you or third parties or a failure of the program to operate with any other programs), even if such holder or other party has been advised of the possibility of such damages.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>If the Disclaimer of Warranty and Limitation of Liability provided above cannot be given local legal effect according to their terms, reviewing courts, mediators, or arbitrators shall apply local law that most closely approximates an absolute waiver of all civil liability in connection with the Software, unless a warranty or assumption of liability accompanies a copy of the Software in return for a fee.</numbered_2_para>

	<chapter_header>Signature</chapter_header>

	<para_1><?= data.signature_phrase || "Intending to be bound by this Agreement, the User hereby executes this agreement:" ?></para_1>

	<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.user) ?>

  </Story_Main>
</Root>
