<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/" templateSpec="eula.indt">
  <Story_Main>
	<cover_title>Welcome to Legalese</cover_title>
	
<chapter_header override="startParagraph=StartParagraph.ANYWHERE">Legalese End-User Software License Agreement</chapter_header>

	<para_1><span_smallcaps>This agreement</span_smallcaps> is made this <? if (data.agreement_date) { ?><?= data.agreement_date ?><?} else {?><textvar name="Output Date" /><?}?> between:---</para_1> 

***[Alexis:  This should be how companies and individuals ought to be described: 

[COMPANY] (Registration Number/UEN), a company incorporated in [Singapore] with its registered office at [■] (the "Company"); 

[■] (NRIC No: [■]) of [■] ("Mr X");

[■], a resident of [■] (Passport No: [■]) of [■] ("Mr Y");]

	</b><parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?> ("<?= data.company.short_name?>") and</parties>
<? if (data.user.address) {?>
	<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.user) ?> (you, the <b>"User"</b>)</parties>
<? } else { ?>
    <parties><?= data.user.name ?> &lt;<?=data.user.email?>&gt; (you, the <b>"User"</b>)</parties>
<? } ?>
	<para_1>(collectively, the <b>"Parties"</b> and each a <b>"Party"</b>.</para_1>

<para_1>Please read this Agreement carefully. By copying, installing, or using all or any portion of this Software, User accepts all the terms and conditions of this Agreement. User agrees that this Agreement is like any written negotiated agreement signed by User. This Agreement is enforceable against User. If User does not agree to the terms of this Agreement, User shall not be authorised to use this Software.</para_1>


	<para_1><span_smallcaps>Whereas:-</span_smallcaps></para_1>

	<recitals>User desires to copy, install, and/or use this Software; and</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">Legalese desires to demonstrate its software capabilities; but</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">Legalese does not want to get into trouble with the law or with User.</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">User has on [***details of when click-through acknowledgements were entered (just as what Clerky has done)], confirmed the following:-</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">(i)   The Software does not perform any validation or fact checking on behalf of User:  what User types in the Software is exactly what will appear in any of the documents generated.</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">(ii)  Once signed PDFs have been generated on the Software, no further changes can be made to any documents so generated.</recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">(iii) As documents generated by the Software <b>may</b> be or become <b>legally binding documents</b>, it is strongly advised that User proceeds with caution.</recitals>	
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">(iv)  Legalese is <b>not an attorney or a legal adviser</b>. The Software and Legalese (including any of its employees and associates)<b> does not give nor purport to give</b> any legal advice whatsoever. Legalese provides User with the Software and access to self-help materials which are aimed at helping User draft and generate its own documents. For legal advice or review, please seek the assistance of an attorney. </recitals>
	<recitals override="spaceBefore=0">(v)   User understands and accepts Legalese's Terms of Service [***hyperlink this to our TOS which should govern the website's use] and Legalese's Privacy Policy [***hyperlink this]</recitals>
	

	<para_1><span_smallcaps>The Parties agree</span_smallcaps> as follows:-</para_1>

	<a_left_sidehead>DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION</a_left_sidehead>
[***Is there a way to check and automatically add defined terms here? All defined terms would be defined in inverted commas in the document, but it's good practice to have all capitalised terms (i.e. defined terms) set out in one section here. We would also want to automatically arrange them in alphabetical order.]

	<numbered_2_para>“Compatible Computer” means a Computer with the recommended operating system and hardware configuration as stated in the Documentation [Would there need to be one?]. </numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>"Computer" means a virtual or physical device that accepts information in digital or similar form and manipulates it for a specific result based on a sequence of instructions, including without limitation desktop computers, laptops, tablets, mobile devices, telecommunication devices, Internet-connected devices, and hardware products capable of operating a wide variety of productivity, entertainment, or other software applications. </numbered_2_para>

[*** This is something we can potentially integrate/automate too. ]	<numbered_2_para>"Legalese" means Legalese.io Pte Ltd, a Delaware corporation, [address], if this Agreement is entered into while User is in the United States, Canada, or Mexico; otherwise, it means Legalese.io Limited, [address], [Singapore/Ireland?].</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>"Software" means (a) all of the information with which this Agreement is provided, including but not limited to: (i) all software files and other computer information; (ii) any proprietary scripting logic embedded within exported file formats or used in an [in an online service? need technical help here]; (iii) sample and stock documents, images, and other artistic works made available by Legalese on Legalese's website [***hyperlink this?] and not obtained from Legalese through a separate service (unless otherwise noted within that service) or from another party (“Content Files”); (iv) related explanatory written materials and files (“Documentation”); and (v) any software, text, or template content hosted on third-party services including without limitation Google Drive, Github, or such other online or electronic documentation and Internet-based services; and (b) any modified versions and copies of, upgrades, updates, and additions to such information, provided to User by Legalese at any time, to the extent not provided under separate terms (collectively, “Updates”). </numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>"User" means you and any legal entity that obtained the Software and on whose behalf it is used; for example, and as applicable, your employer. 	</numbered_2_para>


<numbered_2_para>The headings in this Agreement are for convenience only and shall not affect the interpretation hereof.</numbered_2_para>

<numbered_2_para>Unless the context otherwise requires, references to the singular number shall include references to the plural number and vice versa, references to natural persons shall include bodies corporate, and the use of any gender shall include all genders.</numbered_2_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Approved Use</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software provided by Legalese is intended to automate the customisation and generation of documents in different formats, including without limitation, <span_smallcaps>XML, PDF</span_smallcaps>, Google Docs, Word, and <span_smallcaps>docx</span_smallcaps>. [***these should be defined or set out in full somewhere for the avoidance of doubt]</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>User affirms that any document customised and/or generated (whether in full or in part) using the Software

 be used to draw up or prepare any documents or instruments intended for execution, lodgment, filing, seal, signature, or delivery, the User either:---</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_3_para>does so personally for himself only in any matter or proceeding to which he is a party;</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is legal counsel (by whatever name called) in an entity acting solely for the entity in a matter to which it is a party;</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is a qualified lawyer currently entitled and certified to practise law in the relevant jurisdiction; or</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>is a person explicitly exempted from the requirements limiting the practise of law to qualified lawyers</numbered_3_para>
	<para_1>(the "Approved Uses").</para_1>

	<a_left_sidehead>Third-Party Services</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>The Legalese Service is being provided over the Internet, in conjunction with third-party services (such as Internet Service, Google Drive, Adobe EchoSign/Document Cloud, DocuSign, HelloSign, or another electronic signature service) which may be offered for a fee, or for an expectation of a fee, gain, or reward. The User agrees that such <b>"Third Party Services"</b> are independent of the Legalese Service.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software may be offered in affiliation with technical support services, business advisory services, corporate secretarial services, information services, or advertising ("Commercial Services"). The User agrees that:</numbered_2_para>
	<numbered_3_para>such services are independent of the Legalese Service;</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>use of the Legalese Service does not entitle the User to Commercial Services; and</numbered_3_para>
	<numbered_3_para>any use of Commercial Services shall not be construed as being made in satisfaction of any expectation of fee, gain, or reward arising from use of the Legalese Service.</numbered_3_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Disclaimer of Warranty</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>There is no warranty for the Software, to the extent permitted by applicable law. Except when otherwise stated in writing the copyright holders and/or other parties provide the Software "as is" without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. The entire risk as to the quality and performance of the Software is with you. Should the Software prove defective, you assume the cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>The Software is not intended to substitute for legal or other professional advice. Templates and contracts, whether generic or customised, may fail to meet the User's needs. Use of the Software does not create a solicitor-client relationship between the User and Legalese, or between the User and anyone else.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>Legalese recommends, and the User understands, that only after consulting a qualified lawyer regarding the particulars of the User's situation, should the User use Legalese to prepare documents under the guidance of such a lawyer. (Unless, of course, the User <i>is</i> a qualified lawyer.)</numbered_2_para>

	<a_left_sidehead>Limitation of Liability</a_left_sidehead>

	<numbered_2_para>In no event unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing will Legalese, any copyright holder, or any other party who modifies and/or conveys the program as permitted above, be liable to the User for damages, including any general, special, incidental or consequential damages arising out of the use or inability to use the program (including but not limited to embarrassment in commerce, loss of money, loss of data, or data being rendered inaccurate or losses sustained by you or third parties or a failure of the program to operate with any other programs), even if such holder or other party has been advised of the possibility of such damages.</numbered_2_para>

	<numbered_2_para>If the Disclaimer of Warranty and Limitation of Liability provided above cannot be given local legal effect according to their terms, reviewing courts, mediators, or arbitrators shall apply local law that most closely approximates an absolute waiver of all civil liability in connection with the Software, unless a warranty or assumption of liability accompanies a copy of the Software in return for a fee.</numbered_2_para>

	<chapter_header>Signature</chapter_header>

	<para_1><?= data.signature_phrase || "Intending to be bound by this Agreement, the User hereby executes this agreement:" ?></para_1>

	<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.user) ?>

  </Story_Main>
</Root>
