<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/" templateSpec="kindle.indt" addnewline="false">
<CoverTop><cover_company_name><?= data.new_participant.name ?></cover_company_name></CoverTop>
<CoverBottom_Logotype><cover_corporate_logotype>legalese.io</cover_corporate_logotype></CoverBottom_Logotype>
<CoverBottom_series><noindent_centered><span_smallcaps>Project Participant Introduction</span_smallcaps>
<textvar name="Output Date" />&#8195;<span_smallcaps><textvar name="output time" /></span_smallcaps>
version <?= data.document_version || "1.0.0" ?></noindent_centered>
</CoverBottom_series>
<Story_Main>
<chapter_header>Your Kindle, compliments of Legalese</chapter_header>
<para_1>Hi there!
If you're reading this, you've been invited to participate in Legalese.io.
Welcome to the project!
This Kindle has been pre-loaded with a handful of important books.
Each full member of the Legalese project has read each of those books.
They explain the soul of the innovation and the business of Legalese, more than just the technology.
This "required reading" helps establish a common understanding and language.
You will get more out of participating in Legalese if you read them too.
(If you know of other books that project members should read, please tell us! We want to learn.)
Not everyone who receives this Kindle will finish all the books.
Only when you do -- if you do -- can you become a full member of the team!
So take your time. When you're ready for us, we'll be ready for you.
But, no matter what happens, this Kindle is yours to keep!
It's a little gift from us to you.</para_1>
<chapter_header>TechCrunch said it, so it must be true.</chapter_header>
<blockquote class="quotation">"These are really smart people,” said one lawyer who works with startups. “They believe in world-domination of the engineering class; everything can be reduced to an algorithm, and legal documents are not going to be spared."</blockquote>
<blockquote class="credit" style="text-align:right">-- TechCrunch, January 10 2015
What It Means When Law Firms And Startups Give Away Legal Documents</blockquote>
<chapter_header>Premises and Insights</chapter_header>
<para_1>Why is Legalese important, and what theories give it power?</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead>Software is Eating Law</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Marc Andreessen once said, "Software is eating the world." Law is a big part of the world, and Legalese plans to take a big bite there.</para_1>
<para_2>Legal writing is often accused of being wordy, incomprehensible, arcane. Shakespeare even said, "The first thing we do, let's kill all the lawyers."
But lawyers aren't dumb or deliberately opaque. They're smart people. They do important work. They're just handicapped when it comes to drafting contracts: they're programmers trying to program without a programming language.</para_2>
<para_1>To be fair, law is a hundred times older than software. The Hammurabic Code was written four thousand years ago in Babylon on stone and clay. Computer code -- software as we know it -- is barely forty years old, written in C and Javascript on invisible computers in the cloud.</para_1>
<para_2>Legalese answers the question: What if programming had been invented <i>before</i> law?
The discovery of perspective revolutionized art. In the same way, computing will transform law.
First, through automation, assembly, and opensource templates.
Next, with computable, formalized agreements that can be understood and executed by computers.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>Full-stack Startup</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Many people coming to this project have professional training in law. Lawyers must remind themselves: Legalese isn't meant for law firms. Legalese <i>competes</i> with law firms, just as Uber competes with taxi companies. We're a <i>full-stack startup</i>.</para_1>
<para_2>(This Kindle's Library contains the blog post in which Chris Dixon first introduced the term.)
Lawyers are certainly welcome to participate in the world that Legalese brings. They may even reap financial gain from doing so. But the goal of Legalese is to serve the end-user -- the consumer of legal services.
We begin with one particular segment: startups.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>The Meta-Startup Trend</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>As the economy orients toward freelancers and startups, the need for low-end legal services -- from simple contracts to incorporation and early-stage fundraising -- is growing. Many more startups are being launched. Many of those startups are raising small amounts of capital. The crowdfunding trend will only increase the number of deals being done.
Indeed, just as the way to a man's heart is through his stomach, the way to a new market is through its startups. Many startups have found success by serving other startups. Heroku, Slack, and even Amazon Web Services have pioneered a winning strategy: find customers when they're young, and grow with them as they scale.</para_1>
<para_2>Even law firms follow this model, in Silicon Valley.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>Low-end Disruption</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>They must, because startups -- the large majority of which haven't (yet) raised millions of dollars -- are notoriously unwilling to pay. For anything. Including law. Rather than see a lawyer, they first download sample documents from the Internet and attempt to adapt them as needed.
Top-tier law firms in the Valley are comfortable taking equity or a promissory note instead of cash, as a ticket to future business. In the rest of the world this model hasn't taken off, and that's where our opportunity lies.
In Clayton Christensen's terms, Legalese competes against nonconsumption. This is a new-market disruption -- and a low-end disruption. These are technical terms explained in <i>The Innovator's Solution</i>, available in the Kindle Library.
The very earliest stage of services are not even legal. They're corporate secretarial services. And that's where we enter.
When a startup turns to the Internet, they'll find us. We will help startups over the hump of incorporation and first fundraising -- for next to no money. (We'll make our money later when the startups are funded.)</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead>Prior Art and Competition</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Of course, we aren't the first to think of this. In recent years, dozens of players have launched apps that offer a variety of solutions: free legal templates; wizard-guided investment agreements; cloud management of cap tables as a service; electronic signature workflows. The list goes on.
Given the crowded field, how is Legalese different?</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead>Global markets</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Most new legal apps serve only the US market; some serve only Europe; some India or Hong Kong.</para_1>
<para_2>Legalese comes out of Singapore -- the Delaware of Southeast Asia. Singapore is where businesses from Indonesia to India go to incorporate, and the demand for incorporation and fundraising here is substantial.
But the true domain of Legalese is the Internet. Like Wikipedia, we aim to support every geography and every language ... and, perhaps, the post-geographic world of Smart Contracts and Bitcoin.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>Opensource, Revision Control, Creative Commons</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Accelerators such as Y Combinator, Techstars, and 500 Startups have published free legal templates for angel and seed fundraising. These templates are typically published in Word format.</para_1>
<para_2>Technically speaking, <span_smallcaps>docx</span_smallcaps> is an open standard, and many of these documents have been released under a more-or-less Creative Commons license, if not public domain.
But Word docs, even with "Track Changes" turned on, are still not amenable to the kind of line-by-line diffing and merging that programmers prefer. In the world of software, opensource and revision control go hand in hand.</para_2>
<para_1>Legalese's native document format is XML, and its documents reside in Github.</para_1>
<para_2>So, if you spot a bug in a contract, don't send redlined "track changes". Send a pull request.
Of course we don't expect everyone to edit XML. Docracy has built a fine interface for end-users to collaboratively edit open-source legals. We might plug in to that, or we might rely on other tools like Google Docs. It's just a simple matter of format translation.</para_2>
<para_1>Legalese's default license is explicitly Creative Commons, and all templates in Legalese are organized by license.</para_1>
<para_1>Openness has its advantages. Just as there is only one Wikipedia, there will be only one Legalese.</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead>Optimizing for Scale</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Most apps work at the level of the individual contract. Fill-in-the-blanks is enough for one-off service agreements and nondisclosures, but it doesn't scale to the dozens of agreements that startups must execute for even the simplest fundraising.</para_1>
<para_2>To even reach the point of raising funds requires dozens of signatures. Each new investor implies dozens more. Over the course of investing in over sixty companies, JFDI.Asia, Singapore's startup accelerator, developed Legalese to serve its own needs. When other people asked to use it, we knew Legalese had a place in the world.
Legalese organizes information about parties in Google Spreadsheets. Parties fill in their details through Google Forms. Legalese reuses those particulars across multiple templates, produces PDFs for review, and sends them to Adobe EchoSign for execution. What used to take months can now take days.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>The Promise of White-collar Automation</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Today's law firms hit don't scale because all their thinking happens inside people's heads. If we can move the thinking into machines -- which is what, in a nutshell, programming is about -- then we can achieve the kinds of economies of scale that technology companies routinely demonstrate: when Whatsapp was acquired for $19 billion, they had 420 million users and only 55 employees.</para_1>
<para_2>Today, a lawyer in a decent-sized law firm might serve a dozen clients, at most a hundred. Imagine if that one lawyer, amplified by technology, could serve a hundred thousand clients instead: it might sound outlandish, but that impact ratio is typical for software engineers. Just as Uber has become the biggest taxi company in the world without owning a single car, Legalese could become the biggest law firm in the world without meeting a single client.</para_2>
<b_left_sidehead>Contract Compilation</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>Template management and document automation is well and good, but to a real computer scientist it's boring -- a solved problem -- basically m4 writ large.
There is a greater goal. On the horizon, the gold at the end of the rainbow, the Holy Grail of this project is <i>formalization</i>.
That's the basis for a research project, which proceeds in parallel with the commercial launch of Legalese.
When that project matures, we will be able to model the parties to a contract, and write a complete contract, in a formal language like Javascript or ML. Legalese will be able to compile programs written in that language to natural language contracts in English, French, German, Chinese, Klingon ... you name it. Contracts that are provably identical, that can be evaluated by machine, that can be visualized against test scenarios, that can be subjected to compile-time formal verification ... that's what makes this project interesting to computer scientists.</para_1>
<b_left_sidehead>The Vision</b_left_sidehead>
<para_1>In a Legalese-powered future, how will life be different?
<b>Incorporation will change.</b> Today, a startup needs a corporate secretary to do the simplest things. The job of a corp sec is pretty routine. It can and should be automated. Filing the memorandum and articles of association; director consents; issue of share certificates. First AGM and basic resolutions.</para_1>
<para_2>With Legalese, all these can be produced using a simple API call.</para_2>
<para_1><b>Founder agreements will change.</b> Today, a startup often neglects the basics -- shareholder agreement, vesting schedule, confidentiality, assignment of IP, non-compete -- until the first round of funding (at which point the absence of documentation delays due diligence) ... or until a crisis occurs -- and everybody wishes they'd bought the insurance before they got sick.</para_1>
<para_2>Legalese provides sensible defaults and easy configuration so founders can get the basic agreements in place, saving time and grief down the road.</para_2>
<para_1><b>Seed investment will change.</b> Today, in the US, angel and seed investors have the nice problem of having dozens of standards to choose from. Outside the US, most investors download a US template pretty much at random, then hack out the US bits and hope the resulting paperwork will be fit for local use.</para_1>
<para_2>Legalese helps parties select the appropriate paperwork from its extensive, global library, with customizations for most common jurisdictions.</para_2>
<para_1><b>The balance of power between lawyer and client will change.</b> Today, customers hire lawyers to draft agreements. Once an agreement is drafted, the client uses it once, while the lawyer is free to use it again (and charge for it again).</para_1>
<para_2>Legalese encourages clients to upload their agreements to the opensource document base, so other clients can benefit from previous work. If a bug is found, a pull request can be filed, and all future users can gain the benefit of the bugfix. This ethos, so basic to opensource, is new to law.</para_2>
<chapter_header>Next Steps</chapter_header>
<para_1>If these ideas resonate, you will need a toolbox of theory and tactical techniques to turn promise into reality.
In the Kindle collection "Required Reading" you will find:</para_1>
<bullets><i>Tomorrow's Lawyers</i>, by Richard Susskind.
<i>Full Stack Startup</i>, by Chris Dixon.
<i>The Innovator's Solution</i>, by Clayton Christensen.
<i>The Nature of Technology</i>, by W. Brian Arthur.
<i>The Art of the Start</i>, by Guy Kawasaki.
<i>Crossing the Chasm</i>, by Geoffrey Moore.
<i>Running Lean</i>, by Ash Maurya.
<i>Startup CEO</i>, by Matt Blumberg.
<i>Reinventing Organizations</i>, by Frederic Laloux.</bullets>
<para_1>If you don't have experience with innovation, these books will teach you how to predict and lead Schumpeterian change.
Legalese is a technology business, and especially if you aren't a programmer, these books will explain how software has an aesthetic of its own, and why that aesthetic is inexorably transforming one industry after another.
If you haven't been in a startup before, you will learn about the importance of building a high-performing learning organization. Unlike in most big companies, everybody on the team is expected to be a leader.
It may take you several weeks or months to absorb all these books. Take your time. These are big ideas -- a whole MBA's worth of theory -- and they take time to digest.
Also, you might notice that this article, and these books, don't talk about specific revenue models or strategies for Legalese. Those are still evolving, under active discussion within the project group.
When you're done, introduce yourself to the project group. Say that you've done the required reading and are ready for what comes next!
We look forward to welcoming you.

On behalf of Team Legalese,
Warm regards,

Meng.
</para_1>
</Story_Main>
</Root>
