<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"Shareholders' Agreement", rcpts_to:rcpts_to}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_jfdi", data, { in_series:"04" }) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar><sidebar>This document governs the relationship between the members of the company.</sidebar></Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header>Shareholders' Agreement</chapter_header>

  <para_1><span_smallcaps>This agreement is dated</span_smallcaps> <?= data.shareholders_agreement_date ?> between:</para_1>
  <?!= include("inc_enumerate_parties", data, rcpts_to, { term:{"new_investor": "purchaser"} }) ?>

  <para_1><span_smallcaps>Whereas:</span_smallcaps></para_1>

<? if (data.previous_shareholder_agreement_date) { ?>
  <recitals>This agreement amends and restates a previous agreement dated <?= data.previous_shareholder_agreement_date ?>.</recitals>
<? } ?>
<recitals>New members are joining the company in relation to an issue of Series Seed Preference Shares.</recitals>
<recitals>To regulate the relationship of the Parties inter se being present and prospective members of the Company, and the conduct of the business and affairs of the Company, <? if (data.parties.existing_investor && data.previously_incorporated && data.previous_investors && data.previous_incorporation_locale && data.previous_incorporation_locale.toLowerCase() != "singapore") { ?>
and to protect the interests of the <?= plural(data.parties.existing_investor, "Existing Investor") ?> by ensuring fair representation in the Company, <? } ?>
in the spirit of mutual confidence and co-operation, the Parties have agreed to enter into this Agreement on the terms and conditions hereinafter set out.</recitals>
  <para_1>Now it is hereby agreed as follows:---</para_1>

  <a_left_sidehead>Definitions</a_left_sidehead>
  <para_1>In this Agreement and in the Recitals abovementioned, unless the context otherwise requires:</para_1>
  <definition>Act	means the Singapore Companies Act (Cap. 50) and includes any provision thereof as from time to time modified or re-enacted;</definition>
  <definition>Agreement	(also <i>Shareholders' Agreement</i>) means this Agreement and shall include all modifications and supplements thereto from time to time in force;</definition>
  <definition>Articles	means the Articles in the Constitution of the Company;</definition>
  <definition>Board	means the board of Directors for the time being of the Company;</definition>
  <definition>Business	means the business of the Company which is high-tech software product and service development;</definition>
  <definition>Change of Control	is as defined in the Articles;</definition>
  <definition>Constitution	means the Constitution of the Company; </definition>
  <definition>Control	means the possession, direct or indirect, of the power to direct or cause the direction of the management and policies of a corporation, whether through the ownership of voting securities, by contract, or otherwise and derivative terms thereof (including <b>"Controlling"</b>, <b>"Controlled by"</b>; and "under common Control with") shall also bear such meaning as aforesaid. For the purpose of this definition, the holding of an interest (within the meaning of the Act) of more than 50% of the equity share capital of the relevant corporation shall be deemed to be "Control" of this corporation;</definition>
  <definition>Deed of Ratification	means a deed of ratification and accession whereby the signatory thereof enters into, becomes a party to and undertakes to be legally bound by the terms of this Agreement;</definition>
  <definition>Director	means a director of the Company for the time being, including where applicable an alternate director;</definition>
  <definition>Equity Sale	means a sale by Shareholders to third party purchaser(s) of all or at least 75% of the Shares of the Company;</definition>
  <definition>External Financing	means a fund-raising event in which the company raises no less than <?= data.qualified_financing_proceeds ?> within one round or series<? if (data.external_financing_after) {?>, and in which the closing date (or the transfer of funds amounting to <?= data.qualified_financing_proceeds ?>) occurs after <?=data.external_financing_after?><? } ?>;</definition>
<? if (data.parties.jfdi_investor) { ?>
<definition>Common Board Member Count	means <?= data.number_directors_common ?>;</definition>
<definition>Mutual Consent Board Member Count	means <?= data.number_directors_jointly ?>;</definition>
<definition>Series Seed Board Member Count	means <?= data.number_directors_seriesseed ?>;</definition>
<definition>Common Control Holders	means the Key Holders who are then providing services to the company as employees or as volunteers.</definition>
  <definition>Investment	means the amount invested in the Company by the Investor in the form of the Convertible Note;</definition>
<?}?>
  <definition>Trade Sale	means a sale of 75% or more of the issued Ordinary share capital of the Company to a third party buyer;</definition>
  <definition>Major Shareholder Dollar Threshold	means $<?= data.major_investor_minimum ?>.</definition>
  <definition>Ordinary Shares	means the ordinary shares in the capital of the Company;</definition>
  <definition>Shareholders	means the Parties named above (excepting the Company) and shall include any other person who holds Shares in the Company and who has executed a Deed of Ratification and thereby become bound by the terms of this Agreement and "Shareholder" means such one of them as the case may be;</definition>
  <definition>Shares	means shares in the capital of the Company whether ordinary or preferred;</definition>
  <definition>S$ or $	means the lawful currency for the time being of the Republic of Singapore; and</definition>
  <para_1>Except where the context otherwise requires, words importing the singular include the plural and vice versa, words importing a gender include every gender and references to persons include bodies corporate or unincorporated, any state or any agency thereof and any other entity.</para_1>
  <para_1>Headings, marginal sidenotes, and graphic art are for ease of reference only and have no legal effect. Reference to Clauses are to Clauses of this Agreement and references to this Agreement includes any amendments or supplementals thereto.</para_1>
  <para_1>Except where the context otherwise requires, references to any person include its successors and permitted assignees.</para_1>
  <para_1>References in this Agreement to a time of day are to Singapore time.</para_1>
  <para_1>Any document expressed to be in the "approved form" means a document in the form or substantially in the form approved by (and signed for identification by or on behalf of) the Parties.</para_1>
  <para_1>Except where the context otherwise requires, Clauses which refer to the "Company" shall apply mutatis mutandis to subsidiaries or successors of the Company which may from time to time be established.</para_1>
  <para_1>Any reference in this Agreement to a Shareholder procuring and derivative terms thereof (including "shall procure"), shall only oblige the Shareholder to exercise its voting rights in the Company to vote in favour of the Company performing its obligation as required.</para_1>
  <para_1>This Agreement shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore.</para_1>

  <a_left_sidehead>Effective Date</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="2.1">This Agreement shall come into effect following Completion of the Series Seed Preference Shares Investment Agreements with the New Investors.</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="2.2">At that time any previous Shareholder Agreements will be superseded and replaced in its entirety by this Agreement.</numbered_2_para>

  
<? if (! data.no_class_f) { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Class F Shares</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_para>The Shareholders acknowledge that Class F redeemable preference shares have been issued to the following Shareholders, on the terms of Class F Agreements which have been entered into between the Company and each such Shareholder. Each Class F Agreement, together with the Constitution, sets out the respective rights and obligations attached to the Class F Shares held by such holder of Class F Shares, including the Company’s rights of redemption over the Class F Shares and the timing and conditions on which such rights of redemption shall be waived.  Each holder of Class F Shares and the Company hereby agrees that the terms of the Class F Agreements shall be deemed incorporated into this Agreement by reference, and undertakes that it shall not waive, vary or terminate the Class F Agreements without the prior written consent of the holders of at least a majority of the Series Seed Preferred Shares.</numbered_2_para>

  <? xmLog("shareholders_agreement/class_f_shares: calling data.capTable.getActiveRound()"); ?>
  <? var classFholders  = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getPreviousRound().by_security_type["Class F Shares"]; ?>
  <? if (classFholders) {
	delete classFholders.TOTAL;
	delete classFholders.ESOP;
  ?>
  <? xmLog("shareholders_agreement/class_f_holders: found class F holders = %s", classFholders); ?>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="2" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(classFholders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Holdings</cell_c></Cell>
<? for (var hh in classFholders) {
  if (data._entitiesByName[hh] == undefined) { continue }
  with(data._entitiesByName[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= hh ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!=   data.capTable.investorHoldingsInRound(hh, previousRound) ?></cell_c></Cell>
<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>
<? } ?>



<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Waiver of pre-emptive rights</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
  <numbered_2_para>The Parties hereby waive their pre-emptive rights with regard to the issue of new Class F Shares provided that such issue occurs either as part of a vesting scheme or some other share option plan, share ownership plan, or equity-based remuneration scheme previously approved by the Company, or pursuant to a Compensation Adjustment and at the Discretionary Subscription Price as described in the Class F Agreement and the Constitution respectively.</numbered_2_para>
  <? } ?>

  <?!= include("rm_tags", data) ?>


  
  <a_left_sidehead>New Parties</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para orig_num="47" xname="fev_sha_dora_required">It shall be a condition precedent to the issuance of new shares by the Company to a third party that such third party shall be required to execute the Deed of Ratification and Accession under which it agrees to be bound by and be entitled to the benefit of this Agreement as if it were an original party thereto.</numbered_2_para>

<? if (data.parties.investor) { ?>
  <numbered_2_para>Any party who is a holder of Convertible Debt and not a Shareholder, upon conversion whether in whole or in part, shall be deemed to have ratified and acceded to this Agreement.</numbered_2_para>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead>Transferability of Rights</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Constitution give shareholders pre-emptive rights (on the issue of new securities) and rights of first refusal (to purchase existing securities). These rights shall be transferable on a commercial basis, so that if a deal is oversubscribed, each holder of shares or convertible instruments can delegate their position to one or more favourite investors.</numbered_2_para>
<? if (data.previously_incorporated) { ?>

<a_left_sidehead>Related Companies and Existing Proprietary Assets</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>Pursuant to the Founder Agreement, should the Founders jointly or severally control an existing business (the "Previous Company") whose proprietary assets will be used in the Company's current business, then those Founders shall, at the election of the Investor but in any event prior to the Next External Financing defined in the <?=data.security_type?> Agreement of <?= data.investment_agreement_date ?>, procure</numbered_2_para>
  <bullets>the transfer of those assets, or
the transfer of controlling equity in that existing business, or
a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, exclusive, worldwide license of the Previous Company's assets</bullets>
<para_2>to the Company for a nominal fee.</para_2>
<? } ?>

<? if (data.previously_incorporated && data.previous_incorporation_locale && data.previous_incorporation_locale.toLowerCase() != "singapore") { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>New Investors' Interests to be Protected</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para xname="protect_new_investors">Given that the capital appreciation of the business shall henceforth inhere in the Company <?= data.company.name ?>, the Parties agree that the Previous Company <?= data.parties.previous_company[0].name ?> shall not seek further investment from external investors, and that any external investment shall be directed toward the Company instead. The Founders<? if (data.previous_investors) { ?> and Existing Investors<?}?> hereby agree that, to the extent that they have any interest in or influence over the actions of the Previous Company, they shall act in accordance with this Clause <xref to="protect_new_investors" />.</numbered_2_para>
<? } ?>


<? if (data.previously_incorporated && data.previous_investors
       && data.previous_incorporation_locale && data.previous_incorporation_locale.toLowerCase() != "singapore") { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Existing Investors' Interests to be Protected</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>Prior to the Next External Financing, the Company shall issue and allot shares or other securities so as to represent the interests of the Existing Investors, who hold shares in the Previous Company <?= data.parties.previous_company[0].name ?>, and the Founders shall act accordingly.</numbered_2_para>
<? } ?>

<? if (data.significant_corporate_matters) { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Significant Corporate Matters</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_para>These matters may not be acted upon by a Director or officer of the Company or by any of the parties without the authority of <?= data.scm_authority ?>:</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Company ceasing to carry on the Business or a substantial part of the Business, or a decision to wind up or dissolve the Company;
the merger of all or a significant part of the Business or the Company with any other entity;
any reorganisation, reclassification, reconstruction, consolidation or subdivision of the share capital of the Company or the creation of different classes of securities in the capital of the Company or the introduction of new share capital into the Company;
capital expenditure decisions involving amounts in excess of <?= data.scm_max_spend ?>;
the sale, transfer or disposition by the Company of any asset valued in excess of <?= data.scm_max_spend ?>;
any assignment, or the grant of any licence, by the Company of its intellectual property rights;
the entry into or the incurring of any debts or liabilities including guarantees, indemnities, or the grant of any charge or encumbrance over any assets of the Company in excess of <?= data.scm_max_spend ?>;
the making of any loan or advance by the Company;
the appointment of a managing Director or any modification to the terms or conditions of employment of the managing Director;
entering into or varying contracts with Directors, Shareholders of the Company or any related entity;
any alteration to the composition of the Board that is not contemplated in this agreement; and
any distribution of profits of the Company.</numbered_3_para>
<? } ?>

<? if (data.reserved_matters) { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Reserved Matters</a_left_sidehead>
<?!= data.reserved_matters ?>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead>Alterations Due to External Financing</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>A prospective investor may seek to alter both this Agreement and the Constitution as a condition of External Financing.</numbered_2_para>

  <? if(data.no_further_obligation) {?>
  <numbered_2_para>Provided that it has paid the subscription price for its Series Seed Preference Shares in full, and without prejudice to its rights to participate in future issuances of new securities and rights of first refusal on the transfer of Shares, none of the Purchasers shall be obligated or liable to make any further payments or other contribution, including as capital contribution (whether as participation in an External Financing or otherwise), or by way of loan, or any other contribution towards the working capital and expenses of the Company or any further payment in connection with the Shares at any time held by it or pursuant to this Shareholders’ Agreement, or any other support (such as undertakings, guarantees, securities or otherwise) which may be required by any relevant financier as a condition in relation to any external borrowings by the Company.</numbered_2_para>
  <? } ?>

  <a_left_sidehead>Humility</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Founders acknowledge that the business may outgrow them, and that their primary commitment is to the success of the business. Should, one day, other leadership and management be better suited, the Founders agree to be reminded of this commitment.</numbered_2_para>
  <a_left_sidehead>Regarding Death and Disability</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>As soon as practical, after or in preparation for an External Financing, the Company shall purchase what is commonly called "Key Man" insurance, such that in the event of Death or Disability of a Founder, whether that Founder is indeed a Man or a Woman, the Company can afford to continue operations in the absence of that Founder.</numbered_2_para>

  <para_1>Should the Company not raise External Financing, but recognize total revenue of at least S$250,000, then this provision shall apply with equal force.</para_1>


<? // this material moved over from the series seed investment agreement. ?>
<a_left_sidehead xname="ss_covenants_company">Covenants of the Company</a_left_sidehead>

<b_left_sidehead>Information Rights.</b_left_sidehead>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Basic Financial Information. The Company shall furnish to each Shareholder who paid the Major Shareholder Dollar Threshold, or more, (a "Major Shareholder") and any entity that requires such information pursuant to its organizational documents (1) annual unaudited financial statements for each fiscal year of the Company, including an unaudited balance sheet as of the end of such fiscal year, an unaudited income statement, and an unaudited statement of cash flows, all prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles and practices<? if (data.financial_submission_deadlines) { ?>, within 60 days of the end of each fiscal year<?}?>; and (2) quarterly unaudited financial statements for each fiscal quarter of the Company (except the last quarter of the Company's fiscal year), including an unaudited balance sheet as of the end of such fiscal quarter, an unaudited income statement, and an unaudited statement of cash flows, all prepared in accordance with generally accepted accounting principles and practices, subject to changes resulting from normal year-end audit adjustments<? if (data.financial_submission_deadlines) { ?>, within 60 days of the end of each fiscal quarter<?}?>. If the Company has audited records of any of the foregoing, it shall provide those in lieu of the unaudited versions.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_3_firstbold_fl xname="ss_confidentiality">Confidentiality. Anything in this Agreement to the contrary notwithstanding, no Shareholder by reason of this Agreement shall have access to any trade secrets or confidential information of the Company. The Company shall not be required to comply with any information rights of any Shareholder whom the Company reasonably determines to be a competitor or an officer, employee, director, or holder of ten percent (10%) or more of a competitor. Each Shareholder shall keep confidential and shall not disclose, divulge, or use for any purpose (other than to monitor its investment in the Company) any confidential information obtained from the Company pursuant to the terms of this Agreement other than <? if (data.extended_disclosure) {?>(if the Shareholder is a corporation) to any of the Shareholder's (and the Shareholder's related corporations') shareholders, employees, and officers; (if the Shareholder is an individual) to the Shareholder's immediate family members; and <?}?>to any of the Shareholder's attorneys, accountants, consultants, and other professionals, to the extent necessary to obtain their services in connection with monitoring the Shareholder's investment in the Company.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>
<numbered_3_firstbold_fl>Inspection Rights. The Company shall permit each Major Shareholder to visit and inspect the Company's properties, to examine its books of account and records and to discuss the Company's affairs, finances and accounts with its officers, all at such reasonable times as may be requested by such Major Shareholder.</numbered_3_firstbold_fl>

<numbered_2_firstbold>Additional Rights and Obligations. If the Company issues securities in its next equity financing after the date hereof (the "Next Financing") that (a) have rights, preferences or privileges that are more favorable than the terms of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock, such as price-based anti-dilution protection, or (b) provide all such future investors other contractual terms such as registration rights, the Company shall provide substantially equivalent rights to the Shareholders with respect to the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (with appropriate adjustment for economic terms or other contractual rights), subject to such Shareholder's execution of any documents, including, if applicable, investor rights, co-sale, voting, and other agreements, executed by the investors purchasing securities in the Next Financing (such documents, the "Next Financing Documents"). Any Major Shareholder will remain a Major Shareholder for all purposes in the Next Financing Documents to the extent such concept exists. The Company shall pay the reasonable fees and expenses, not to exceed $5,000 in the aggregate, of one counsel for the Shareholders in connection with the Shareholders' review, execution, and delivery of the Next Financing Documents. Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, subject to the provisions of Section <xref to="ss_termination" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/>, upon the execution and delivery of the Next Financing Documents by Shareholders holding a majority of the then-outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock held by all Shareholders, this Agreement (excluding any then-existing and outstanding obligations) shall be amended and restated by and into such Next Financing Documents and shall be terminated and of no further force or effect.</numbered_2_firstbold>

<numbered_2_firstbold>Trademark Filing. As at the date hereof, the Company has filed an application for registration of trade mark for the "<?=data.trademark_filing?>" mark with the Registrar of Trade Marks in Singapore. The parties agree that if the aforesaid application is not accepted for registration, or if accepted, is opposed by any third party or is refused or revoked by the Registrar, whether in whole or in part, the Company shall change its logo, mark, name, domain name, social media account name and/or any other associated intellectual property, if and to the extent required by <?= data.parties.new_investor[1].name ?> and notified to the Company (“Rebranding”). The Company shall, and each Key Holder shall procure that the Company will, do all things necessary to give effect to the Rebranding, including making all applicable filings, registrations and applications to ensure that following the Rebranding, the Company will own and possess all intellectual property rights necessary for the conduct of the Business without any violation or infringement of the rights of others. Without prejudice to the foregoing, each Shareholder shall exercise all voting and other rights and powers available to them so as to give effect to the Rebranding including to procure any change of name of the Company.</numbered_2_firstbold>

<? if (data.company_has_preemptive_rights) {?>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Assignment of Company's Preemptive Rights. The Company shall obtain at or prior to the Initial Closing, and shall maintain, a right of first refusal with respect to transfers of shares of Common Stock by each holder thereof, subject to certain standard exceptions. If the Company elects not to exercise its right of first refusal with respect to a proposed transfer of the Company's outstanding securities by any Key Holder, the Company shall assign such right of first refusal to the Major Shareholders. In the event of such assignment, each Major Shareholder shall have a right to purchase that portion of the securities proposed to be transferred by such Key Holder equal to the ratio of (a) the number of shares of the Company's Common Stock issued or issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock owned by such Major Shareholder, to (b) the number of shares of the Company's Common Stock issued or issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock owned by all Major Shareholders.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<?}?>

<? if (data.reservation_of_common_stock_required) { ?>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Reservation of Common Stock. The Company shall at all times reserve and keep available, solely for issuance and delivery upon the conversion of the Series Seed Preferred Stock, all Common Stock issuable from time to time upon conversion of that number of shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock equal to the Total Shares Authorized for Sale, regardless of whether or not all such shares have been issued at such time.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead>Covenants of the Key Holders</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_para>Within 30 business days of the Effective Date, each Key Holder shall execute employment agreements with the Company, which agreements shall be approved by a Board composed as described in clause <xref to="ss_election_of_board" />, or else forfeit all his Restricted Class F Shares.</numbered_2_para>


<a_left_sidehead>RESTRICTIONS ON TRANSFER; DRAG ALONG.</a_left_sidehead>

<? if (data.limitations_on_disposition) {?>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Limitations on Disposition. Each person owning of-record shares of Common Stock of the Company issued or issuable pursuant to the conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock and any shares of Common Stock of the Company issued as a dividend or other distribution with respect thereto or in exchange therefor or in replacement thereof (collectively, the "Securities") or any assignee of record of Securities (each such person, a "Holder") shall not make any disposition of all or any portion of any Securities unless:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para xname="ss_prospectus_registered">there is then in effect a prospectus registered under the Securities Act covering such proposed disposition and such disposition is made in accordance with such prospectus; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para xname="ss_disposition_notified">such Holder has notified the Company of the proposed disposition and has furnished the Company with a statement of the circumstances surrounding the proposed disposition, and, at the expense of such Holder or its transferee, with an opinion of counsel, reasonably satisfactory to the Company, that such disposition will not require registration of such securities under the Securities Act.</numbered_3_para>
<para_1>Notwithstanding the provisions of Sections <xref to="ss_prospectus_registered"/> and <xref to="ss_disposition_notified"/>, no such prospectus or opinion of counsel will be required: (i) for any transfer of any Securities, if to an American person, in compliance with the US Securities and Exchange Commission's Rule 144 or Rule 144A, or (ii) for any transfer of any Securities by a Holder that is a partnership, limited liability company, a corporation, or a venture capital fund to (A) a partner of such partnership, a member of such limited liability company, or stockholder of such corporation, (B) an affiliate of such partnership, limited liability company or corporation (including, any affiliated investment fund of such Holder), (C) a retired partner of such partnership or a retired member of such limited liability company, (D) the estate of any such partner, member, or stockholder, or (iii) for the transfer without additional consideration or at no greater than cost by gift, will, or intestate succession by any Holder to the Holder's spouse or lineal descendants or ancestors or any trust for any of the foregoing; provided that, in the case of clauses (ii) and (iii), the transferee agrees in writing to be subject to the terms of this Agreement to the same extent as if the transferee were an original Shareholder under this Agreement.</para_1>
<? } ?>

<numbered_2_firstbold>"Market Stand-Off" Agreement. To the extent requested by the Company or an underwriter of securities of the Company, each Holder shall not sell or otherwise transfer or dispose of any Securities or other shares of stock of the Company then owned by such Holder (other than to donees or partners of the Holder who agree to be similarly bound) for up to 180 days following the effective date of any prospectus of the Company filed under the Securities Act.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_drag">Drag Along Right. If a Deemed Liquidation Event (as defined in the Amended Constitution) is approved by each of (i) the holders of a majority of the shares of Common Stock then outstanding (other than those issued or issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock), (ii) the holders of a majority of the shares of Common Stock then issued or issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock then outstanding and (iii) the Board, then each Stockholder shall vote (in person, by proxy or by action by written consent, as applicable) all shares of capital stock of the Company now or hereafter directly or indirectly owned of record or beneficially by such Stockholder (collectively, the "Shares") in favor of, and adopt, such Deemed Liquidation Event and to execute and deliver all related documentation and take such other action in support of the Deemed Liquidation Event as may reasonably be requested by the Company to carry out the terms and provision of this Section <xref to="ss_drag" />, including executing and delivering instruments of conveyance and transfer, and any purchase agreement, merger agreement, indemnity agreement, escrow agreement, consent, waiver, governmental filing, share certificates duly endorsed for transfer (free and clear of impermissible liens, claims and encumbrances) and any similar or related documents. The obligation of any party to take the actions required by this Section <xref to="ss_drag" /> will not apply to a Deemed Liquidation Event if the other party involved in such Deemed Liquidation Event is an affiliate or stockholder of the Company holding more than 10% of the voting power of the Company. "Stockholder" means each Holder and Key Holder, and any transferee thereof.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Exceptions to Drag Along Right. Notwithstanding the foregoing, a Stockholder need not comply with Section <xref to="ss_drag" /> above in connection with any proposed Sale of the Company (the "Proposed Sale") unless:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>any representations and warranties to be made by the Stockholder in connection with the Proposed Sale are limited to representations and warranties related to authority, ownership and the ability to convey title to such Shares, including representations and warranties that (i) the Stockholder holds all right, title and interest in and to the Shares the Stockholder purports to hold, free and clear of all liens and encumbrances, (ii) the obligations of the Stockholder in connection with the transaction have been duly authorized, if applicable, (iii) the documents to be entered into by the Stockholder have been duly executed by the Stockholder and delivered to the acquirer and are enforceable against the Stockholder in accordance with their respective terms and, (iv) neither the execution and delivery of documents to be entered into in connection with the transaction, nor the performance of the Stockholder's obligations thereunder, will cause a breach or violation of the terms of any agreement, law, or judgment, order, or decree of any court or governmental agency;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the Stockholder will not be liable for the inaccuracy of any representation or warranty made by any other Person in connection with the Proposed Sale (except to the extent that funds may be paid out of an escrow established to cover breach of representations, warranties, and covenants of the Company);</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>the liability for indemnification, if any, of the Stockholder in the Proposed Sale and for the inaccuracy of any representations and warranties made by the Company or its Stockholders in connection with such Proposed Sale, is several and not joint with any other Person (except to the extent that funds may be paid out of an escrow established to cover breach of representations, warranties and covenants of the Company as well as breach by any stockholder of any identical representations, warranties, and covenants provided by all stockholders), and except as required to satisfy the liquidation preference of the Series Seed Preferred Stock, if any, is pro rata in proportion to, and does not exceed, the amount of consideration paid to such Stockholder in connection with such Proposed Sale;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>liability will be limited to the Stockholder's applicable share (determined based on the respective proceeds payable to each Stockholder in connection with the Proposed Sale in accordance with the provisions of the Amended Constitution) of a negotiated aggregate indemnification amount that applies equally to all Stockholders but that in no event exceeds the amount of consideration otherwise payable to the Stockholder in connection with the Proposed Sale, except with respect to claims related to fraud by the Stockholder, the liability for which need not be limited as to the Stockholder;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>upon the consummation of the Proposed Sale, (i) each holder of each class or series of the Company's stock will receive the same form of consideration for their shares of such class or series as is received by other holders in respect of their shares of such same class or series of stock unless the holders of at least a majority of Series Seed Preferred Stock elect otherwise, (ii) each holder of a series of Series Seed Preferred Stock will receive the same amount of consideration per share of such series of Series Seed Preferred Stock as is received by other holders in respect of their shares of such same series, (iii) each holder of Common Stock will receive the same amount of consideration per share of Common Stock as is received by other holders in respect of their shares of Common Stock, and (iv) unless the holders of at least a majority of the Series Seed Preferred Stock elect to receive a lesser amount, the aggregate consideration receivable by all holders of the Preferred Stock and Common Stock shall be allocated among the holders of Preferred Stock and Common Stock on the basis of the relative liquidation preferences to which the holders of each respective series of Preferred Stock and the holders of Common Stock are entitled in a Deemed Liquidation Event (assuming for this purpose that the Proposed Sale is a Deemed Liquidation Event) in accordance with the Company's Amended Constitution in effect immediately prior to the Proposed Sale.</numbered_3_para>

<? if (data.ia_spells_out_participation_right) {?>
<a_left_sidehead xname="ss_participation_right">Participation RIGHT.</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_firstbold>General. Each Major Shareholder has the right of first refusal to purchase the Major Shareholder's Pro Rata Share of any New Securities (as defined below) that the Company may from time to time issue after the date of this Agreement, provided, however, the Major Shareholder will have no right to purchase any such New Securities if the Major Shareholder cannot demonstrate to the Company's reasonable satisfaction that such Major Shareholder is at the time of the proposed issuance of such New Securities an "accredited investor" as such term is defined in Section 4A of the Securities Act. A Major Shareholder's "Pro Rata Share" for means the ratio of (a) the number of shares of the Company's Common Stock issued or issuable upon conversion of the shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock owned by such Major Shareholder, to (b) the Fully-Diluted Share Number.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>New Securities. "New Securities" means any Common Stock or Preferred Stock, whether now authorized or not, and rights, options or warrants to purchase Common Stock or Preferred Stock, and securities of any type whatsoever that are, or may become, convertible or exchangeable into Common Stock or Preferred Stock; provided, however, that "New Securities" does not include: (a) shares of Common Stock issued or issuable upon conversion of any outstanding shares of Preferred Stock; (b) shares of Common Stock or Preferred Stock issuable upon exercise of any options, warrants, or rights to purchase any securities of the Company outstanding as of the Agreement Date and any securities issuable upon the conversion thereof; (c) shares of Common Stock or Preferred Stock issued in connection with any stock split or stock dividend or recapitalization; (d) shares of Common Stock (or options, warrants or rights therefor) granted or issued after the Agreement Date to volunteers, employees, officers, directors, contractors, consultants or advisers to, the Company or any subsidiary of the Company pursuant to incentive agreements, stock purchase or stock option plans, stock bonuses or awards, warrants, contracts or other arrangements that are approved by the Board; (e) shares of the Company's Series Seed Preferred Stock issued pursuant to this Agreement; (f) any other shares of Common Stock or Preferred Stock (and/or options or warrants therefor) issued or issuable primarily for other than equity financing purposes and approved by the Board; and (g) shares of Common Stock issued or issuable by the Company to the public pursuant to a prospectus registered under the Securities Act.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Procedures. If the Company proposes to undertake an issuance of New Securities, it shall give notice to each Major Shareholder of its intention to issue New Securities (the "Notice"), describing the type of New Securities and the price and the general terms upon which the Company proposes to issue the New Securities. Each Major Shareholder will have (10) days from the date of notice, to agree in writing to purchase such Major Shareholder's Pro Rata Share of such New Securities for the price and upon the general terms specified in the Notice by giving written notice to the Company and stating therein the quantity of New Securities to be purchased (not to exceed such Major Shareholder's Pro Rata Share).</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Failure to Exercise. If the Major Shareholders fail to exercise in full the right of first refusal within the 10 day period, then the Company will have one hundred twenty (120) days thereafter to sell the New Securities with respect to which the Major Shareholders' rights of first refusal hereunder were not exercised, at a price and upon general terms not materially more favorable to the purchasers thereof than specified in the Company's Notice to the Major Shareholders. If the Company has not issued and sold the New Securities within the 120 day period, then the Company shall not thereafter issue or sell any New Securities without again first offering those New Securities to the Major Shareholders pursuant to this Section <xref to="ss_participation_right"/>.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead xname="ss_election_of_board">ELECTION OF BOARD OF DIRECTORS.</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Voting; Board Composition. Subject to the rights of the stockholders to remove a director for cause in accordance with applicable law, during the term of this Agreement, each Stockholder shall vote (or consent pursuant to an action by written consent of the stockholders) all shares of capital stock of the Company now or hereafter directly or indirectly owned of record or beneficially by the Stockholder (the "Voting Shares"), or to cause the Voting Shares to be voted, in such manner as may be necessary to elect (and maintain in office) as the members of the Board:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para xname="ss_common_board_designees">that number of individuals, if any, equal to the Common Board Member Count (collectively, the "Common Board Designees") designated from time to time in a writing delivered to the Company and signed by the members who then hold shares of issued and outstanding Common Stock of the Company representing a majority of the voting power of all issued and outstanding shares of Common Stock;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para xname="ss_series_seed_board_designees">that number of individuals, if any, equal to the Series Seed Board Member Count (collectively, the "Series Seed Board Designees") designated from time to time in a writing delivered to the Company and signed by Shareholders who then hold a majority of the then-outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para xname="ss_mutual_consent_board_designees">that number of individuals, if any, equal to the Mutual Consent Board Member Count (collectively, the "Mutual Consent Board Designees" and, together with any Common Board Designee and any Seed Board Designee, each a "Board Designee") designated from time to time in a writing delivered to the Company and signed by (a) members who then hold a majority of then-outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock and (b) Common Control Holders who then hold shares of issued and outstanding Common Stock of the Company representing a majority of the voting power of all issued and outstanding shares of Common Stock of the Company.</numbered_3_para>
<para_1>Subject to the rights of the stockholders of the Company to remove a director for cause in accordance with applicable law, during the term of this Agreement, a Stockholder shall not take any action to remove an incumbent Board Designee or to designate a new Board Designee unless such removal or designation of a Board Designee is approved in a writing signed by the parties entitled to designate the Board Designee.</para_1>
<? if (data.ceo_has_proxy) {?>
<numbered_2_para xname="ss_ceo_has_proxy">Each Stockholder hereby appoints, and shall appoint, the then-current Chief Executive Officer of the Company, as the Stockholder's true and lawful proxy and attorney, with the power to act alone and with full power of substitution, to vote all shares of the Company's capital stock held by the Stockholder as set forth in this Agreement and to execute all appropriate instruments consistent with this Agreement on behalf of the Stockholder if, and only if, the Stockholder (a) fails to vote or (b) attempts to vote (whether by proxy, in person or by written consent), in a manner which is inconsistent with the terms of this Agreement, all of the Stockholder's Voting Shares or execute such other instruments in accordance with the provisions of this Agreement within five days of the Company's or any other party's written request for the Stockholder's written consent or signature. The proxy and power granted by each Stockholder pursuant to this Section are coupled with an interest and are given to secure the performance of the Stockholder's duties under this Agreement. Each such proxy and power will be irrevocable for the term of this Agreement. The proxy and power, so long as any Stockholder is an individual, will survive the death, incompetency and disability of such Stockholder and, so long as any Stockholder is an entity, will survive the merger or reorganization of the Stockholder or any other entity holding Voting Shares.</numbered_2_para>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead name="ss_misc">Miscellaneous Provisions</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_sha_a_and_w">Amendments and Waivers. Any term of this Agreement may be amended, terminated or waived (either generally or in a particular instance and either retroactively or prospectively) only with the written consent of the Company and the Shareholders holding a majority of the then-outstanding shares of Series Seed Preferred Stock (or Common Stock issued on conversion thereof); provided, however, that any amendment to Section <xref to="ss_common_board_designees" /> (Common Board Designees) or Section <xref to="ss_mutual_consent_board_designees" /> (Mutual Consent Board Designees) will, in addition to any other consents required, also require the written consent of the holders of a majority of the outstanding shares of the Company's Common Stock then held by all of the Common Control Holders.</numbered_2_firstbold>

<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_termination">Termination. Unless terminated earlier pursuant to the terms of this Agreement,</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>the rights, duties and obligations under Sections <xref to="ss_covenants_company"/><?if(data.ia_spells_out_participation_right){?>, <xref to="ss_participation_right"/><?}?> and <xref to="ss_election_of_board"/> will terminate immediately prior to the closing of the Company's initial public offering of Common Stock pursuant to an effective prospectus registered under the Securities Act,</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, this Agreement (excluding any then-existing obligations) will terminate upon the closing of a Deemed Liquidation Event as defined in the Company's Amended Constitution, as amended from time to time; and</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Section <xref to="ss_confidentiality" format="Paragraph Number (firstbold)"/> will survive any termination of this Agreement.</numbered_3_para>

<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ss_priority">Priority. In the event of any ambiguity or discrepancy between the provisions of this Agreement and the Constitution, then the provisions of this Agreement shall prevail and accordingly the parties shall exercise all voting and other rights and powers available to them so as to give effect to the provisions of this Agreement and shall further if necessary procure any required amendment to the said Constitution.</numbered_2_firstbold>
  
  <chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>
  <para_1><span_smallcaps>In witness whereof</span_smallcaps> we have hereunto set our hand on <?= data.shareholders_agreement_date ?></para_1>

  <?!= include("inc_enumerate_signatures", data, {rcpts_to:rcpts_to, _include2: {} }) ?>

  <schedule_header>Table of Investors</schedule_header>
  <? xmLog("shareholders_agreement/existing_investors: calling data.capTable.getActiveRound()"); ?>
  <? var oldInvestors  = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getOldInvestors(); ?>
  <? var previousRound = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getPreviousRound(); ?>
<? if (previousRound != undefined && oldInvestors != undefined) { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Existing Investors</a_left_sidehead>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="3" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(oldInvestors.holders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Address</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Holdings</cell_c></Cell>
<? for (var hh in oldInvestors.holders) { with(data._entitiesByName[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= hh ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= address ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!=   data.capTable.investorHoldingsInRound(hh, previousRound) ?></cell_c></Cell>
<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>
<? } ?>

<a_left_sidehead>Investors Receiving New Securities</a_left_sidehead>
  <? var newIssues = data.capTable.getActiveRound().getNewIssues(); ?>

<para_1><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="3" aid:trows="<?= Object.keys(newIssues.holders).length+1 ?>" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Name</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>Address</cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_none"><cell_c>New Issues</cell_c></Cell>
<? for (var hh in newIssues.holders) { with(data._entitiesByName[hh]) { ?>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= hh ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="140" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?= address ?></cell_c></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="100" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="horizontal_hairline"><cell_c><?!= newIssues.holders[hh]._inWords ?></cell_c></Cell>
<? } } ?>
</Table></para_1>

</Story_Main>
</Root>
