<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/">

  <Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>This document records the legal rights and liabilities attaching to Series YC-AA Convertible Preference Shares. This agreement is modeled on on the Series AA model documents published by Y Combinator.</sidebar>
  </Firstpage_Sidebar>

<Story_Main>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Series YC-AA Convertible Preference Shares </b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_1_para xname="ycaa">The Company may issue <b>Series YC-AA Shares</b> in the capital of the Company, at an issue price of S$0.00001 each or such other amount as the Directors may determine, which shall carry the following rights, benefits and privileges and be subject to the following restrictions: </numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards issue. YC-AA Shares may be issued with the sanction of an ordinary resolution pursuant to agreements between the Company and individual holders (within this Article <xref to="ycaa" />, the "Subscription Agreements"), the terms of which the Directors may determine. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards redemption. YC-AA Shares shall not be redeemable.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards conversion. A Holder of YC-AA Shares shall have the right to convert those shares to ordinary shares at the Conversion Ratio at any time. The Conversion Ratio shall be one-for-one, adjusted for:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Summary.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>Anti-Dilution: If, subsequent to the issue of a YC-AA Share, any ordinary or preference shares are issued at an effective (fully-diluted) price per (post-conversion or post-exercise) share lower than the price per share paid for the YC-AA Share, then the Conversion Ratio shall be adjusted according to a standard broad-based weighted-average anti-dilution formula to produce more ordinary shares.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Recapitalization due to any stock dividend, stock split, combination of shares, reorganization, recapitalization, reclassification, repurchase, redemption, cancellation, or other similar event.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Details.</numbered_2_firstbold> // addition of actual wording. //
<numbered_3_firstbold>Special Definition. For purposes of this paragraph 3(d), “Additional Shares of Common” shall mean all shares of Common Stock issued (or, pursuant to paragraph 3(d)(iii), deemed to be issued) by the Corporation after the filing of this Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation, other than issuances or deemed issuances of shares of Common Stock:</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_4_para>upon the conversion of the Preferred Stock;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>and options, warrants or other rights to purchase Common Stock issued or issuable to employees, officers or directors of, or consultants or advisors to the Corporation or any subsidiary pursuant to stock grants, restricted stock purchase agreements, option plans, purchase plans, incentive programs or similar arrangements;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>upon the exercise or conversion of Options or Convertible Securities;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable as a dividend or distribution on Preferred Stock or pursuant to any event for which adjustment is made pursuant to paragraph 3(d), 3(g) or 3(h) hereof;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable in a registered public offering under the Securities Act;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable pursuant to the acquisition of another corporation by the Corporation by merger, purchase of substantially all of the assets or other reorganization or to a joint venture agreement, provided, that such issuances are approved by the Board of Directors;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable to banks, equipment lessors, real property lessors, financial institutions or other persons engaged in the business of making loans pursuant to a debt financing, commercial leasing or real property leasing transaction approved by the Board of Directors;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable in connection with any settlement of any action, suit, proceeding or litigation approved by the Board of Directors;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable in connection with sponsored research, collaboration, technology license, development, OEM, marketing or other similar agreements or strategic partnerships approved by the Board of Directors; and</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>issued or issuable to suppliers or third party service providers in connection with the provision of goods or services pursuant to transactions approved by the Board of Directors.</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_3_firstbold>No Adjustment of Conversion Price. No adjustment in the Conversion Price of the Preferred Stock shall be made in respect of the issuance of Additional Shares of Common unless the consideration per share for an Additional Share of Common issued or deemed to be issued by the Corporation is less than the Conversion Price in effect on the date of, and immediately prior to such issue, for such series of Preferred Stock.</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_3_firstbold>Deemed Issue of Additional Shares of Common. In the event the Corporation after the date of the filing of this Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation shall issue any Options or Convertible Securities or shall fix a record date for the determination of holders of any class of securities entitled to receive any such Options or Convertible Securities, then the maximum number of shares (as set forth in the instrument relating thereto without regard to any provisions contained therein for a subsequent adjustment of such number) of Common Stock issuable upon the exercise of such Options or, in the case of Convertible Securities, the conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities or, in the case of Options for Convertible Securities, the exercise of such Options and the conversion or exchange of the underlying securities, shall be deemed to have been issued as of the time of such issue or, in case such a record date shall have been fixed, as of the close of business on such record date, provided that in any such case in which shares are deemed to be issued:</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_4_para>no further adjustment in the Conversion Price of any series of Preferred Stock shall be made upon the subsequent issue of Convertible Securities or shares of Common Stock in connection with the exercise of such Options or conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>if such Options or Convertible Securities by their terms provide, with the passage of time or otherwise, for any change in the consideration payable to the Corporation or in the number of shares of Common Stock issuable upon the exercise, conversion or exchange thereof (other than a change pursuant to the anti-dilution provisions of such Options or Convertible Securities or pursuant to Recapitalization provisions of such Options or Convertible Securities), the Conversion Price of each series of Preferred Stock and any subsequent adjustments based thereon shall be recomputed to reflect such change as if such change had been in effect as of the original issue thereof (or upon the occurrence of the record date with respect thereto);</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>no readjustment pursuant to the clause above shall have the effect of increasing the Conversion Price of a series of Preferred Stock to an amount above the Conversion Price that would have resulted from any other issuances of Additional Shares of Common and any other adjustments provided for herein between the original adjustment date and such readjustment date;</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_4_para>upon the expiration of any such Options or any rights of conversion or exchange under such Convertible Securities which shall not have been exercised, the Conversion Price of each Series of Preferred Stock computed upon the original issue thereof (or upon the occurrence of a record date with respect thereto) and any subsequent adjustments based thereon shall, upon such expiration, be recomputed as if:</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_5_para>in the case of Convertible Securities or Options for Common Stock, the only Additional Shares of Common issued were the shares of Common Stock, if any, actually issued upon the exercise of such Options or the conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities and the consideration received therefor was the consideration actually received by the Corporation for the issue of such exercised Options plus the consideration actually received by the Corporation upon such exercise or for the issue of all such Convertible Securities which were actually converted or exchanged, plus the additional consideration, if any, actually received by the Corporation upon such conversion or exchange, and</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_5_para>in the case of Options for Convertible Securities, only the Convertible Securities, if any, actually issued upon the exercise thereof were issued at the time of issue of such Options, and the consideration received by the Corporation for the Additional Shares of Common deemed to have been then issued was the consideration actually received by the Corporation for the issue of such exercised Options, plus the consideration deemed to have been received by the Corporation (determined pursuant to Section 3(d)(v)) upon the issue of the Convertible Securities with respect to which such Options were actually exercised; and</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_4_para>if such record date shall have been fixed and such Options or Convertible Securities are not issued on the date fixed therefor, the adjustment previously made in the Conversion Price which became effective on such record date shall be canceled as of the close of business on such record date, and thereafter the Conversion Price shall be adjusted pursuant to this paragraph 3(d)(iii) as of the actual date of their issuance.</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_3_firstbold>Adjustment of Conversion Price Upon Issuance of Additional Shares of Common. In the event this Corporation shall issue Additional Shares of Common (including Additional Shares of Common deemed to be issued pursuant to paragraph 3(d)(iii)) without consideration or for a consideration per share less than the applicable Conversion Price of the Preferred Stock in effect on the date of and immediately prior to such issue, then, the Conversion Price of the Preferred Stock shall be reduced, concurrently with such issue, to a price (calculated to the nearest cent) determined by multiplying such Conversion Price by a fraction, the numerator of which shall be the number of shares of Common Stock outstanding immediately prior to such issue plus the number of shares which the aggregate consideration received by the Corporation for the total number of Additional Shares of Common so issued would purchase at such Conversion Price, and the denominator of which shall be the number of shares of Common Stock outstanding immediately prior to such issue plus the number of such Additional Shares of Common so issued. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Conversion Price shall not be reduced at such time if the amount of such reduction would be less than $0.01, but any such amount shall be carried forward, and a reduction will be made with respect to such amount at the time of, and together with, any subsequent reduction which, together with such amount and any other amounts so carried forward, equal $0.01 or more in the aggregate. For the purposes of this Subsection 3(d)(iv), all shares of Common Stock issuable upon conversion of all outstanding shares of Preferred Stock and the exercise and/or conversion of any other outstanding Convertible Securities and all outstanding Options shall be deemed to be outstanding.</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_3_firstbold>Determination of Consideration. For purposes of this subsection 3(d), the consideration received by the Corporation for the issue (or deemed issue) of any Additional Shares of Common shall be computed as follows:</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_4_para>Cash and Property. Such consideration shall:</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_5_para>insofar as it consists of cash, be computed at the aggregate amount of cash received by the Corporation before deducting any reasonable discounts, commissions or other expenses allowed, paid or incurred by the Corporation for any underwriting or otherwise in connection with such issuance;</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_5_para>insofar as it consists of property other than cash, be computed at the fair market value thereof at the time of such issue, as determined in good faith by the Board of Directors; and</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_5_para>in the event Additional Shares of Common are issued together with other shares or securities or other assets of the Corporation for consideration which covers both, be the proportion of such consideration so received, computed as provided in clauses (a) and (b) above, as reasonably determined in good faith by the Board of Directors.</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_4_para>Options and Convertible Securities. The consideration per share received by the Corporation for Additional Shares of Common deemed to have been issued pursuant to paragraph 3(d)(iii) shall be determined by dividing</numbered_4_para>
<numbered_5_para>the total amount, if any, received or receivable by the Corporation as consideration for the issue of such Options or Convertible Securities, plus the minimum aggregate amount of additional consideration (as set forth in the instruments relating thereto, without regard to any provision contained therein for a subsequent adjustment of such consideration) payable to the Corporation upon the exercise of such Options or the conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities, or in the case of Options for Convertible Securities, the exercise of such Options for Convertible Securities and the conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities by</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_5_para>the maximum number of shares of Common Stock (as set forth in the instruments relating thereto, without regard to any provision contained therein for a subsequent adjustment of such number) issuable upon the exercise of such Options or the conversion or exchange of such Convertible Securities.</numbered_5_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Adjustments for Subdivisions or Combinations of Common Stock.  In the event the outstanding shares of Common Stock shall be subdivided (by stock split, by payment of a stock dividend or otherwise), into a greater number of shares of Common Stock, the Conversion Price of the Preferred Stock in effect immediately prior to such subdivision shall, concurrently with the effectiveness of such subdivision, be proportionately decreased.  In the event the outstanding shares of Common Stock shall be combined (by reclassification or otherwise) into a lesser number of shares of Common Stock, the Conversion Prices in effect immediately prior to such combination shall, concurrently with the effectiveness of such combination, be proportionately increased.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Adjustments for Subdivisions or Combinations of Preferred Stock.  In the event the outstanding shares of Preferred Stock shall be subdivided (by stock split, by payment of a stock dividend or otherwise), into a greater number of shares of Preferred Stock, the Original Issue Price and Liquidation Preference of the Preferred Stock in effect immediately prior to such subdivision shall, concurrently with the effectiveness of such subdivision, be proportionately decreased.  In the event the outstanding shares of Preferred Stock shall be combined (by reclassification or otherwise) into a lesser number of shares of Preferred Stock, the Original Issue Price and Liquidation Preference of the Preferred Stock in effect immediately prior to such combination shall, concurrently with the effectiveness of such combination, be proportionately increased.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Adjustments for Reclassification, Exchange and Substitution.  Subject to Section 2 above (“Liquidation Rights”), if the Common Stock issuable upon conversion of the Preferred Stock shall be changed into the same or a different number of shares of any other class or classes of stock, whether by capital reorganization, reclassification or otherwise (other than a subdivision or combination of shares provided for above), then, in any such event, in lieu of the number of shares of Common Stock which the holders would otherwise have been entitled to receive, each holder of such Preferred Stock shall have the right thereafter to convert such shares of Preferred Stock into a number of shares of such other class or classes of stock which a holder of the number of shares of Common Stock deliverable upon conversion of such Preferred Stock immediately before that change would have been entitled to receive in such reorganization or reclassification, all subject to further adjustment as provided herein with respect to such other shares.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Certificate as to Adjustments.  Upon the occurrence of each adjustment or readjustment of the Conversion Price pursuant to this Section 3, the Corporation at its expense shall promptly compute such adjustment or readjustment in accordance with the terms hereof and furnish to each holder of Preferred Stock a certificate setting forth such adjustment or readjustment and showing in detail the facts upon which such adjustment or readjustment is based.  The Corporation shall, upon the written request at any time of any holder of Preferred Stock, furnish or cause to be furnished to such holder a like certificate setting forth (i) such adjustments and readjustments, (ii) the Conversion Price at the time in effect and (iii) the number of shares of Common Stock and the amount, if any, of other property which at the time would be received upon the conversion of Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Waiver of Adjustment of Conversion Price. Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, any downward adjustment of the Conversion Price of a series of the Preferred Stock may be waived by the consent or vote of the holders of the majority of the outstanding shares of such series either before or after the issuance causing the adjustment. Any such waiver shall bind all future holders of shares of such series of the Preferred Stock.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Notices of Record Date.  In the event that this Corporation shall propose at any time:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>to declare any Distribution upon its Common Stock, whether in cash, property, stock or other securities, whether or not a regular cash dividend and whether or not out of earnings or earned surplus;</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>to effect any reclassification or recapitalization of its Common Stock outstanding involving a change in the Common Stock; or</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>to voluntarily liquidate or dissolve or to enter into any transaction deemed to be a liquidation, dissolution or winding up of the corporation pursuant to Section 2(d);</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>then, in connection with each such event, this Corporation shall send to the holders of the Preferred Stock at least 10 days’ prior written notice of the date on which a record shall be taken for such Distribution (and specifying the date on which the holders of Common Stock shall be entitled thereto and, if applicable, the amount and character of such Distribution) or for determining rights to vote in respect of the matters referred to in (ii) and (iii) above.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Such written notice shall be given by first class mail (or express courier), postage prepaid, addressed to the holders of Preferred Stock at the address for each such holder as shown on the books of the Corporation and shall be deemed given on the date such notice is mailed.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_para>The notice provisions set forth in this section may be shortened or waived prospectively or retrospectively by the consent or vote of the holders of a majority of the Preferred Stock, voting as a single class and on an as-converted basis.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_firstbold>Reservation of Stock Issuable Upon Conversion.  The Corporation shall at all times reserve and keep available out of its authorized but unissued shares of Common Stock solely for the purpose of effecting the conversion of the shares of the Preferred Stock, such number of its shares of Common Stock as shall from time to time be sufficient to effect the conversion of all then outstanding shares of the Preferred Stock; and if at any time the number of authorized but unissued shares of Common Stock shall not be sufficient to effect the conversion of all then outstanding shares of the Preferred Stock, the Corporation will take such corporate action as may, in the opinion of its counsel, be necessary to increase its authorized but unissued shares of Common Stock to such number of shares as shall be sufficient for such purpose.</numbered_3_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards automatic conversion. In a Change of Control event, or in the event of an IPO, all YC-AA Shares shall automatically convert to ordinary shares at the Conversion Ratio. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards voting. Other than as provided for under the Act, the Holders of YC-AA Shares shall be entitled to vote on any matter in a general meeting of the Company, pari passu with holders of ordinary shares, and in the case of a poll their votes shall be counted according to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if the YC-AA Shares were converted. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards dividends. The Holders of YC-AA Shares shall not be entitled to participate in the profits of the Company available for distribution by way of dividend or otherwise. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards surplus profits and assets. The Holders of YC-AA Shares shall have no right to participate in the profits or assets or any distributions of proceeds of the Company beyond the rights conferred under this Article.  </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ycaa_lp">Distribution upon Liquidation. In the event of any liquidation, dissolution or winding up of the Company, either voluntary or involuntary, the holders of the YC-AA Stock shall be entitled to receive, prior and in preference to any distribution of any of the assets of the Company to the holders of ordinary shares by reason of their ownership of such shares, an amount per share for each share of YC-AA Stock held by them equal to the Liquidation Preference specified for such share of YC-AA Stock, or such lesser amount as may be approved by the holders of the majority of the outstanding shares of YC-AA Stock. If upon the liquidation, dissolution or winding up of the Company, the assets of the Company legally available for distribution to the holders of the YC-AA Stock are insufficient to permit the payment to such holders of the full amounts specified in this Section <xref to="ycaa_lp" />, then the entire assets of the Company legally available for distribution shall be distributed with equal priority and pro rata among the holders of the YC-AA Stock in proportion to the full amounts they would otherwise be entitled to receive pursuant to this Section <xref to="ycaa_lp" />. Subsequent to such distribution, a holder of YC-AA Stock shall not be entitled to participate further in the remaining assets of the Company.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards transfers, registration, register and replacement. YC-AA Shares will be in registered form and the Company shall maintain a register thereof. The provisions of these Articles relating to the registration, transfer, transmission, certificates and replacement thereof applicable to ordinary shares shall apply mutatis mutandis to YC-AA Shares subject to the terms of the Agreement. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards substitution securities. In the event of a Change of Control, winding-up, or dissolution of the Company pursuant to reconstruction, amalgamation, merger or consolidation, the resultant corporate entity responsible for the liabilities of the Company with respect to YC-AA Shares shall issue such securities in substitution and replacement of YC-AA Shares and on such terms as shall be approved by at least 51% of all then existing Holders of YC-AA Shares unless the terms of such securities in substitution are no less favourable than the terms of YC-AA Shares in which case the approval by Holders of YC-AA Shares shall not be required. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards pro-rata rights. Holders of YC-AA Shares shall enjoy the rights described in Articles <xref to="rofr" /> and <xref to="preemptive" /> in proportion to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if converted. The ordinary shares issued upon conversion from YC-AA Shares, being spoken for, shall not be considered "new" for the purposes of Article <xref to="preemptive" /> and shall not be offered to other Members.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_para>Save as provided above, there are no other anti-dilution or protective provisions in respect of the YC-AA Shares.</numbered_2_para>

</Story_Main>
</Root>
