<b_left_sidehead_nonum xname="ycaa">Class YC-AA Convertible Preference Shares </b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<numbered_1_para>The Company may issue <b>Class YC-AA Shares</b> in the capital of the Company, at an issue price of S$0.00001 each or such other amount as the Directors may determine, which shall carry the following rights, benefits and privileges and be subject to the following restrictions: </numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards issue. YC-AA Shares may be issued with the sanction of an ordinary resolution pursuant to agreements between the Company and individual holders (within this Article <xref to="ycaa" />, the "Subscription Agreements"), the terms of which the Directors may determine. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards redemption. YC-AA Shares shall not be redeemable.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards conversion. A Holder of YC-AA Shares shall have the right to convert those shares to ordinary shares at the Conversion Ratio at any time. The Conversion Ratio shall be one-for-one, adjusted for:</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_3_para>Anti-Dilution: If, subsequent to the issue of a YC-AA Share, any ordinary or preference shares are issued at an effective (fully-diluted) price per (post-conversion or post-exercise) share lower than the price per share paid for the YC-AA Share, then the Conversion Ratio shall be adjusted to produce more ordinary shares -- as though the YC-AA Share had originally been issued at the lower price. </numbered_3_para>
<numbered_3_para>Recapitalization due to any stock dividend, stock split, combination of shares, reorganization, recapitalization, reclassification, repurchase, redemption, cancellation, or other similar event.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards automatic conversion. In a Change of Control event, or in the event of an IPO, all YC-AA Shares shall automatically convert to ordinary shares at the Conversion Ratio. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards voting. Other than as provided for under the Act, the Holders of YC-AA Shares shall be entitled to vote on any matter in a general meeting of the Company, pari passu with holders of ordinary shares, and in the case of a poll their votes shall be counted according to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if the YC-AA Shares were converted. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards dividends. The Holders of YC-AA Shares shall not be entitled to participate in the profits of the Company available for distribution by way of dividend or otherwise. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards surplus profits and assets. The Holders of YC-AA Shares shall have no right to participate in the profits or assets or any distributions of proceeds of the Company beyond the rights conferred under this Article.  </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold xname="ycaa_lp">Distribution upon Liquidation. In the event of any liquidation, dissolution or winding up of the Company, either voluntary or involuntary, the holders of the YC-AA Stock shall be entitled to receive, prior and in preference to any distribution of any of the assets of the Company to the holders of ordinary shares by reason of their ownership of such shares, an amount per share for each share of YC-AA Stock held by them equal to the Liquidation Preference specified for such share of YC-AA Stock, or such lesser amount as may be approved by the holders of the majority of the outstanding shares of YC-AA Stock. If upon the liquidation, dissolution or winding up of the Company, the assets of the Company legally available for distribution to the holders of the YC-AA Stock are insufficient to permit the payment to such holders of the full amounts specified in this Section <xref to="ycaa_lp" />, then the entire assets of the Company legally available for distribution shall be distributed with equal priority and pro rata among the holders of the YC-AA Stock in proportion to the full amounts they would otherwise be entitled to receive pursuant to this Section <xref to="ycaa_lp" />. Subsequent to such distribution, a holder of YC-AA Stock shall not be entitled to participate further in the remaining assets of the Company.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards transfers, registration, register and replacement. YC-AA Shares will be in registered form and the Company shall maintain a register thereof. The provisions of these Articles relating to the registration, transfer, transmission, certificates and replacement thereof applicable to ordinary shares shall apply mutatis mutandis to YC-AA Shares subject to the terms of the Agreement. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards substitution securities. In the event of a Change of Control event, winding-up, or dissolution of the Company pursuant to reconstruction, amalgamation, merger or consolidation, the resultant corporate entity responsible for the liabilities of the Company with respect to YC-AA Shares shall issue such securities in substitution and replacement of YC-AA Shares and on such terms as shall be approved by at least 51% of all then existing Holders of YC-AA Shares unless the terms of such securities in substitution are no less favourable than the terms of YC-AA Shares in which case the approval by Holders of YC-AA Shares shall not be required. </numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_firstbold>As regards pro-rata rights. Holders of YC-AA Shares shall enjoy the rights described in Articles <xref to="rofr" /> and <xref to="preemptive" /> in proportion to the number of ordinary shares they would hold if converted.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<numbered_2_para>Save as provided above, there are no other anti-dilution or protective provisions in respect of the YC-AA Shares.</numbered_2_para>
