<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<? var jfdi_investor = data.capTable.getRound("JFDI Round").new_investors["JFDI.2014 Pte. Ltd."];
   jfdi_investor.name = "JFDI.2014 Pte. Ltd.";
?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_standard_parties", data, {cover_title:"JFDI Founder Agreement", rcpts_to:rcpts_to}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_jfdi", data, { in_series:"03" }) ?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<sidebar>This foundational document confirms the Founders' acceptance of the offer made by JFDI to participate in the next Accelerate Bootcamp.</sidebar>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
<chapter_header>Founder Agreement</chapter_header>
<? if (data.founder_agreement_supersedes_previous) { ?>
<para_1><i>This Agreement supersedes a previous Founder Agreement dated <?= data.founder_agreement_date ?>.</i></para_1>
<? } ?>
<para_1>This Agreement legally binds the following individuals and organizations (the "Parties") with respect to the JFDI.Asia Accelerate Bootcamp <span_ucnum><?= data.jfdi_accelerate_batch ?></span_ucnum> (the "Bootcamp"):</para_1>
<? for (var i in data.parties.founder) { ?>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.founder[i]) ?><? if (data.parties.founder.length == 1) { ?> (the "Founder")<? } ?></parties>
<? } ?>
<? if (data.parties.founder.length > 1) { ?><para_1>(the "Founders")</para_1><? } ?>
<parties><?
if (data.company.id != undefined && data.company.id.length > 0) { ?><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?><? }
else { ?><?= data.company.name ?>, a Singapore Private Limited Company <?
  if (! data.previously_incorporated) { ?>promoted by the Founders<? }
  else if ( data.previous_incorporation_locale != "Singapore" ) { ?>with a previous incarnation registered in <?= data.previous_incorporation_locale ?><?
  }
} ?> (the "Startup")
<?= jfdi_investor.name ?>, an investor into the Startup ("JFDI.2014"); and
JFDI.Asia Pte. Ltd, the operator of the Bootcamp ("JFDI.Asia"), party by virtue of its management agreement with JFDI.2014.</parties>
<para_1>By this Agreement the Parties express a mutual understanding as follows:</para_1>
<numbered_1_para>The <span_ucnum><?= data.jfdi_accelerate_batch ?></span_ucnum> Bootcamp shall run in two phases. The "Accelerate" phase begins on <?= data.accelerate_start_date ?>. The Bootcamp ends with Demo Day, on or around <?= data.demo_day_date ?>. The Founders should be prepared to remain in Singapore through <?= data.remainder_date ?> to negotiate funding.
Upon acceptance of this Agreement, the Founders will be provisionally admitted to the <? if (data.skip_hoops != true) { ?>"Validate" phase of the Bootcamp. During this phase, the Founders are not required to be present in Singapore. The Founders should work on customer development, product development, and early traction through a Minimum Viable Product (concierge or scalable or both.) JFDI will work with the Founders online to prepare them for Accelerate. The Founders should also recruit as needed to ensure that the team contains a complete mix of capabilities: product, customer, and business development.
Upon demonstrating early traction and a complete team, the Founders will be invited to the "Accelerate" phase in Singapore. During this phase, the Startup should aim to demonstrate:
</numbered_1_para>
<bullets>scalable traction: sales and user growth that does not require direct involvement by the Founders.
proof of revenue: that some percentage of leads or users are willing to pay.</bullets>
<numbered_1_para> <? }
 else { ?>Bootcamp. <? }
 ?>JFDI.2014 shall, if all goes well, invest a total of <?= jfdi_investor.money ?> into the Startup;</numbered_1_para>
<para_2>and <? if (! data.previously_incorporated) { ?>the Founders shall procure that <? } ?>in consideration of this investment <? if (data.intangibles_clause) { ?>and for other good and valuable consideration described in Clause <xref to="intangibles" />, which the Parties agree to value at <?= (data.intangibles_value || "S$150,000") ?>,
<? } ?>
the Startup shall authorise and issue <? if (data.jfdi_standard_valuation != false) { ?>convertible debt, equity, or some other security in the corporation such that, immediately prior to the Next External Financing, JFDI.2014 will own a certain percentage (the "Conversion Percentage") of the total capital in the Startup, on a fully-diluted, as-if-converted basis.<? } else { ?><?= data.nonstandard_valuation_text ?><? } ?></para_2>
<numbered_1_para>The Next External Financing refers to the first financing event subsequent to JFDI.2014's investment in which the Startup raises more than <?= data.qualified_financing_round_size ?> within one round or series<? if (data.qualified_round_type != undefined) { ?> of <?= data.qualified_round_type ?> securities<? } ?>.
<? if (data.jfdi_standard_valuation == false ) { ?><? } else { ?>
The Conversion Percentage shall be<?
if (data.valuation_basis == "table") { ?>
<? if (data.jfdi_standard_valuation != false) { ?> calculated on the basis of the <?= jfdi_investor.money ?> cash investment by JFDI and<? } ?>
 according to the following valuation table, or as agreed between the Startup and JFDI.2014.
</numbered_1_para>
<? if (data.nonstandard_valuation_table) { ?><table_enclosing_para><?!= data.nonstandard_valuation_table ?></table_enclosing_para><? } else { ?>
<table_enclosing_para><Table aid:table="table" aid:tcols="2" aid:trows="6" xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/">
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid:theader="" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>Valuation</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid:theader="" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Basis</cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>S$475,000</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Startup has at least 100 paying customers (if B2C) or 20 paying customers (if B2B) and annualized recurring revenues of at least S$50,000 based on a 3-month trailing average.</cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>S$390,000</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Startup has at least 100 paying customers (if B2C) or 20 paying customers (if B2B) and cumulative revenues of at least S$50,000.</cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>S$250,000</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Startup has no revenues, but about 300 Daily Active Users for a consumer app or 10 recurring paying customers for a B2B app.</cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>S$200,000</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Startup has a prototype developed and launched, and at least 30 daily active users (B2C) or three positive customer testimonials (B2B).</cell_fl></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="67.93779527550001" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_r"><cell>S$170,000</cell></Cell>
<Cell aid:ccols="1" aid:ccolwidth="226.33779527550004" aid:crows="1" aid:table="cell" aid5:cellstyle="border_l"><cell_fl>Startup has no users, but a prototype developed based on at least 12 customer development interviews.</cell_fl></Cell>
</Table><? if (data.agreed_percentage) { ?>The Conversion Percentage has been tentatively agreed at <?= data.agreed_percentage ?>%. Confirmation will be subject to delivery and acceptance of substantiating evidence.<? }
else { ?>Valuation basis to be measured and fixed at the start of the "Accelerate" phase.<? } ?></table_enclosing_para><numbered_1_para><? } ?><? }
else if (data.valuation_basis == "existing") { ?> determined on the basis of the valuation set in the previous round of financing by professional investors.</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>The Startup shall disclose to JFDI the details of the previous round of financing, including the identities of the investors, terms of the investment, and evidence of funds transferred.
<? if (data.previous_post_money_valuation) { ?>
As an example, if the previous round of financing established a post-money valuation for the Startup at <?= data.previous_post_money_valuation ?>, then JFDI's total investment of <?= jfdi_investor.money ?> (cash) plus <?= data.intangibles_value ?> (intangibles) determines the Conversion Percentage at <?= data.agreed_percentage ?>%.
<? } ?>
</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para><? }
       else if (data.valuation_basis == "discussion") { ?> determined as agreed by the Parties.
<?   } else if (data.valuation_basis == "fixed") { ?> <?= data.agreed_percentage ?>%<?
if(data.tranche_1_percentage){?> in two tranches: the first being <?=data.tranche_1_amount?> for <?=data.tranche_1_percentage?>%, and the second being <?=data.tranche_1_amount?> for <?=data.tranche_2_percentage?>%<?}?>.
<?   } ?>
<? } ?>
The Founders shall travel to and from Singapore at their own expense. JFDI.Asia and JFDI.2014 shall not be obligated to reimburse any expenses incurred, or transfer any funds to the Founders or to their Startup, prior to formal acceptance to the Accelerate phase.
<? if (data.skip_hoops != true) { ?>Formal acceptance to the Accelerate phase will be offered as soon the Founders demonstrate, to JFDI.Asia's satisfaction, that they can:
</numbered_1_para><bullets>articulate their innovation insight
articulate their industry dynamics
show that they have done market research and refined their early adopter customer archetype
articulate channels to reach those customers
describe their competitive analysis and positioning
articulate their sustainable competitive advantage
show an MVP already launched
started acquiring users or customers
</bullets>
<para_1>Teams which do not meet these criteria by <?= data.accelerate_start_date ?> will be considered for a subsequent bootcamp.</para_1>
<numbered_1_para><? } ?>
Within four weeks of the start of the Accelerate phase, the Founders shall <? if (data.previously_incorporated) { ?>have incorporated the Startup as a Singapore Private Limited legal entity and <? } ?>have opened a Singapore corporate bank account.
After Accelerate begins, the Startup's Singapore bank account is ready, and the Startup and Founders have signed the JFDI Investment Agreement, the Shareholders' Agreement, the Founders Agreement, and the Class F agreement, JFDI.2014 will transfer <? if (data.skip_hoops != true) { ?><?=data.tranche_1_amount?> (twenty-five thousand Singapore dollars), that being the first tranche of its total cash investment, in return for a future <?=data.tranche_1_percentage?>% of the business.
Conditional upon demonstrating further traction, the Startup will also be offered a chance to pitch to potential investors on Demo Day. If the Startup is struggling to show traction, JFDI.Asia may cancel the pitch. For the avoidance of doubt, a Startup which does not qualify to pitch will not be invited to Demo Day, not even to be in the audience.
JFDI.2014 shall make the second tranche payment of <?=data.tranche_2_amount?> on or around Demo Day. This payment shall be made at JFDI.Asia's sole discretion, but is typically conditional upon the Founders participating in the Singapore component of the bootcamp, and the Startup demonstrating product/market fit in the form of a revenue commitment from at least two external, arms-length customers. The second tranche payment will entail a further <?=data.tranche_2_percentage?>% in the business. If the second tranche payment is not paid, JFDI.2014 will maintain its interest at the first-tranche level of <?=data.tranche_1_percentage?>%. The Startup may not decline the second tranche investment.
<? } else { ?><?= jfdi_investor.money ?> in one tranche.
<? } ?>
The Startup shall grant JFDI.2014 the right but not the obligation to invest a separate S$70,000 in the Startup at any time up to and including the Next External Financing, on the same terms as enjoyed by any other third-party investors.
During the course of the Bootcamp the Founders shall treat the Startup as their exclusive work priority. During the first and last months of the Bootcamp the Founders shall be in Singapore and attend substantially all of the sessions offered by JFDI.
The Founders are responsible for finding housing and for ensuring that their presence in Singapore complies with employment and immigration regulations.
<? if (data.intangibles_clause) { ?><b xname="intangibles">Intangibles.</b> <? } ?>During the Bootcamp, JFDI.Asia shall invest time and energy working with the Startup, providing coaching, counseling, mentoring, administrative guidance, and the opportunity to pitch before investors on Demo Day. The primary focus of the Bootcamp is to give first-time founders an experiential understanding of the requirements of venture investors. Founders will be given the opportunity to make the best possible case for investment. JFDI will coordinate mentors to give guidance and feedback on the Startup's likelihood of raising investment.
The majority of startups entering JFDI have not yet incorporated their businesses. JFDI.Asia shall provide standardised legal paperwork such as an Investment Agreement, Shareholder Agreement, Volunteer and Employment Agreement, Memorandum and Articles of Association, etc. (the "Subsequent Agreements"). The terms of this Agreement will be set out in detail in those Subsequent Agreements.
Should the Parties not execute the relevant Subsequent Agreements by the beginning of the Accelerate phase, then this Agreement will terminate at that time, JFDI.2014 will not invest in the Startup, and the Startup will not be eligible to attend Accelerate.
JFDI.2014 can only invest in a Singapore Private Limited company.</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>If the Startup has already been incorporated in Singapore as a Private Limited company (an "Existing Local Company"), then JFDI shall make its investment in that company instead of requiring incorporation of a new entity, and "Startup" in this Agreement shall refer to the Existing Local Company.
If the Founders previously did the business of the Startup through a corporate entity outside Singapore (an "Existing Foreign Company"), then the Founders shall, after incorporating the Startup in Singapore, transfer the capital structure of the existing company to the new Singapore entity; and the existing company may then become a wholly owned subsidiary of the Singapore entity, or license or assign all of its assets to the Singapore entity.
In either case, the Founders warrant that they jointly have both effective and economic control of the Existing Company, and undertake to disclose to JFDI.Asia in writing as soon as possible after the execution of this Agreement:</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_3_para>the Existing Company's corporate documentation including its Memorandum and Articles of Association, Shareholders Agreements, Directors Agreements, etc.;
the capitalisation table of the Existing Company including all debt and equity issues; and
all material liabilities and contractual agreements of the Existing Company.</numbered_3_para>
<numbered_1_para>If the Founders have incorporated more than one entity to hold the business, then JFDI.2014 can only invest in the holding company which wholly or majority owns all the other entities. If it is not possible to re-organize the corporate structure accordingly to the satisfaction of JFDI.2014 by the start of the Bootcamp, then this agreement will terminate at that time.
In the event that proprietary assets to be used in the Startup (including but not limited to intellectual property assets) reside with individuals or in another legal entity whether such individuals or entities are in Singapore or abroad, the Founders shall, within four weeks of formal acceptance, cause said assets to be transferred into the Singapore Startup legal entity, free and clear of any pledge, reservation of right, or other encumbrance.
The Founders warrant that they have no reason to believe that any other party may lay exclusive claim to any intellectual property, asset, or other proprietary interest of the Startup.
As an investor, JFDI.2014 shall hold the following rights which the Founders and/or other shareholders may or may not also hold:
</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent_noupspace>transferable pre-emptive right of first refusal in all future issues of equity securities or securities convertible to equity;
tag-along rights in the case of sale of stock by a Founder;
information rights regarding traction and financial metrics.
</numbered_2_para_indent_noupspace>
<numbered_1_para>Subsequent to the Bootcamp, JFDI.2014 shall cooperate with future financings and other corporate activities by responding to paperwork requests in a timely fashion.
The Founders shall have the responsibility to maintain the Startup as a legal entity in good standing with the Singapore authorities. A Singapore company is required to have a local director ordinarily resident in Singapore. If the Founders are not ordinarily resident in Singapore they must either find someone who is, or be prepared to retain a third-party nominee director on standard commercial terms.
<? if (data.local_director) { ?>
Unless otherwise agreed in writing, if none of the Founders are Singapore citizens or permanent residents, and therefore require JFDI staff to act as a local director, then the Founders and the Startup shall execute a limited power of attorney and/or a proxy to empower JFDI.2014 and its representatives, in the event the Startup fails, to wind up or strike off the company in the absence of the Founders.
<? } ?>
The Founders shall cause the Startup to ratify this agreement by corporate resolution, and otherwise agree to promptly undertake such actions as JFDI.Asia may request from time to time in writing to give effect to this agreement, including but not limited to a novation of this agreement, if requested.
The division of equity in the Startup amongst the Founders and/or other employees, advisors and consultants is a matter for the Founders to agree on, so long as JFDI.2014's interests are not diluted prior to the Next External Financing.
This offer may be rescinded should the Founders be unable to comply with the requirements herein, or fail to deliver other supporting documents requested by JFDI.Asia.
</numbered_1_para><b_left_sidehead_nonum>Expiry</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<para_1>This agreement must be executed by all parties listed on the Signature Page by <?= data.expiry_date ?>. If it is not signed by all parties at that time, this agreement shall be null and void and of no effect.
</para_1>
<chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>
<para_1>Intending to be bound by this agreement, the Parties on this Signature Page now set their hands:
</para_1>
<? for (var i = 0; i < data.parties.founder.length; i++) { ?>
<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.parties.founder[i]) ?>
<? } ?>

<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data._entitiesByName[jfdi_investor.name]) ?>

</Story_Main>
</Root>
