<?
  var start = data._include.numbering_level ? '<numbered_'+data._include.numbering_level+'_para>' : '<numbered_2_para>';
  var end = '</' + start.substr(1).replace(/ .*/, ">");
?>
<?!=start?>This Agreement (and any dispute, controversy, proceedings or claim of whatever nature arising out of this Agreement or its formation) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore and the Parties irrevocably submit to the jurisdiction of the Courts of the Republic of Singapore. <?!=end?>
<?!=start?>Notwithstanding any provisions to the contrary in this Agreement, in the event of any dispute or difference arising out of or in connection with this Agreement (including any question regarding its existence, validity or termination) whether during the continuance of this Agreement or at any time after the termination hereof, the parties shall first attempt to resolve the same by negotiation in good faith or through mediation at the Singapore Mediation Centre ("SMC") between the appointed representative of the respective Parties. <?!=end?>
<?!=start?>In the event that the dispute or difference shall remain unresolved within thirty (30) days upon conclusion of such negotiation or mediation, any Party shall be entitled to refer the dispute to arbitration in Singapore in accordance with the Law Society of Singapore Arbitration Scheme ("LSAS") following the LawSoc Arbitration Rules for the time being in force, which rules are deemed to be incorporated by reference to this Clause <xref to="medarb" />. The arbitral tribunal shall consist of a sole arbitrator, who shall be appointed by the President of the Law Society of Singapore, under the LawSoc Arbitration Rules. The language of the arbitration shall be English. Any award made hereunder shall be final and binding upon the Parties and judgement on such award may be entered in any court or tribunal having jurisdiction thereof. <?!=end?>
<?!=start?>Pending the resolution or final determination of the dispute or difference pursuant to this Clause <xref to="medarb" />, the Parties shall procure that the Company shall, as far as practicable, continue to carry on its day-to-day business, having regard to the dispute or difference. <?!=end?>
<?!=start?>Notwithstanding the foregoing, each of the Parties reserves its right to immediately commence any interim Court action such as an injunction against any of the other Parties to enforce the terms of this Agreement in a forum of its choice. <?!=end?>
<?!=start?>This Clause <xref to="medarb" /> shall survive the termination of this Agreement for any reason whatsoever.<?!=end?>
