<? if (data.founders_give_company_lpa || (data.company_gives_investors_lpa && data.new_investor.power_of_attorney)) { ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Limited Powers of Attorney for Maintenance of Good Standing</a_left_sidehead>
<?   if (data.founders_give_company_lpa) { ?>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Company as Agent. Each Founder hereby irrevocably designates and appoints the Company and its duly authorized officers and agents as his agent and attorney in fact, to act for and on his behalf and stead,</numbered_2_firstbold>
<para_2>if and only if the Company is unable because of any Founder's unavailability, unreachability, uncontactability, or mental or physical incapacity or for any other reason to secure the Founder's signature or other authorisation to effect any compliance paperwork or other filings necessary to maintain the Company's good standing status with government authorities,</para_2>
<para_2>to execute and file any such applications or documents and to do all other lawfully permitted acts to further the application for, prosecution and issuance including striking off or winding down of the Company, thereon with the same legal force and effect as if originally executed by the Founder. The Founder hereby waives and irrevocably quits claim to the Company any and all claims, of any nature whatsoever, which the Founder now or hereafter has for infringement of any and all rights assigned to the Company.</para_2>
<?   } ?>
<?   if (data.company_gives_investors_lpa && data.new_investor.power_of_attorney) { ?>
<numbered_2_firstbold>Investor as Agent. The Company hereby irrevocably designates and appoints the Investor and its duly authorized officers and agents as its agent and attorney in fact, to act for and on its behalf and stead, if and only if the Company's directors or members are themselves unavailable, unreachable, uncontactable, or incapacitated, to the extent that the Company is unable to maintain good standing status with government authorities, to execute and file any such applications or documents and to do all other lawfully permitted acts to further the application for, prosecution and issuance including striking off or winding down of the Company, thereon with the same legal force and effect as if originally executed by the Company. The Company hereby waives and irrevocably quits claim to the Investor any and all claims, of any nature whatsoever, which the Company now or hereafter has for infringement of any and all rights assigned to the Investor.</numbered_2_firstbold>
<?   } ?>
<? } ?>
