<ab_a_left_reset override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=3">Changes to Clause 3 of the Articles of Association</ab_a_left_reset>

<para_1>Clause 3 currently titled "Class A Preference Shares" will be renumbered 3A.</para_1>

<para_1>The following definitions will be added to the Articles.</para_1>

<b_left_sidehead_nonum>Definitions</b_left_sidehead_nonum>
<definition_nonum><?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>	means the <?= data.security_type ?> in the share capital of the Company, having the rights and being subject to the restrictions specified in these Articles described under "<?= data.new_security_type ?>";</definition_nonum>
<? if (data.shadows_an_underlying_security) { ?>
<definition_nonum><?= data.underlying_security_short_plural ?>	means the <?= data.underlying_security_name ?> in the capital of <?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.startup[0]) ?> (the "Incubatee"), described in the Articles of Association of the Incubatee;</definition_nonum>
<? } ?>

<ab_a_left_sidehead override="numberingContinue=false numberingStartAt=2"><?= data.new_security_type ?></ab_a_left_sidehead>

<para_1>The Company may issue preference shares in the capital of the Company ("<?= data.new_security_short ?>") which shall carry the following rights, benefits, and privileges, and be subject to the following restrictions:--</para_1>
<? if (data.shadows_an_underlying_security) { ?>
<ab_b_left_sidehead>As Regards the Relationship with the Underlying Security</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl><?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> represent <?= data.underlying_security_name ?> of <?= data.parties.underlying_company[0].name ?> (the <b>"Underlying Security"</b> or "<?= data.underlying_security_short_plural ?>"). The term "Underlying Security" shall include both the TG CP Shares and any security to which the TG CP Shares are converted or convertible.
Proceeds from the issuance of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall be used solely to purchase <?= data.underlying_security_name ?> in <?= data.parties.underlying_company[0].name ?>.
<?= data.underlying_security_short_plural ?> purchased in this way shall be held in trust by the Company for the beneficial owners: the holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>.
Proceeds arising from the Company's interests in the Underlying Security, including dividends and capital gains, shall accrue wholly to the holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>.
<?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall be convertible, at the election of the holder, to the Underlying Security at any time, subject to the limitations imposed by the Company's agreements with the Incubatee. As such limitations may prohibit transfer or assignment of <?= data.underlying_security_short_plural ?>, proceeds may not be realised until the Incubatee achieves a liquidity event.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>As Regards Other Classes of Shares in <?= data.company.name ?></ab_b_left_sidehead>

<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>The class of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall be, as far as economic and control rights are concerned, effectively independent of other classes of shares in the Company, except insofar as the RCPS shareholders may enjoy certain pre-emptive rights and rights of first refusal described below.
Holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall enjoy no special rights in respect of their Membership in the Company beyond those arising from their holdings of other classes of shares.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Transfer of Shares</ab_b_left_sidehead>

<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Before the Shares may be transferred to any person who is neither a member of the Company nor a member of TradeGecko Pte. Ltd., rights of first refusal must be offered to the following categories in order, pro rata with customary excess rights:</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>
<ab_numbered_4_para_fltab>Holders of TGAS
Holders of RCPS shares in JFDI.2012 Pte. Ltd.
Ordinary Shareholders in JFDI.2012 Pte. Ltd.
Holders of RCPS shares in Other JFDI Companies (JFDI.2013 Pte. Ltd., JFDI.2014 Pte. Ltd., JFDI.Asia Pte. Ltd., etc.)
Members of TradeGecko Pte. Ltd.</ab_numbered_4_para_fltab>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Issue of Shares</ab_b_left_sidehead>

<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>New issues of TGAS shall not be made to any person who is not already a member of the Company.</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>New issues of TGAS shall first be offered, pro rata with customary excess rights, to existing Holders of TGAS, then to RCPS Shareholders of JFDI.2012, then to Ordinary Shareholders of JFDI.2012.</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Voting</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall enjoy no voting rights at any general meeting of the Members of the Company beyond those arising from their holdings of other classes of shares.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Dividends</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall not be entitled to participate in the profits of the Company available for distribution by way of dividend or otherwise.
Any dividends issued to the Company by virtue of its ownership of Underlying Securities shall be paid through to the holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>, less any withholdings required by law, and less any reasonable incidental expenses incurred by the Company in relation to the receipt and payment of these dividends, including professional fees paid to legal or accounting specialists, and management fees due the Company, calculated to cover the cost of the Company's attention to the <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Redemption</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>TGA Shares may be redeemed at the option of the Company by transferring title of the Underlying Security to the holder.</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>

<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Repayment of Capital</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>On a liquidation, dissolution, or winding-up of the Company, or on a return of capital by the Company, holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall receive, so far as is practicable, title to the Underlying Security.
On a liquidation, dissolution, or winding-up of the Incubatee, or a return of capital by the Incubatee, holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall receive the cash or other liquid assets delivered by the Incubatee or its agents or receivers, less any reasonable incidental expenses incurred by the Company in relation to the receipt and payment of these dividends, including professional fees paid to legal or accounting specialists, and management fees due the Company, calculated to cover the cost of the Company's attention to the <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>
<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Participation in Surplus Assets and Profits</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> will not be entitled to participate in the surplus profits or assets of the Company beyond transfer of title of the Underlying Security.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>
<ab_b_left_sidehead>Regarding Priority of Payment of Capital and Dividends in Relation to Other Classes of Shares</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Payments of capital and dividends to holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall be calculated and made separately from other classes of shares.
Only those gains arising from the Underlying Security shall benefit holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?>.
Gains arising from the Underlying Security shall not benefit holders of other classes of shares.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>
<ab_b_left_sidehead>No Annual Meeting</ab_b_left_sidehead>
<ab_numbered_3_para_fl>Pursuant to Section 175A of the Companies Act (Cap. 50), holders of <?= data.new_security_short_plural ?> shall agree to dispense with the holding of annual general meetings within their class of shares.
</ab_numbered_3_para_fl>
<? } ?>
