<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/" templateSpec="singlepage.indt">
<letterhead><?= data.company.name ?></letterhead>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<?= data.company.name ?>

<?= data.company.idtype ?> <span_ucnum><?= data.company.id ?></span_ucnum>
<?= data.company.address ?>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
<basic_para>



</basic_para>
<resolution_title>Declaration</resolution_title>

<chapter_header override="startParagraph=StartParagraph.ANYWHERE">Striking Off <?= data.company.name ?></chapter_header>
<? if (data.parties.director.length == 1) { ?>
<para_1>I, <?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.director[0]) ?> (the "Director") do solemnly and sincerely declare as follows:</para_1>
<? } else { ?>
<para_1>We,</para_1>
<?    for (var i in data.parties.director) { ?>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.parties.director[i]) ?></parties>
<?    } ?>
<para_1>(the "Directors")</para_1>
<para_1><span_smallcaps>do solemnly and sincerely</span_smallcaps> declare as follows:</para_1>
<? } ?>
<numbered_1_para><?
 if (data.parties.director.length == 1) { ?>I am the sole local director of <? }
 else { ?>We are the directors of <? } ?>
<?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?> (the "Company").
The Company has not commenced business since the date of incorporation on <?= data.company.incorporation_date || data.company.date_of_incorporation || data.incorporation_date || data.date_of_incorporation ?>.
The bank account of the Company has been closed.
<? if (data.last_agm_date == undefined || ! data.last_agm_date.length) { ?>The Company has not held an AGM, or the first AGM to be held within 18 months from the date of incorporation is not due.
<? } ?>
The company officers have no outstanding summonses or composition fines issued by <?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].name ?> ("<?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].short_name ?>") or Warrant of Arrest issued by the Court.
The Company has no outstanding penalties or offers of composition fine owing to <?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].short_name ?>.
The Company has no outstanding tax liabilities owing to IRAS and is not indebted to any other government department.
The Company has no outstanding charges in the Register of Charges.
The Company is not involved in or threatened with legal proceedings within or outside Singapore.
We have sought the written consent of all the shareholders to strike the name of the Company off the register, and received no objection from any shareholder.
The Company has no assets and no liabilities.
The Company has no contingent assets and liabilities (i.e. assets/liabilities that may arise in the future.)
We hereby give our consent for the Company to apply to <?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].short_name ?> to consider striking the name of the Company off the register under Section 344 of the Companies Act (Cap. 50).
We hereby authorise <?= data.parties.corporate_secretary[0].name ?> to e-file to <?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].short_name ?> on the aforesaid application for striking off.
</numbered_1_para>
<para_1><span_smallcaps>Declared by:</span_smallcaps></para_1>
<? for (var i=0;i<data.parties.director.length;i++) { ?>
<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.parties.director[i]) ?>
<? } ?>
</Story_Main>
<Bottom_Box delete_if_empty="true" />
</Root>
