<Root xmlns:aid="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/4.0/" xmlns:aid5="http://ns.adobe.com/AdobeInDesign/5.0/" templateSpec="singlepage.indt">
<letterhead><?= data.company.name ?></letterhead>
<Firstpage_Sidebar>
<?= data.company.name ?>

<?= data.company.idtype ?> <span_ucnum><?= data.company.id ?></span_ucnum>
<?= data.company.address ?>
</Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
<resolution_title>Letter to Accountant</resolution_title>
<basic_para>
<?= data.parties.accountant[0].name ?>

<?= data.parties.accountant[0].address ?>

</basic_para>

<para_1>Dear Sirs,</para_1>
<para_1>We are writing to you, at your request, to confirm our understanding that your preparation of the statement of financial position of <b><?= data.company.name ?></b> (the "Company") as at <b><?= data.shutdown_financial_period_end_date ?></b> and the statement of comprehensive income, statement of changes in equity, and cash flow statements for the period then ended were made at our request based on information and accounting records furnished by us.
We acknowledge our responsibility for the fair presentation of the financial statements in accordance with Singapore Financial Reporting Standards, including the appropriate disclosure of all information required by the Companies Act (Cap. 50).
</para_1>
<numbered_1_para>We have made available to you---</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>all financial records and related data;
all minutes of the meetings of shareholders and directors.</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para>There have been no---</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>Irregularities involving management or employees.
Communications from the <?= data.parties.state_regulator[0].name ?> concerning non-compliance with, or deficiencies in, financial reporting practices that could have a material effect on the financial statements.
Violations or possible violations of laws or regulations, the effects of which should be considered for disclosure in the financial statements or as a basis for recording a loss contingency.</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para>There are no---</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>Unasserted claims or assessments that our lawyer has advised us are probable of assertion.
Material liabilities or gain-or-loss contingencies that are required to be accrued or disclosed by the Companies Act (Cap. 50) and recommendations of the Institute of Certified Public Accountants.
Material transactions of related assets or liabilities that have not been properly recorded in the accounting records from which the financial statements are prepared.
Events that have occurred subsequent to the reporting date that would require adjustment to, or disclosure in, the financial statements.
Bank accounts that have not been disclosed to you, for example new accounts opened during the year.</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para>Provision, when material, has been made for---</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>Losses to be sustained in the fulfilment of, or from inability to fulfil, any sales commitment.
Losses to be sustained as a result of purchase commitments for stock quantities in excess of normal requirements or at prices in excess of the prevailing market prices.
Losses to be sustained as results of reduction of excess or obsolete stocks to their estimated net-realisable value.</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para>We have no plans or intentions that materially affect the carrying value or classification of assets or liabilities.
The Company has satisfactory title to all owned assets and there are no liens or encumbrances on such assets nor has any asset been pledged.
We have complied with all aspects of contractual agreements that would have a material effect on the financial statements in the event of non-compliance.
The following have been properly recorded or disclosed in the financial statements:---</numbered_1_para>
<numbered_2_para_indent>Related-party transactions and related amounts receivable or payable, including sales, purchases, loans, transfers, leasing arrangements, and guarantees.
Capital stock/shares purchase options or agreements or shares reserved for options, warrants, conversions, or other arrangements.
Arrangements with financial institutions involving restrictions on cash  balances and lines of credit or similar arrangements.
Arrangements to repurchase assets previously sold and options to purchase property or equipment of material amounts.
Amounts due to directors and shareholders will not be due for payment until after other liabilities have been fully settled.</numbered_2_para_indent>
<numbered_1_para>The company has ceased business from <?= data.shutdown_financial_period_end_date ?>.
Any expenditure included in the accounts was properly made in connection with the carrying-on of the Company's business.</numbered_1_para>
<para_1>Yours faithfully,</para_1>
<? for (var i=0;i<data.parties.director.length;i++) { ?>
<?!= include("inc_signature", data, data.parties.director[i]) ?>
<? } ?>
</Story_Main>
<Bottom_Box delete_if_empty="true" />
</Root>
