<?!= data.xml_declaration ?>
<?!= data.xmlRoot() ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_2_parties", data, {cover_title:"Super Simplified Convertible Loan Agreement", party1:data.company, party2:data.new_investor}) ?>
<?!= include("inc_cover_legalese", data, { }) ?>
<? var iHaveCap = data._orig_pre_money_valuation ? true : false; xmLog("simplified_note: data.pre_money_valuation = %s (%s)", data.pre_money_valuation, iHaveCap); ?>
<? var subTitle; ?>
<?    if (  iHaveCap && ! data._orig_discount) { subTitle = "Cap Only, No Discount" }
 else if (  iHaveCap &&   data._orig_discount) { subTitle = "Cap and Discount" }
 else if (! iHaveCap &&   data._orig_discount) { subTitle = "Discount, no Cap" }
 else if (! iHaveCap && ! data._orig_discount) { subTitle = "No Cap, No Discount" }

 if (data._orig_discount && data.hundred_minus_discount == undefined) {
 data.hundred_minus_discount = (100-100*data._orig_discount).toFixed(2);
 }
?>
<Firstpage_Sidebar></Firstpage_Sidebar>
<Story_Main>
  <chapter_header>Convertible Loan Agreement</chapter_header>
<para_1><span_smallcaps>This agreement</span_smallcaps> is made on <textvar name="Output Date" /> between</para_1>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.new_investor) ?> (the "Investor")</parties>
<parties><?!= include("inc_party", data, data.company) ?> (the "Company")</parties>
<para_1>(collectively, the "Parties").</para_1>

<para_1><span_smallcaps>Whereas:</span_smallcaps></para_1>
  <recitals>The Company is a private company incorporated in Singapore limited by shares.</recitals>
  <recitals>The Company wishes to pay a third party, but lacking sufficient funds, looks to the Investor for assistance.</recitals>
  <recitals>The result of this assistance will be a debt owned by the Company to the Investor.</recitals>
  <recitals>The Company presently lacking the funds to repay that debt in cash, the Company is prepared to issue equity to the Investor in future.</recitals>
  <recitals>The Investor and the Company desire and wish to enter into this Agreement to regulate the relationship between the Parties.</recitals>

  <para_1><span_smallcaps>It is hereby agreed</span_smallcaps> as follows:</para_1>

  <a_left_sidehead>Definitions</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>In this Agreement, except to the extent that the context otherwise requires, the following terms shall have the meanings set forth below:</numbered_2_para>
  <definition>Articles	means the Regulations in the Constitution of the Company.</definition>
  <definition>Payment to Third-Party	The payment of <?=data.third_party_payment_amount?> to a person named <?= data.third_party_name?> (the "Third Party").</definition>
  <definition>Principal	means <?=data.new_investor.new_commitment?>, that being agreed as the Singapore Dollar equivalent of the Payment to Third Party, less any repayments that may be made from time to time.</definition>

  <a_left_sidehead>Condition Precedent</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>This Agreement shall be effective when the Investor delivers to the Company evidence of the transfer of either</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_3_para>the "Payment to Third-Party" from the Investor to the Third Party; or</numbered_3_para>
  <numbered_3_para>the Principal from the Investor to the Company.</numbered_3_para>

  <a_left_sidehead>Subscription</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Parties agree to recognize a resulting debt of <?= data.new_investor.new_commitment ?> (the &#8220;Investment Amount&#8221;) owed by the Company in the form of a convertible promissory note (the &#8220;Note&#8221;) issued by the Company to the Investor.</numbered_2_para>

  <a_left_sidehead>Total Round Size</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Note issued to the Investor may form part of a series of such Notes issued on essentially identical terms (the "Series") except that the Investor, Investment Amount<?= data.variable_terms ?data.variable_terms:","?> and Closing Date may change from Note to Note. The total amount of the Series shall not exceed <?= data.amount_raising ?> without the written agreement of all the holders of the Notes in the Series currently outstanding.</numbered_2_para>

  <a_left_sidehead>Maturity Date</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Principal <? if (data._orig_interest != 0) { ?>and unpaid accrued interest on<? } else { ?>of<? } ?> the Note will be due and payable <?= data.term ?> from the date of the signing of this Agreement (the &#8220;<b>Maturity Date</b>&#8221;).</numbered_2_para>


  <a_left_sidehead>Interest</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para><? if (data._orig_interest != 0) { ?>
Interest on the Note will accrue on an annual basis at the rate of <?= data.interest ?> per annum based on a 365 days year.<? } else { ?>
The Note shall bear no interest. <? } ?>
</numbered_2_para>


<a_left_sidehead>Repayment</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_para>The Company may repay the Principal<? if (data._orig_interest != 0) { ?>and unpaid accrued interest<? }?> at any time prior to the Maturity Date, or conversion, whichever is sooner.</numbered_2_para>


<a_left_sidehead>Automatic Conversion</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para><b>Automatic Conversion at the Maturity Date.</b> On the Maturity Date, the Note, and any accrued but unpaid interest thereon, will automatically convert into Equity Securities at <?= (100 - 100*data._orig_maturity_conversion_discount).toFixed(2) ?>% of the Conversion Price.</numbered_2_para>

<a_left_sidehead>Optional Conversion</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>At any time prior to the Maturity Date, the Company may elect to convert the Principal<? if (data._orig_interest != 0) { ?>and unpaid accrued interest<? }?> into Equity Securities at the Conversion Price.</numbered_2_para>

<a_left_sidehead>Conversion Price</a_left_sidehead>

<numbered_2_para>The "Conversion Price" shall be <?= data.price_per_share ?> per share (the &#8220;<b>Conversion Price</b>&#8221;), subject to proportional adjustment for stock splits, stock dividends, combinations, recapitalizations and the like.</numbered_2_para>

<? if (data.antidilution || data.new_investor.antidilution) { var antidilution = data.antidilution || data.new_investor.antidilution; ?>
<a_left_sidehead>Anti-Dilution</a_left_sidehead>
<numbered_2_para>The Conversion Price determined above will be subject to a <?= antidilution ?> adjustment to reduce dilution in the event that the Company issues additional equity securities (other than:---)</numbered_2_para>
<numbered_3_para>shares reserved as employee shares described under the Company’s option pool;
founder shares identified as Class F shares and subject to vesting,
shares issued for consideration other than cash pursuant to a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or similar business combination approved by the Board;
shares issued pursuant to any equipment loan or leasing arrangement, real property leasing arrangement or debt financing from a bank or similar financial institution approved by the Board; and
shares with respect to which the holders of a majority of the outstanding Notes waive their anti-dilution rights</numbered_3_para>
<para_1>at a purchase price less than the calculated Conversion Price. In the event of an issuance of stock involving tranches or other multiple closings, the antidilution adjustment shall be calculated as if all stock was issued at the first closing. The conversion price will also be subject to proportional adjustment for stock splits, stock dividends, combinations, recapitalizations and the like.</para_1>
<? } ?>

  <a_left_sidehead>Sale of the Company</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>If the Company elects to consummate a sale of the Company prior to the Maturity Date, then at the election of the Investor, <? if (iHaveCap) { ?>either</numbered_2_para>
  <numbered_3_para><?}?>the Investor shall receive a payment equal to <?= data.acquisition_preference ?> times the Note<? if (iHaveCap) { ?>, or</numbered_3_para>
  <numbered_3_para>the Principal<? if (data._orig_interest != 0) { ?>and unpaid accrued interest<? }?> shall convert into Equity Securities at the Conversion Price.</numbered_3_para><? } else { ?>.</numbered_2_para><?}?>


  <a_left_sidehead>Amendment and Waiver</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The terms of this Agreement and the Note may be amended, or any term thereof waived, upon the written consent of the Company and the Investor.</numbered_2_para>


  <a_left_sidehead>No Security Interest</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Note will be a general unsecured obligation of the Company.</numbered_2_para>


  <a_left_sidehead>Investor Rights</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para><? if (data.information_rights == "quarterly then yearly") { ?>The Investor will have customary information and inspection rights, including receiving an annual budget, annual unaudited financial statements, quarterly unaudited financial statements, and any other information reports prepared for shareholders while the Note remains outstanding.<? } else { ?>
The Investor shall, by virtue of this Agreement, have no additional information rights over the financials of the company beyond those required by law or beyond any existing relationship.<? } ?>
<? if (data.new_investor.additional_rights) { ?>

<?= data.new_investor.additional_rights ?>
<? } ?>
  </numbered_2_para>


<?!= include("inc_assignment", data, { consent_article: "20.3.4" }) ?>

  <a_left_sidehead>Fees And Expenses</a_left_sidehead>
  <numbered_2_para>The Parties will bear their own fees and expenses incurred in the transaction.</numbered_2_para>

  <a_left_sidehead xname="medarb">Governing Law and Jurisdiction</a_left_sidehead>
  <?!= include("inc_mediation_arbitration", data) ?>

<chapter_header>Signatures</chapter_header>
    <para_1><span_smallcaps>In witness whereof</span_smallcaps> we have hereunto set our hands.</para_1>

	<?!= include("inc_enumerate_signatures", data, {rcpts_to:rcpts_to, _include2: { term: { new_investor: "investor" } } }) ?>
	
</Story_Main>
</Root>
